<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_silencer_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the thread for silencers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_silencer_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the application of threads on the barrel to install a silencer. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_scope_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about mounts for sights</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_scope_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about mounts for sights and their installation. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_grenade_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about the grenade attachments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_grenade_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the rifle mounts and their installation. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_magazine_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on extended magazines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_magazine_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about extended magazines. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_5.45_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 5.45 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_5.45_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about cutting barrel technology for caliber 5.45x39. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_5.56_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 5.56 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_5.56_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on cutting technology for the caliber 5.56x45. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_9.18_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 9.18 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_9.18_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about cutting barrel technology for caliber 9.18. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_9.19_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 9.19 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_9.19_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on cutting technology for the caliber 9.19. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_7.62.39_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 7.62x39 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_7.62.39_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about cutting barrel technology for caliber 7.62x39. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_7.62.51_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 7.62x51 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_7.62.51_descr">
		<text>A flash disk containing information about the technology of cutting the barrel to the caliber 7.62x51. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_7.62.54_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on cutting under 7.62x54 caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_7.62.54_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about cutting barrel technology for caliber 7.62x54. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_plates_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on plate insert</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_plates_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on a variety of plates and inserts in suits, as well as the technology of their installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_alloy_name">
		<text>Flash drive with alloys data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_alloy_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about a wide variety of materials-alloys, as well as the technology of their use. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_ceramics_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on ceramic elements</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_ceramics_descr">
		<text>A flash disk containing information about specific ceramic accessories for suits, as well as the technology for using them in suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_doublearmor_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on double-layered armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_doublearmor_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the inner layer of armor for suits, as well as the technology of its use in suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_segments_name">
		<text>Flash drive with segmented protection data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_segments_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on segmented protection for suits, as well as technology for its use in suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_carcass_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about frames</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_carcass_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on various frames for suits, as well as technologies for their use in suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_titan_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on titanium parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_titan_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about various titanium parts, as well as technologies for their use and application. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_protectivesbk_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on SBK-RKGTS.Mk.II</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_protectivesbk_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the system of radiochemical protection SBC-RKGTS.m.II, as well as the technology of its use in suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_obrabotka_name">
		<text>Flash card with data on the processing of suits</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_obrabotka_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the processing of various compositions. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_combined_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the combined protection</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_combined_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the combined protection, as well as the technology of its use in suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_regulirovka_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the adjustment of weapon components</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_regulirovka_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the adjustment of weapon components. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_polimers_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on polymeric materials</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_polimers_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about polymeric materials, as well as technologies for their use. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_trigger_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modifications of the trigger mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_trigger_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the modifications of the trigger mechanism. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_position_name">
		<text>Flash drive with positioning data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_position_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about exact positioning system, as well as its application technology. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_gazcilindr_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on gas cylinder modifications</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_gazcilindr_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on gas cylinder modifications. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_napileniya_name">
		<text>Flash drive with spraying data for weapons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_napileniya_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on spraying for weapons, as well as technologies for their use. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_avtomatrezhim_name">
		<text>Flash drive with automatic shooting data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_avtomatrezhim_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the automatic shooting mode, as well as the technology of its installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_porshen_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modification of the gas piston</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_porshen_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the modification of the gas piston. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_protivoves_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on counterbalance</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_protivoves_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on counterweights for weapons, as well as their installation technology. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_shtok_name">
		<text>Flash drive with stock modification data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_shtok_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on stock modification. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_skolzdetali_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about moving parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_skolzdetali_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the modification of the sliding parts. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_gazregulator_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the gas regulator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_gazregulator_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the gas regulator for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_speedmechanism_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the rate of fire rate increase</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_speedmechanism_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on mesenisms of increasing the rate of fire for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_tormoz_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about muzzle brake</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_tormoz_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the muzzle brake for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismstrigger_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about the mechanisms for the trigger system</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismstrigger_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the mechanisms for trigger systems for weapons. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismszatvor_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the mechanisms for the bolt</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismszatvor_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the mechanisms for the bolt for weapons. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanisgazregulator_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the mechanisms for the gas regulator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanisgazregulator_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the mechanisms for the gas regulator for weapons. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_stvol_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modification of the barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_stvol_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information on the modification of the barrel. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismtormoz_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the mechanisms for the muzzle brake</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismtormoz_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the mechanisms for the muzzle brake for weapons. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismstvol_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the mechanisms for the barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_mechanismstvol_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the mechanisms for the barrel for weapons. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_newmaterials_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the replacement of components</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_newmaterials_descr">
		<text>A flash disk containing information on the replacement of components with elements from new materials for weapons. Detailed guidance. Inexperienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_usilitel_name">
		<text>Flash drive with pneumatic amplifier data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_usilitel_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the pneumatic amplifier for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_servomotors_name">
		<text>Flash drive with servo mechanism data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_servomotors_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about servos and their installation. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_carbon_name">
		<text>Flash drive with carbon details</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_carbon_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about specific carbon parts and their installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_exosystems_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on systems for exoskeletons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_exosystems_descr">
		<text>A flash disk containing information about systems for exoskeletons and their installation. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_amortizators_name">
		<text>Flash drive with shock absorber data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_amortizators_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about shock absorbers and their use. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_artdetector_name">
		<text>Flash drive with artifact detector data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_artdetector_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the determinant of the position of artifacts for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_layers_name">
		<text>Flash drive with additional layers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_layers_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about additional layers for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_rubberizol_name">
		<text>Flash drive with rubber insulation data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_rubberizol_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about rubber insulation for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_thermoizol_name">
		<text>Flash drive with thermal insulation data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_thermoizol_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about thermal insulation for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_orgsteklo_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about details from plexiglas</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_orgsteklo_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about parts from plexiglass for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_constant_name">
		<text>USB stick with constantan data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_constant_descr">
		<text>A flash drive containing information on the modification of psyche protection for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_propitka_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the treatment of suits</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_propitka_descr">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the treatment of suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_chestplates_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on additional body armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_chestplates_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about additional body armor for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_newscopes_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on integrated sights</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_newscopes_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the modification of the integrated sights for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_contrast_name">
		<text>Flash drive with contrast sights</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_contrast_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the modification of the contrast of sights for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_autoaim_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the guidance system</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_autoaim_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information on the guidance system for sights for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_pnv_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about night vision googles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_pnv_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the night vision googles for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_dynamicscope_name">
		<text>Flash drive with adjustable sight data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_dynamicscope_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information on adjustable sights for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_lenses_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on lens modification</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_lenses_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information on the modification of lenses for weapons. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_rukoyatka_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modification of the handle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_rukoyatka_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the modification of the grip arms. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_compensator_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modification of the compensator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_compensator_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the modification of the weapon compensator. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_filters_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about filters</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_filters_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about additional filters for weapons and their installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_antenns_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about antennas</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_antenns_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on the installation of protective antennas for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_ecran_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on protective screens</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_ecran_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about protective screens for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_cupols_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on protective domes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_cupols_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about protective domes for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_closedbreath_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the system of closed breathing</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_closedbreath_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the system of closed breathing for suits. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_psystimulators_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the system of psychostimulation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_psystimulators_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the system of psychostimulation for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_skaneri_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about scanners</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_skaneri_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about scanners for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_ionwind_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about the system "Ion wind"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_ionwind_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the system for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_psyprotect_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about the modification of the psi protection</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_psyprotect_descr">
		<text>A flash drive containing information on the modification of psyche protection for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_pruzhini_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modification of the spring</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_pruzhini_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the modification of the weapon spring. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_priemnik_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the modification of the magazine receiver</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_priemnik_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the modification of the magazine receiver of a weapon. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_injectorfury_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about the injector "Rage"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_injectorfury_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the "Rage" injector for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_dustprotect_name">
		<text>Flash drive with dust protection system data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_dustprotect_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the dust protection system for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_injectorgemo_name">
		<text>Flash drive with hemoglobin injection data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_injectorgemo_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the hemoglobin injector for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_biostimulator_name">
		<text>Flash drive with biostimulant data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_biostimulator_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on biostimulants for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_feniksregen_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data about the system "Phoenix"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_feniksregen_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the system "Phoenix" for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_neuroemittor_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the neurowave emitter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_neuroemittor_descr">
		<text>Flash drive containing information about the neurowave emitter for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_complexdoctor_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about the complex "Doctor"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_complexdoctor_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the complex "Doctor" for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_gasballons_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on gas cylinders</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_gasballons_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on gas cylinders for suits, as well as their installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_artmodules_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on modules for artifacts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_artmodules_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the modules for artifacts for suits, as well as their installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_kreplenie_name">
		<text>Flash drive with unloading data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_kreplenie_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about unloading for suits, as well as their installation. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_restoresystem_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on regeneration systems</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_restoresystem_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information on regeneration systems for suits, as well as their installation. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_skatsystem_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the system "Skat"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_skatsystem_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the system "Skat" for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_marafonecsystem_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about the complex "Marathon"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_marafonecsystem_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the complex "Marathon" for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_poisonfilters_name">
		<text>Flash drive with data on the filtration of poisons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_poisonfilters_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the filtering system for poisons for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_systemvaryag_name">
		<text>Flash drive with information about the system "Varyag"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_systemvaryag_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the Varyag system for suits. Detailed guidance. Even experienced technicians will welcome such a find and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_dynamo_name">
		<text>Flash drive with dynamo data</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_upgr_flash_disk_dynamo_descr">
		<text>Flash disk containing information about the modification of dynamo machines. Detailed guidance. Technicians will be happy with this discovery and will be able to make a new upgrade or several new upgrades thanks to the information from the flash disk.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological item \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable information</text>
	</string>
</string_table>