<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<!--===========================================================
<			A.R.E.A. task translation by Fox and Surs
<===========================================================-->
<string_table>

	<!--===== dialogs_area =====-->
	<string id="deactivate_items_0">
		<text>Professor, can you deactivate a couple of my items?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_1">
		<text>I think so, we have a decontamination chamber in the laboratory. But you understand that I can not do this for you for free? I also want to warn you right away that our camera is quite large, and each time we spend almost the same amount of decontamination agents, so it will be more profitable for you to use our services if there are several infected items.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_2">
		<text>Well, I will take that into account.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_3">
		<text>That will cost 3000 UAH. Are you agree?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_4">
		<text>Yes, do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_5">
		<text>Maybe later.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_6">
		<text>Just a moment, I'll fix the gloves ... Let's get your things here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_7">
		<text>Thank you, Professor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="deactivate_items_8">
		<text>Looks like I forgot them somewhere, I'll be back.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="inf_craft_0">
		<text>Who else but a technician should know how to repair weapons and equipment, right? Tell me what they do in the Zone. I've been here quite recently.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_1">
		<text>What I know - I'll tell you. Ask what interests you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_2">
		<text>Tell me about barrel replacing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_3">
		<text>Tell me about the costume disassembly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_4">
		<text>Tell me about the costume repair.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_5">
		<text>Tell me about the gun repair.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_6">
		<text>Tell me about weapons dismantling.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_7">
		<text>Tell me about the handmade cartridges.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_8">
		<text>Tell me about something else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_9">
		<text>I'm not interested in anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_10">
		<text>The gun barrel is a delicate thing. To replace it, you need two things: the barrel itself and the replacement kit. The barrel is usually either bought or obtained from a gun by hand, from a knife to a sledgehammer. Rusty or dead barrels will not work, so they will need to be cleaned and tidied up. They are cleaned here by different means: gasoline, kerosene, vodka, water, solvents, cleaning kits and many others. Kits for replacement are different, that is, for each caliber has its own set. Basically, these field kits are available from dealers. Also, by the way, not every weapon and caliber can be replaced by the barrel, this too.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_11">
		<text>Well, the suit is not difficult to disassemble, the main thing here is accuracy. Disassembled mainly in sets, they are sold by merchants. There are sets for killed suits, and there are sets more delicate - for new ones. All important details are cut out of suits, the rest is thrown away, because here, in the Zone, there is no benefit from such trifles. Then, with the received spare parts, they repair their equipment or sell it. Still, as a rule, only those suits are dismantled, from which there is something to get. For example, it makes no sense to even spend your time and money on jackets or raincoats, and some live here on disassembling exoskeletons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_12">
		<text>In the field, repairing suits is better than artisanal, of course, difficult, but possible. Almost everything is used in the repair: from a rag to heavy armor plates. But the consumables themselves will not stick to the suit, so you still need something that can organize this whole thing. Then glue, sewing and repair kits will do, maybe something else. Well, consumables are also important. It's better to use high-quality than any garbage, because it can all cost more than even the technician. Glue, sewing and repair kits can be purchased from merchants. You can get consumables yourself, for example, from disassembling costumes, or you can also buy from merchants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_13">
		<text>Weapons in the zone are quite difficult and expensive to maintain. Repair by a professional can be much cheaper almost always, but you yourself simply need to regularly take care of your weapons with the help of improvised tools, since repairs are always more expensive. To repair trunks, just like to repair costumes, consumables and repair kits are needed. For repair, all spare parts can be bought from merchants or obtained by yourself, for example, many manually disassemble the trunks and repair them themselves.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_14">
		<text>Well, disassembling weapons is probably the easiest. Stalkers use everything that comes to hand, various sets of tools, sometimes they even use cutlery, but remember that you need to disassemble everything carefully. Further, spare parts are used to repair or sell.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_15">
		<text>Yes, also an interesting topic. More recently, merchants have all kinds of kits for making a cartridge, but any homemade ammunition will be worse than the factory one. Usually they use tools for making a cartridge and materials for them. All this can be bought from merchants. I can't tell further details, because each set has its own instruction. Well, read, it's not difficult to figure it out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_16">
		<text>Well, here in the Zone, in general, there are a lot of things that they do. Of rags and vodka - bandages. They themselves sew sleeping bags and backpacks, materials and tools for which almost any trader has. They also love to make cigarettes and jambs from improvised means, but this is more often in Freedom. Yes, a lot of things actually, the main thing is to turn your wit into it - and you will collect the trunk yourself, yes, there were some.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_craft_17">
		<text>Well, okay. Thanks for the info.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<!--===== dialogs_area_orders =====-->
	<string id="about_trade_dasc_0">
		<text>Listen, man, why is the assortment so meager? No costumes, no better weapons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_dasc_1">
		<text>Yes, the fact is that I can't store whole arsenals here, despite the fact that this is a huge hangar. There are no warehouses here, right? The roof leaks, holes in the walls, and emissions also cause problems. In the best case, you can poke a box of stewed meat. Stalkers order suits and weapons through me or other merchants. Shustry supplies the most expensive weapons, and here in Hollow I mostly hunt for trifles. And to order we carry only for their own.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_dasc_2">
		<text>Thanks, for the clarification.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_dasc_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_dasc_1">
		<text>No, man, you have a rotten reputation. As you correct - come, but for now I will not take risks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_dasc_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_dasc_0">
		<text>Lumberjack, why aren't you offering enhanced guns and suits?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_dasc_1">
		<text>Well, you know, I can't risk such orders with the first newcomer. Earn yourself a reputation and a good relationship - you will be more serious orders.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_dasc_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_trade_csky_0">
		<text>I'm new here and I have questions. Why is it so empty? Is there another crisis in Clear Skies?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_csky_1">
		<text>It's not a crisis, it's fine, it's just that we don't keep better weapons and armor here. It's banal and unprofitable. Traders, including myself, work on orders, we don't trade hand-to-hand. Mostly from outside the perimeter, the stuff is already delivered here through brokers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_csky_2">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_csky_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_csky_1">
		<text>Listen, I don't even know why they still haven't kicked you out of the clan. Correct your reputation - come.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_csky_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_actor_not_in_same_clan_csky_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_actor_not_in_same_clan_csky_1">
		<text>Man, I only work for my own, and for the rest I'm working on trifles. If you want to get your gear, go to the Lumberjack in Dark Valley or to Nimble.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_actor_not_in_same_clan_csky_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_csky_0">
		<text>Blackbird, look at all the serious equipment people have, they say they bought it from you. Maybe there's something better for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_csky_1">
		<text>Don't be offended, but you're new here, untested. You can get a better reputation and earn our trust, and you'll get better products.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_csky_2">
		<text>Okay, I'll be back.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_army_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_army_1">
		<text>I was ordered not to throw equipment to the left and right to anybody. You are not supposed to make such orders by rank, as you grow up - come.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_army_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_not_army_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_army_1">
		<text>Who the hell are you? Supply is made strictly for the part. Neither shoulder straps, nor our chevrons on you, I do not observe something.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_army_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_army_0">
		<text>Listen, why aren't you offering enhanced guns and suits?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_army_1">
		<text>Well, you know, I can't risk such orders with the first comer or newcomer. You do not have to be ranked for making such orders as you grow up - come.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_army_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_dolg_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_dolg_1">
		<text>You know, I have information that you should not trust. Correct your reputation - there will be a conversation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_dolg_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_dolg_0">
		<text>Colonel, can I get more serious equipment?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_dolg_1">
		<text>We cannot risk such orders with the first counter. Earn yourself a reputation, rank and good relations - your equipment will be more serious. I clearly explained?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_dolg_2">
		<text>Yes, sir.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_not_dolg_0">
		<text>Colonel, why don't you offer enhanced guns and suits? Even Duty equipment is not in stock.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_dolg_1">
		<text>I do not squander the breech. And I can't risk such orders with the first comer or newcomer. Earn your reputation, rank and good relations here - you will be more serious orders. But if you are not from "Duty", then you can forget about our equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_dolg_2">
		<text>Clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_freedom_0">
		<text>I would like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_freedom_1">
		<text>No man, I have info that you shouldn't be trusted. You get your reputation right, we'll talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_freedom_2">
		<text>Oh, I see.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_freedom_0">
		<text>Man, why aren't you offering enhanced guns and suits?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_freedom_1">
		<text>Relax, I can't risk these orders with a first-time or rookie. If you get a reputation, rank and relationship here, you'll get bigger orders.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_freedom_2">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_not_freedom_0">
		<text>Why aren't you offering enhanced guns and suits? I can't see even Freedom equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_freedom_1">
		<text>Man, I can't risk these orders with a first-time or rookie. You get a reputation, rank and relationship here, you'll get bigger orders. But if you're not from Liberty, you can forget about our equipment, too.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_freedom_2">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_merc_0">
		<text>I'd like to make an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_merc_1">
		<text>What? Get away from my shop, man. With your reputation among us, it's amazing that you're still alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_merc_2">
		<text>I'll be back.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_merc_0">
		<text>Colleague, why aren't you offering enhanced guns and suits?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_merc_1">
		<text>Where'd you come from? I can't risk these orders with a first-time or newbie. If you get a reputation, rank and relationship here, you'll get bigger orders.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_merc_2">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_not_merc_0">
		<text>Dushman, why don't you offer guns and suits more seriously? You can't even see the Mercenaries' equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_not_merc_1">
		<text>And you're a mercenary? Well, then our equipment's not for you either. And I can't risk ordering with the first person I meet or the new guy. You get a reputation, rank and relationship here, you'll get bigger orders.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_trade_sakharov_0">
		<text>Professor, I know you don't have much of a choice, but could I buy somehow your suits?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_sakharov_1">
		<text>It's difficult, but even though we're in the Zone, supplies sometimes come here as well. Please note that the number of orders will be limited, and so far I can't offer you more than one. However, if you do some work for me... I think you understand me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_sakharov_2">
		<text>Oh, I see.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_sakharov_0">
		<text>I'd like to place an order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_sakharov_1">
		<text>You see... We don't trust you very much, but you can always make things right.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_sakharov_2">
		<text>I hear you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_trade_bandit_0">
		<text>Fuck, godfather, where would I get a trumpet trump? Nichrome no one on the basis of dumb.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_bandit_1">
		<text>Well, in the Zone with valleys, the situation is as follows: we do not trade with hands almost, only with slag, because it is not profitable, and we carry to order. I manage the orders here. But if you're kind of muddy or unverified, then do not expect anything better than pasta. And if you're muddy, don't shine at all. You got that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_trade_bandit_2">
		<text>I got it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_bandit_0">
		<text>Godfather, I want to order a gun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_bandit_1">
		<text>No, you don't understand, get out of here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_order_bad_rep_bandit_2">
		<text>I'll be back.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--===== dialogs_redforest =====-->
	<string id="red_forester_about_tech_0">
		<text>Forester, you're kind of a technician, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_tech_1">
		<text>Yeah, I can and I know a lot of things, and there are tools. But I don't help randomly wandering in here, first I build a reputation for myself.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--===== dialogs_mlr_arena =====-->
	<string id="totaliz_pre_0">
		<text>What now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_pre_1">
		<text>I see you have earned a good reputation in the arena, which means you can bet and watch the battles! Yeah, yeah, just like the big debt bumps, think of it as my gift to you as a great fighter. Bets for you are purely symbolic from 1 to 5 thousand, the win depends on the number of participants, winners / losers, in general you can win net from 40% of your bet, and 3 times more.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="totaliz_begin_0">
		<text>I want to see the fight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_1">
		<text>Choose whose fight you want to see:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_2">
		<text>Man vs. man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_6">
		<text>Look what I got:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_9">
		<text>Two stalkers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_21">
		<text>Who you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_32">
		<text>On the stalker on the left.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_33">
		<text>On the stalker on the right.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_10">
		<text>A group of stalkers vs. a group of bandits</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_34">
		<text>On a group of stalkers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_35">
		<text>On a group of gangsters</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_11">
		<text>"Duty" against the prisoner "Freedom."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_23">
		<text>Who you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_36">
		<text>On "Duty"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_37">
		<text>On "Freedom"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_12">
		<text>Military vs. stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_24">
		<text>Who you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_38">
		<text>On military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_39">
		<text>On a stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_3">
		<text>A man with a monster.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_7">
		<text>Look what I have:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_13">
		<text>Stalker and pseudo-dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_25">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_40">
		<text>On stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_41">
		<text>On the pseudo-dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_14">
		<text>Duty and a group of snorks</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_26">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_42">
		<text>On the "loner"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_43">
		<text>On a group of snorks</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_15">
		<text>Bandit and bloodsucker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_27">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_44">
		<text>On the bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_45">
		<text>On a bloodsucker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_16">
		<text>Two military and burer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_28">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_46">
		<text>On the military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_47">
		<text>On the burer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_4">
		<text>Monster with a monster.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_8">
		<text>Look what I have:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_17">
		<text>Snork vs Snork</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_29">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_48">
		<text>Left snork</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_49">
		<text>Right snork</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_18">
		<text>Bloodsucker vs Bloodsucker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_30">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_50">
		<text>Bloodsucker on the left</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_51">
		<text>Bloodsucker on the right</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_19">
		<text>Chimera vs Chimera</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_31">
		<text>Who are you betting on?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_52">
		<text>Chimera on the left</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_53">
		<text>Chimera on the right</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_54">
		<text>How much do you bet?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_58">
		<text>I don't have that much money.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_20">
		<text>I'm not interested in that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="totaliz_begin_5">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="total_reward_dialog_0">
		<text>What about the money?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="total_reward_dialog_1">
		<text>Keep your winnings.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="total_reward_dialog_2">
		<text>It's okay, you lost.</text>
	</string>

	<!--===== dialogs_mlr =====-->
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_0">
		<text>Hello, Sparrow.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_1">
		<text>Hey.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_2">
		<text>How's the mood?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_3">
		<text>It's normal, but it's a little breathtaking. I never thought I'd end up in a monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_4">
		<text>How long have you been here, where do you come from?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_5">
		<text>And as a former me, the Zone has long been trampled. I've been hanging out at the bar lately, and I haven't dried up since the whole catavasia thing started here on Radar. Then it became interesting to know what happened and look at the chaos that began! The military are everywhere, the Lithuanians are in full prostration, so I came across experienced guys from the "monolith", except by a miracle did not shoot each other. Well, I helped the guys a little after the shock, decided to go to their base, and then I got used to it kind of.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_6">
		<text>Why did you decide to stay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_7">
		<text>Can't without the Zone. I've been thinking about it, but as I remembered, on a big land with me... ...this unemployment, this lack of perspective and this lack of will... Yeah, yeah, even here, it's more than that. Okay, well, we'll still have time at the base if I survive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wings_soldier_mon_mlr_1_talk_8">
		<text>Thank you for talking to me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_0">
		<text>Hey, Sapsan, you know about these locks?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_1">
		<text>Where did you get this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_2">
		<text>I needed it from an entrepreneur at a dump site to deliver it somewhere, split the loot equally, huh?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_3">
		<text>Are you sure?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_4">
		<text>Let's open it up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_5">
		<text>I changed my mind, I'm sorry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sapsan_talk_6">
		<text>So, uh... look what's in here and take what you like.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sacharov_talk_0">
		<text>Professor, there's a package for you from a businessman in a hoarding shop:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_task_sacharov_talk_1">
		<text>Okay, well... we conspired to have me pay for the delivery. Here's one of these wonderful artifacts:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_trader_first_meet_0">
		<text>Hey, are you a local leader here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_trader_first_meet_1">
		<text>Yeah, became a bump in the jail, and I'm gonna die it. What do you want?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_trader_first_meet_2">
		<text>Maybe work or something like that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_trader_first_meet_3">
		<text>You're the one who came to work right, there's nothing to sit on your brother's neck. Well, as for "something," I sell gear, you live off the money, download it to me. They call me Afghan and why, don't ask. Do you have any more questions?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_0">
		<text>Hey, man, you specialize in repairs here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_1">
		<text>Oh, wait, you seem normal-- not a pontore. Yeah, I'm a repairman here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_2">
		<text>What do you mean "normal"?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_3">
		<text>Yeah, I am, you know? I got into a zone of foolishness and juveniles because of that fucking beer. Asked "friends" to stand on the lookout while they cleaned the store, so they got a couple of blocks of cigarettes and a case of beer and they're throwing trash at us. Well, these guys, they threw away everything, and I ran the slowest, and they grabbed me shorter. I didn't rat them out, because there's only one fuckin' guy who would've sewed this robbery up, and who knows how I'd be met in a cell after that. I've been on parole for four years and I'm a man. Thought I wouldn't get involved in such stories anymore, find a job and shoot a hut, make my life better...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_4">
		<text>Well, then what?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_5">
		<text>Not so lucky for you, sorry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_6">
		<text>Oh, fuck you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_7">
		<text>Well, it didn't work out any further. There's no work, no money, and there's a buddy I've been doing time with. So the godfather offered to come here. He saw me because I smelled like Carlo's dad on the machines, so I had no choice. I would have gone to the stalkers, but I don't know anybody here, there wasn't even money for a smooth ride, and if the garbage was taken the second time - parole wouldn't have gotten off. But you know, I don't like all this prison romance, these concepts are alien to me, and they are not appropriate here in the Zone. This isn't the zone that's on the big land that could have provided more willpower. I wish I could save up the money and forget the hell out of this place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_8">
		<text>Well, that's how it is. What do they call you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_factory_smart_terrain_10_bandit_mechanic_first_meet_9">
		<text>Engineer, I think you understand why.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_1_0">
		<text>Greetings, Mentor. What is the "trivial" task?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_1_1">
		<text>We need to take over the stalker base on the outskirts. The brothers believe that they will interfere with our plans, and in the future will be a threat to the brotherhood.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_1_2">
		<text>Am I going in there alone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_1_3">
		<text>No, not alone. You'll meet another one of our bands, they're acting as storm troopers. I give newcomers some time to spend first with one group and then with another group to make it easier for them to define their place in the fraternity. It's just a shame that the third band is already dead. Okay, run to the mission, come on.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_2_0">
		<text>Hello, are you the Inquisitor? My mentor has informed me that from now on I am at your disposal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_2_1">
		<text>You've been a great help to us, he's finally gotten more or less tough guys. Hold a good gun and get some rest, you can take a walk to our BWC base. We'll run a marathon here and I'll call you in.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_dlg_2_2">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_1_0">
		<text>I'm not comfortable asking, but Mentor was talking about some third unit that was destroyed. Who did he mean?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_1_1">
		<text>Crystal Group. Once it was our most powerful group of forces, focused on defending the O-Consciousness, the Monolith, the Sarcophagus and its surrounding areas.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_1_2">
		<text>But what happened?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_1_3">
		<text>Then, as you know, some freak or a group of freaks broke our protective barrier called "Burner" and there came the Woofers, all kinds of "adventurers", even those bastards. I don't have a lot of information, because me and Preacher were doing some fucking... sorry, too many gaps in my old life. In general, I was distracted: the whole group was put under the spotlight, the guys held on to the last one, and could they prevent the threat or not, look for yourself. By the way, you can go through the Sarcophagus, find some information or maybe a weapon. Just grab something to get the radiation out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_1_4">
		<text>I think I'll go. I'm interested in the fate of this group.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_1_5">
		<text>Oh, come on, it's too dangerous.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_2_0">
		<text>Here, take this. Most of the information is either lost or I don't know how to read it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_2_1">
		<text>I'll tell the Mentor, he'll take care of it later. Sorry, guys.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_about_leader_0">
		<text>Why did you decide to stay in the fraternity? From what I understand, you were "zombie" first.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_5_1_dlg_about_leader_1">
		<text>I woke up somewhere near Pripyat, with people I didn't know, and nothing as they didn't remember. All we had in common was the uniform and we didn't let each other down. My old life is behind me, brother - so it happened and nothing can be fixed here. I also found my gun and twenty-two notches on it. I don't think I'll be accepted anywhere else.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="talk_to_gar_outpost_dolg_main_soldier_0">
		<text>What is this place, anyway?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_gar_outpost_dolg_main_soldier_1">
		<text>What are you, green or something? I don't know, a dump and a dump. Shitty place really is in terms of radiation and scumbags. There's a big depot on the right of the road, stay out of it, the gangsters have a base there. That's all I know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_gar_outpost_dolg_main_soldier_2">
		<text>What if Voronin finds out what you're doing here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_gar_outpost_dolg_main_soldier_3">
		<text>Know your place, stalker, otherwise you can lose your life. And where are the facts confirming your words? That's the same, there are none of them. Come on, go away, while we are good.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="baraholka_trader_two_talk_0">
		<text>Hi, what is this place?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_two_talk_1">
		<text>Dude, this is a flea market. Here stalkers do what they can, so they sell, here to my right behind the counter - our bartender and part-time hunter, though retired. My colleague is sitting on the left of the sofa.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_gar_talk_to_choper_0">
		<text>Tell me about this place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_gar_talk_to_choper_1">
		<text>What can I say, the place here is not very pleasant. Radiation at least ass shit, but all kinds of freaks, like dolgars and bandits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_gar_talk_to_choper_2">
		<text>Well, what about the places of interest?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_gar_talk_to_choper_3">
		<text>Here you can say the flea market is the main pearl, and the rest ... there is a railway to the north of the depot, do not pop into it, there the bandits rebuilt the camp. Further north is the direct road to the bar, where the post of dolgars is standing there. Near here, near the exit to the cordon, there is some kind of substation, but no one pokes in there, the place is bad, and the anomalies are full. Yes, by the way, we have as many as three abnormal zones nearby, and one of them, unfortunately, is in the substation itself, where electrons spark everywhere. These stalkers chose places and didn't allow anyone to approach them, though the bandits didn't need to, they didn't come to get artifacts here, but to steal from those who actually got them, therefore their place is so “strategically advantageous”, that is, approach to the bar. Well, the beast here is docile, at least on the surface and if you do not climb into the substation. There is one tunnel in which a piece of iron leads from the depot and the devil knows what is there, but the bandits generally do not go there. I feel that there are such samples of local fauna gathered, eh.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_start_dlg_0">
		<text>Oops, new faces in my eatery. Well, hi, man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_start_dlg_1">
		<text>Hey, are you a part-time job as a cook?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_start_dlg_2">
		<text>Yeah, well, that was a little useful for me, though. Hold the water, from the bottom of your heart. If you want a drink, a snack and a sip, you found the right place. We don't have 100 X-rays here, but we don't have any fags, all guys are straight, spoons aren't holes in gums.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_start_dlg_3">
		<text>Let there be time, I will.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_ab_find_number_0">
		<text>Is there anything else you can do for fun?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_ab_find_number_1">
		<text>I'm not your fucking clown. You puzzled me, though, anyway. How about some Russian roulette? I got an old Nagan here, playing the whole drum. I'm not gonna shoot myself, of course. I'm gonna shoot in the air. If you win, 5000 is yours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_ab_find_number_2">
		<text>Come on, then.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_4_0">
		<text>Hey, brother. I was supposed to get something from the Wings.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_4_1">
		<text>Whoo, here's your Abakan.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_4_2">
		<text>So, huh - earned the respect of "Wings"? Well done, you'll go far. Keep your squad branded bodysuit.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_3_0">
		<text>Your face is painfully sour, isn't it recoverable?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_3_1">
		<text>Not at the moment. Someone must have taken apart the remote control, but that's half the trouble. There's a faulty cooling system, we'll have to inspect it, but I doubt I'll be strong enough here. But that's not your problem anymore, right? Look, have you ever been assigned to any other squad?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_3_2">
		<text>I don't think so, Mentor said to go to you in a message and that's it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_3_3">
		<text>I think you have some potential in you. I'd like to thank our entire group and give you our signature combs, you deserve it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_3_4">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_3_5">
		<text>Great, I'll let the base know. Go to the supplier in Pripyat, he'll give you our uniforms, I think you'll be pleasantly surprised. By the way fighter, I hope to see you in our lines in the future.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_2_0">
		<text>What do you want from me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_2_1">
		<text>Protect this place with the guys while I try to assess the situation. I think the creatures here will bother us more than once.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_0">
		<text>And you must be our new companion. So, ready to take a walk and see the former greatness of this place?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_1">
		<text>Hi, are you "Wings"? Tell me about you and the situation that we forgot here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_2">
		<text>"Wings," exactly what's left of them. They call me Griffin, those guys over there are Sparrow and Pegasus, the vain man with the SVD is the Wind. So listen, there used to be a lot of us here, and this place was terrifying to the hearts of the infidels. Until one of the stalkers sabotaged the local zombie station, so to speak. And what started here, it had to be seen - "Duty", "Liberty", loners and military. Our best units took the most powerful blow, as a result: all dead. But in fact, no one managed to get hold of this place, I do not know what happened here, but these places are now inhabited by all kinds of creatures and zombies, among others.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_3">
		<text>[...]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_4">
		<text>Now we need to go to the bunker under the installation of the so-called "Burner" and assess the situation, to answer one of the main questions facing the current brotherhood: "Is it realistic to restart this installation?" Are you ready?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_5">
		<text>I'm ready, let's go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_4_dlg_1_6">
		<text>Not ready, I'll take a look around for a while.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_1_0">
		<text>I'm here about an assignment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_1_1">
		<text>These "Cossacks" were sniffing out the activity of our patrols on Radar and the periphery of Pripyat. I want you to make a choice how we deal with this next, it will be a test of your thinking abilities.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_1_3">
		<text>I think we need to deal with their nearest bridgehead, that is, the barrier. We need to discourage them from spying.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_1_4">
		<text>We should find the rest of the intelligence team. I don't think the two of them acted together.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_1_5">
		<text>Yeah, well, in that case, you can go storming. Hold a dozen grenades, let's see how you handle it, since you suggested it. The brotherhood has no soldiers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_1_6">
		<text>And you're damn right it is. Except that's how bad their PDA reports are. One of our recruits you were standing with earlier was supposed to steal heels of Monolithic combs from a warehouse and give them to saboteurs. We'll take care of the rest of the grief scouts ourselves, you gotta figure out this spy. I called the recruits, they should be here, they also know that I have a serious conversation with everyone, ask them what I would like them to do.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_2_0">
		<text>Here you go:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_2_1">
		<text>Um, what kind of box is this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_3_dlg_2_2">
		<text>[...]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_2_dlg_1_0">
		<text>What's my next challenge?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_2_dlg_1_1">
		<text>Follow me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_2_dlg_2_0">
		<text>You see these beauties? Take them and kill them. That's how you prove your loyalty to our cause. Come on, brother, no shadow of a doubt.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_2_dlg_2_1">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_2_dlg_3_0">
		<text>Well done! These cattle tried to break through to the center, but our guys took them, pre-stunned by the explosion. Now I'll have the other test subjects cut off their heads and pack them in a nice box. Come back in an hour, you're gonna have to run for a while.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_0">
		<text>Well, hello there, brother. Why are you here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_1">
		<text>Well, you called me for something.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_2">
		<text>Because of the money, brother.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_3">
		<text>I came here for my secret desire.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_4">
		<text>At the call of the heart. I came here to defend our Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_5">
		<text>Hmm and where do you come from such jokers. In general, the "Monolith" is not the same as before. Roughly speaking, fraternity is supported only by a handful of enthusiasts. After disabling the Burner, many fell out of the ranks of the group. Some stayed here simply because they would die outside the brotherhood, but that does not mean that sooner or later they will leave. And some, like I stayed here only because they want to build their personal paradise and the technologies of "O-Consciousness", allow themselves to do this ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_6">
		<text>At least honestly. In general, the "Monolith" is not the same as before. Roughly speaking, fraternity is supported only by a handful of enthusiasts. After disabling the Burner, many fell out of the ranks of the group. Some stayed here simply because they would die outside the brotherhood, but that does not mean that sooner or later they will leave. And some, like I stayed here only because they want to build their personal paradise and the technologies of O-Consciousness, allow themselves to do this ... you are honestly speaking an interesting case.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_7">
		<text>Here it is the very thing that keeps people like us in brotherhood. In general, the "Monolith" is not the same as before. Roughly speaking, fraternity is supported only by a handful of enthusiasts. After disabling the Burner, many fell out of the ranks of the group. Some stayed here simply because they would die outside the brotherhood, but that does not mean that sooner or later they will leave. And some, like we stayed here only because we want to build our own personal paradise and the technologies of "O-Consciousness", allow themselves to do this ...
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_8">
		<text>Don't make me laugh. In general, the "Monolith" is not the same as before. Roughly speaking, fraternity is supported only by a handful of enthusiasts. After disabling the Burner, many fell out of the ranks of the group. Some stayed here simply because they would die outside the brotherhood, but that does not mean that sooner or later they will leave. And some, like I stayed here only because they want to build their personal paradise and the technologies of "O-Consciousness", allow themselves to do this ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_9">
		<text>Did you talk about some trials?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_10">
		<text>There is a time for everything, a new brother. Remember that your past life is coming to an end. The brotherhood eventually became even smaller, but much more embittered. What you have to go through here, in particular during the tests, will seem like a real horror to any objectively normal person. To begin with, I want to see your will, I'm taking all your equipment from you and I want you to kill a pseudo-giant who has settled nearby. And how you do it - whether with your bare hands, with the help of your brothers or with the help of a found weapon, this does not bother me. So you show yourself what you are capable of achieving the goal and what means you are likely to resort to. Give me your stuff.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_1_11">
		<text>Um, okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_2_0">
		<text>The creature is dead. But why do we kill them, unless they can become our allies in the fight against ... infidels.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="main_monolith_mlr_task_1_dlg_2_1">
		<text>The forces of "O-Consciousness" are not even enough to keep a handful of people in check, and you're talking about mutants. Well done, your things are in the blue box here, you can pick them up. When you are ready for the next challenge, come.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="take_barman_doc_from_factory_pole_0">
		<text>Howdy, Barman. I visited the factory in Polyana, found some records. Interested in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="take_barman_doc_from_factory_pole_1">
		<text>Come here, let's see what kind of garbage ... so, well, it's only that some sofa anonymous or collectors will appreciate, you can safely wipe with these pieces of paper. But for the solution to the secrets of the plant respect, of course, keep some money:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_0">
		<text>Well, I'm ready.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_1">
		<text>Well, I'm directly eager to find out all the secrets of this place. But be on the lookout, I hope we can do without incident.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_2_0">
		<text>Hmm ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_2_1">
		<text>That's always like that, understand? Again nearly died and again you saved me. And there was nothing ... There you have the moral, man: rely only on objective, versatile information, draw his mother's parallels and don't live in pink glasses. Ugh, bitch!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_2_2">
		<text>What's next?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_2_3">
		<text>Will you give me the documents? After a sortie to my memory, I'll keep it. Unfortunately, there is nothing to pay you back, but I can become you a good friend if you want to wander with me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_2_4">
		<text>Yes, hold on, they do not need me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_2_dlg_2_5">
		<text>Are you kidding me? I risked my life because of you, and three times. I'd better go give the bartender.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="talk_to_saving_rookie_dlg_0">
		<text>Howdy, man. Thank you very much, otherwise I think the bloodsucker would gobble up me, the door is rather flimsy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_saving_rookie_dlg_1">
		<text>How did you end up here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_saving_rookie_dlg_2">
		<text>As banal as it may sound, I was looking for something to eat here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_saving_rookie_dlg_3">
		<text>Did you find anything?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_saving_rookie_dlg_4">
		<text>Nope, only ruin and dust. Listen, if you want to make some money, I have a proposal.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_0">
		<text>What did you want to offer me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1">
		<text>This is all a factory. You know, the place here is certainly not the "first freshness", but no one has come here, since frankly there are not a lot of artifacts here, and it is dangerous here for the outskirts of the Zone. But recently rumors about a local plant began to go, they say that some kind of weapon is stored here, which the government was developing after the first explosion. Well, you probably know stories about the Marked and the Strelka, which almost all the underground complexes have plundered? And here is the hope for newcomers without delving into the center to get something that is valuable and expensive. So they popped here, and I am among them, and after us the bandits, since where there are stalkers, there you can get hold of swag.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_2">
		<text>Would you like to invite me together to search for valuable information in this place?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_3">
		<text>Yeah. But first, please help me, it's better not to hang around here without a gun. I had a good shotgun, I collected money for it before I came here, but I went to the local substation (it's not far from here) and there was some strange anomaly, well, in general I was careless and it just hit! Good thing I was not hurt, but I really screwed up, so I threw the gun and ran here. You can laugh, but when it's a miracle I didn't die... Anyway, will you get it for me? Oh, and, uh, if you want to help me with something else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_4">
		<text>Well, I'm going to get your shotgun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_5">
		<text>Not now.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_0">
		<text>Take your gun, and the anomaly is so strange really, I haven't seen such electro.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_1">
		<text>Thank you, take this as a token of gratitude, I found it nearby. Get ready well, come one night, let's go to the factory.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_from_factory_0">
		<text>Honestly, I was already at the factory.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_from_factory_1">
		<text>Come on man, don't lie. Do you have evidence?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_from_factory_2">
		<text>Yes, that's all I found there:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_from_factory_3">
		<text>No.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_from_factory_4">
		<text>In business, but ... there are no miracles. Thank you for at least clarifying the situation, and it looks dangerous there. You have nothing to pay me back except for your shotgun. Hold on, I won't need him anymore:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rookie_pole_task_1_dlg_1_from_factory_5">
		<text>Well, do not fuck me up.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_trader_day_0">
		<text>Grandmas and artifacts drive fast, bitch!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_trader_day_1">
		<text>Here, take that I managed to sell, there's no art, believe me, please:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_trader_night_0">
		<text>Grandmas and artifacts drive fast, bitch!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_trader_night_1">
		<text>Take what is, do not shoot only:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="request_to_no_go_nimble_bar_0">
		<text>And what is interesting in those rooms behind the guard?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="request_to_no_go_nimble_bar_1">
		<text>Not what, but who. There is an experienced person alone there, he can get what unique equipment you want. But now I won't let you go there. First I have to make sure that you can be trusted, that is, you must have a good reputation.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="request_to_no_go_nimble_bar_1_0">
		<text>Well, now can I go to this person?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="request_to_no_go_nimble_bar_1_1">
		<text>Hmm, yes. I will warn Garik, that person's name is Nimble. Right and right along the corridor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="request_to_no_go_nimble_bar_2_0">
		<text>And what is interesting in those rooms behind the guard?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="request_to_no_go_nimble_bar_2_1">
		<text>Not what, but who. There is an experienced person alone there, he can get what unique equipment you want. Hmm, I know you as a reliable person with a good reputation. You can tell Garik to let you in and go to this man whom they call the nimble. Right and right along the corridor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="request_go_to_nimble_0">
		<text>I need to get through.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_0">
		<text>Wow, you and your detachment broke through the Burner and stayed there for half a year?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_1">
		<text>Well, not half a year, but a little over a month. Yes, that was me. Lukash, nice to meet you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_2">
		<text>And how was it, tell me, eh?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_3">
		<text>Listen, well, I don't want to stir up the past, we got out and that's fine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_4">
		<text>Oh, and thanks for that.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_2_0">
		<text>Well hello, Gatekeeper.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_2_1">
		<text>So you are going to Limansk? If it weren't for Leshiy, well, you understand. Welcome and come on here, just be careful and try not to get on our patrols, you have no agreements with them.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_1_0">
		<text>I collected the money.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_1_1">
		<text>You can go to the beach now, I warned them. You'll be contacted by a mercenary named "The Gatekeeper", act on circumstances. And find something to shed some light on Scar's disappearance, please.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_1_0">
		<text>Hey, Lukash. I'd like to find Leshyi, is there a man like you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_1_1">
		<text>Why would you do that? Well, you're lucky enough to get down to the ground floor, he'll be standing downstairs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_1_2">
		<text>Thank you, finally.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_0">
		<text>You're Leshyi, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_1">
		<text>Yeah, you need a guide or how...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_2">
		<text>"Or how." Anyway, I know something about your past and I could use your help, mercenary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_3">
		<text>Um... what kind of help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_4">
		<text>Can you negotiate with those mercenaries who guard the bridge in Redwood? I have to go to Limansk. I know this sounds cocky, but I can promise you that I'll try to find all the traces that may have been left of Scar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_5">
		<text>You know, it's been a long time since I've been in the syndicate, I don't even know who runs that group by the bridge. I've got some other connections, so I just need some time. In the meantime, you'll get the money, yes, yes - the most common rustling money, a thousand edas 150 at least.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_0">
		<text>Hello to you, Lesnik. I'm here because I want to get to the other side of the bridge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_1">
		<text>Over a bridge, then? That's got nothing to do with me, go with the people who hold the bridge now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_2">
		<text>You may have remembered, but it's thanks to you that Limansk is now crawling with mercenaries.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_3">
		<text>I haven't memorized it, but I don't want to help you either. I'm still not sure if I did the right thing helping that "mercenary."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_4">
		<text>Look, please help me. Who cares if you did the right thing or not? Either way, I can find out if I go into town.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_5">
		<text>Look, if you don't tell me everything quickly, I'll write you a trip to the morgue.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_6">
		<text>Old man, if the Zone wants me there, I'll be there. But it's in your best interest to help me now, because no one if it'll favor you next time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_2_1_7">
		<text>Eh, that's true. I saw something special in Scar, and Zone needed him. And you... yeah, I'd like to know what happened to him. So listen: we helped get the "mercs" out of the bubble. Then, when everything settled down - they came to me, led by Leshiy. It must have been one of those who said that I also took part in the rescue. So I talked to Leshiy, he gave me some provisions, money and ammunition, and left. He said he went to the Army warehouses, to Freedom. That was where you should look for him. It's true that several years had passed, but judging from our conversation, he seriously intended to join them.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_0">
		<text>I've heard something about the story of "Clear Sky" and I'd like to follow in the footsteps of your group.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_1">
		<text>What are you doing looking for? Ha, listen to this. You don't stand a chance of surviving in those parts, but even if you do, it's gonna be really hard to find information about our stay there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_2">
		<text>Cold, aren't you interested? Or what you want for detailed information.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_3">
		<text>Uh, okay. But first help us lime a pack of swamp bloodsuckers and then I'll tell you everything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_4">
		<text>Give me the coordinates of these humanoids.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_5">
		<text>Fuck you, suck on your own bloodsuckers.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_2_0">
		<text>I could barely handle them. Let's get the info in there now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_2_1">
		<text>The Observers have already reported to me, well done. Well, you're a fighter, then. So listen: the guys were telling me how the damn bridge in Limansk was stormed. In case you didn't know, in the city, as well as on the way to it from the Red Forest, the mercenaries are running everything. Of course, they won't lower the bridge for you, but there's still a living participant in those events and call him "The Forester". It was he who somehow agreed with Scar that a group of "merks" would lower the bridge while our fighters were covering them from the other side. I think you should go to the "Lesnik" and talk to him. And here's the details of the passage to the "Red Forest" from "Militari", if you don't already have, and a small reward for the bloodsuckers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_2_2">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_0">
		<text>Check me, but watch out for your hands!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_1">
		<text>Ahh... Okay, you wait...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_2">
		<text>Got arms and legs, you're right.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_3">
		<text>Well, what's up? Does it suck at all? What the fuck are you talking like a fish?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_4">
		<text>Truth be told, bro, you can get a first-aid kit or two, but not the fact that it'll help. And I have a real topic, we'll make it for 2500 UAH. I've got one syringe, I'm going to fall down, heals everything, but you won't stop glowing... In general, without a normal antidote, it's gonna get worse. Finish 3000 UAH from the top and all this will pass. Well, did you finish it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_5">
		<text>Oh, for fuck's sake, you're gonna get paid again... Take it, molded it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_6">
		<text>No, fuck, just get the radiation out. I'll patch the rest up at these prices myself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_7">
		<text>You didn't make, you fucking robbed, you fucking robbed your brother.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_8">
		<text>I'm not fucking around in this, but I think you should feel better. Look, don't fucking fall apart.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_9">
		<text>Everything, although there's still... Karoche, I didn't put you in, you put me in. If you die at an angle, it's not my fault. Do you understand? I got it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_heal_10">
		<text>You're filtering the market, okay? You die in here somewhere, it's not my fault. Now get out of here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_dasc_traveler_mlr_0">
		<text>Hey, man, you waiting for someone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_dasc_traveler_mlr_1">
		<text>Oh, hey! You don't need a guide? So, look where I can safely take you: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Cordon [Rookie village] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Hidden base] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Garbage [Junkyard]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_dasc_traveler_mlr_list_0">
		<text>Remind me where your routes lead?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_dasc_traveler_mlr_list_1">
		<text>\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Cordon [Rookie village, 1000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Hidden base, 2500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Garbage [Junkyard, 2500]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_dasc_traveler_mlr_base_0">
		<text>I need your help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_dasc_traveler_mlr_base_1">
		<text>Where are we going?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_dasc_traveler_mlr_base_2">
		<text>To Cordon %c[255,238,153,26][Rookie village, 1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_dasc_traveler_mlr_base_3">
		<text>To the Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][Hidden base, 2500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_dasc_traveler_mlr_base_4">
		<text>To garbage %c[255,238,153,26][Junkyard, 2500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_dasc_traveler_mlr_base_5">
		<text>Perhaps I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_0">
		<text>Hi, who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_1">
		<text>I'm a conductor calling Leopard. As you can see, the "dead city" is surrounded on all sides by all sorts of enemies, but few people know about the underground sewer network, but I know. And we can safely go outside the city, and then I can take you to one of our bases. True, there are not very many of them:\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red Forest [outpost behind the bridge]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_list_0">
		<text>Remind me where your routes lead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_list_1">
		<text>Look: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red Forest [outpost in front of the bridge, 2500]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_0">
		<text>I want to leave the city.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_1">
		<text>Where are we going?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_3">
		<text>To the Red Forest %c[255,238,153,26]["outpost in front of the bridge", 2500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_4">
		<text>Perhaps I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_0">
		<text>Howdy, what are you doing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_1">
		<text>I can ask you a very reasonable question: "And you fuck?". But something still concerns you, namely, I provide services for "my" - the services of a guide. I know short and safe routes to:\n%c[255,238,153,26]• "Dead City" [Trade cooperative] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red Forest [outpost behind the bridge]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_list_0">
		<text>Remind me again, where do your routes lead?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_list_1">
		<text>Here: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• "Dead city" [Trade cooperative, 8000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red Forest [outpost behind the bridge, 2500]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_0">
		<text>I need your services.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_1">
		<text>Where to?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_2">
		<text>In the "Dead City" %c[255,238,153,26][Trade cooperative, 8000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_3">
		<text>To the Red Forest %c[255,238,153,26]["outpost behind the bridge", 2500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_4">
		<text>Perhaps I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="inf_trader_sell_stashes_0">
		<text>I want to buy info about the cache.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_sell_stashes_1">
		<text>Prepared money? 5000 UAH</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_sell_stashes_2">
		<text>Hold on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_sell_stashes_3">
		<text>Not.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_sell_stashes_4">
		<text>I send coordinated to your device. What is in the cache is unknown, maybe nothing at all.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_dog_marsh_part_two_0">
		<text>I saw that weirdo with a dog and even talked to him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_dog_marsh_part_two_1">
		<text>Oh, how, but I already forgot about this request. So what is there?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_dog_marsh_part_two_2">
		<text>Yes, as always, no specifics, Lassie her name said, they say. Well, there are two more puppies with her, also, like they did not show signs of aggression.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_dog_marsh_part_two_3">
		<text>Puppies? Oh, what only in the zone you will not see. Well, thanks, I'll know now that we're not the only Doc who has such a “dog breeder”. If necessary, take the info about the transition of one, from the military to the Red Forest. We got an echo of the past adventures of the group, well, a bit of provisions.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="talk_to_inf_trader_0">
		<text>Who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_inf_trader_1">
		<text>I am an informant here and can offer you all kinds of services. At the moment, this is various information and maps with paths to a particular location. Don't ask where it comes from.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_0">
		<text>Do you have the latest information?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_1">
		<text>I am ready to share with you information about the marsh doctor for 7000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_2">
		<text>There is information about a strange stalker who is looking for the Gunslinger group for 10,000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_3">
		<text>I have information shedding light on the second shutdown of the "Brain Scorcher" for 15,000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_4">
		<text>I have information about the adventures of the mysterious stalker on the "Generators" for 24,000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_5">
		<text>Not at the moment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_6_7_8_9">
		<text>Come on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_10">
		<text>This is not interesting to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_11">
		<text>The old man is now in the Swamps, everything is waiting for his friend, “Gunslinger”. Recently, a guy came to him, to whom the Doctor told his story, and what is important - the story of the Gunslinger group itself! You can personally go to him and see.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_12">
		<text>This same stalker who went to the Doctor is now looking for traces of the Gunslinger group. He has already researched laboratories in Dark Valley and Yantar and is clearly not going to stop there. Judging by verified sources, he wants to break into the center of the Zone and finish what the aforementioned group of stalkers could not for one reason or another.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_13">
		<text>This is the same stalker and he turns off the "Brain Scorcher"! I wonder when they guess at least somehow harm the control panel, and not masturbate the switch every time? Rumor has it that he is now going to Pripyat and that he had some kind of assignment from the Doctor. I don't know if the old man wants to find his friend in this way or whether something more is hidden behind this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_information_from_trader_14">
		<text>Have you ever heard of Generators? Until recently, this place was considered only a myth, but after the second campaign of the Strelka group to the center of the Zone, all doubts were dispelled. There is persistent debate about what is located there, but old satellite images indicate some strange infrastructure, after which this place was named. Apparently, the Monolith group is controlled from there, as well as all the important processes in the Zone. So our stalker has already gone there and I think he is serious, probably his intervention could lead to serious changes in the Zone, the leaders of some groups have already expressed their dissatisfaction with this information.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_0">
		<text>I want to buy info on various transitions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_1">
		<text>Look what I have:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_2">
		<text>From Army Warehouse to Radar %c[255,238,153,26][25000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_3">
		<text>From Radar to the bunker below it %c[255,238,153,26][37500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_4">
		<text>From Radar to Central Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][50000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_5">
		<text>From central Pripyat to the outskirts %c[255,238,153,26][100000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_6">
		<text>From central Pripyat to NPP %c[255,238,153,26][150000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_7">
		<text>From the southern part of the NPP to the northern %c[255,238,153,26][175000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_8">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_9_12_14_16_18_20">
		<text>Do you have the money with you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_10">
		<text>No.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="inf_trader_buy_transitions_11_13_15_17_19_21">
		<text>Yeah, here you go.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_0">
		<text>Do you need any help, Noah?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_1">
		<text>Well, I have a few things to do:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_2">
		<text>Bring in a new shotgun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_3">
		<text>Deal with the snorks on the South Plateau.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_4">
		<text>Sorry, I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_5">
		<text>I don't like mine at all, so if you brought me something like "Saiga"... but I don't know if I can get a weapon like that in the Zone. But I've seen a couple of bandits with Protekta, bring me a gun like that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_6">
		<text>It's time to finish with these creatures, they want to kill me day and night, they just have a raging hatred for me, I can feel it. Every night I hear the breath of one of these things crawling near the barge. Waiting and sniffing. To get to the plateau, you'll have to use the teleporter, I marked it on the map, it's not far from the "burnt-out farm".</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_1_noah_done_0">
		<text>Keep your "Protecta".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_1_noah_done_1">
		<text>Great, thank you. Now these things are gonna think three times before they get in here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_2_noah_done_0">
		<text>I screwed up those snorks, a lot of them were there. And why are they hunting you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_2_noah_done_1">
		<text>I don't know... I used to go there occasionally and clean things up, but now I don't have time to watch the puppies. Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_0">
		<text>Easy, easy, don't shoot! You almost killed me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Why did you even come here? Go on, don't waste my time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_2">
		<text>I got it. Okay, don't get too excited, do you need any help? Answer a few questions?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_3">
		<text>Come on, don't just piss off.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_0">
		<text>I have a few questions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_1">
		<text>[...]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_2">
		<text>Where did you get that dog?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_3">
		<text>Why do you live on this boat?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_4">
		<text>Why don't you trust people?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_5">
		<text>I should probably go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_7">
		<text>This is Lassie. Nice bitch ... If not for her, they would have devoured me in a dream a long time ago. Damned mutants ... I hate it! Only you close your eyes - and they are already there, pulling claws, fangs, feeling ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_8">
		<text>Oh, I see.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_9">
		<text>Why would she have puppies if she's always hanging around you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_10">
		<text>It's the Ark! Remember... If you want to live, remember! When the Wave goes, be there for it. Here - you have a chance to survive... No mutant will get through here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_11">
		<text>What the fuck is the wave, where did you get that from?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_12">
		<text>Because these creatures are watching me day and night. You don't understand ... those snorts from the southern plateau followed me right up to the "Ark"! I'm an experienced hunter and I know that they wouldn't give a damn about chasing the victim for so long. But here something is unclean, it seems to me that they have a reason. I don't know what a collective, or perhaps a protectorate, was seeking ... and my guesses were only confirmed by the recent attack of these creatures on a barge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_13">
		<text>Okay, this is the Zone. Anything can be here, but if your guesses are correct, then we are now in a deep ass.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_14">
		<text>I have survived too much.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start_0">
		<text>Well, what's your special case?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start_1">
		<text>You will see in a moment. As you know, the most dangerous enemy to man is man. There's an ATP near here, and there's a group of unscrupulous individuals who are shaking down everyone, and I'm getting pretty fed up with it. We need to deal with them once and for all. All right, are you in? Grab a better gun and plenty of ammo, cause it's gonna get hot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start_2">
		<text>I'm in, let's go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start_3">
		<text>Sorry, but somehow without me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start1_0">
		<text>Yeah... What a bunch of bastards...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start1_1">
		<text>How's that? Have you tasted blood? Heh-heh! Soon you'll be a real shark. Murder's a way to get rich around here, too, and stop thinking yourself up. If it ain't you, it'll be you. A dead man doesn't need the loot, as you know. Well, let's go to the village.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start2_0">
		<text>Eh, it's a good thing there are people like you. Why would you doing this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_3_start2_1">
		<text>Who else but me? Wolf used to watch the village... Till something got into his head and he packed up and left for the center of the Zone. What for? Why? Hell knows. Maybe he'll come back. I don't think I'm getting out of here. Who am I going to leave people like you here for? How many more of you will there be? Here's a tried-and-true route to the garbage. Right on the road, over the bridge, then you'll know from the map. And keep this, so ours in the village will know you're one of their own. Now you can consider yourself a Stalker.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_2_start_0">
		<text>I'm ready now what?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_2_start_1">
		<text>Now listen to me carefully, stalker. To survive, and not just survive, you have to search. And he who seeks, finds. Like someone else's stash. What? Not fair? Not fair? We're in the zone. And if you don't get your noble impulses up and running, you're not gonna last long here. Now keep looking. I got a backpack hidden around here somewhere. See if you can find it. When you find it, bring me its contents.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_2_start1_0">
		<text>I found your stash. I see you've got a sense of humor, joker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_2_start1_1">
		<text>Excellent! You are not as bad as you seem. I can't disappear with your attention in the Zone. And do not throw this jar out; you can still bungle out of it if your hands grow from the right place. Get ready for now, I have a special case for you.</text>
		<text>That's great! You're not as bad as you look. With your attentiveness you won't get lost in the Zone. And don't throw that tin away, you can still make something out of it if your hands grow from the right place. In the meantime prepare yourself, I have a special job for you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_0">
		<text>Another one, coming in here like it's a honeydew. You're lucky you made it to the village. Why don't you come with me and I'll show you the local specialties and see what kind of fruit you are.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_1">
		<text>Come on, look, no surprises.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_2">
		<text>Thanks of course, but I don't have time for this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_3">
		<text>Listen to me and stay close, then there won't be any surprises. So, one of the big dangers in the Zone is mutants. Even the smallest beast can get you into a lot of trouble. There's a herd of boars just off the road, we've got to deal with them, it's getting dangerous. Don't get in front of me, if they come at you, find a higher place where they can't get you!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_cancel_0">
		<text>Is your offer still valid? You were going to show the neighborhood.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_cancel_1">
		<text>Yes, still valid. So, the first of the dangerous things that are here are mutants. It's been a while since we went hunting, and we're going to fix it now. Grisha noticed some wild boars in a ravine not far away. We will deal with them. Be careful, these aren't simple boars. Aim for the torso or back, they have a stronger snout. Shall we go?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_cancel_2">
		<text>Of course, let's go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start_cancel_3">
		<text>First need to prepare, a little later.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start1_0">
		<text>Huh, knock them off. One fanger almost grabbed me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start1_1">
		<text>So, how do you like the local fauna? That's not what you're gonna see here. Here's my hunting knife, and you can't open cans with yours. You can't go anywhere in the Zone without a good knife. You can use it to cut mutants with thinner skins, and for a bigger creature you'll need something bigger. Sometimes you have to eat whatever you find, and the meat of mutated creatures is not an exception, but without the right preparation, I would not advise you to risk your life. There's Gourmet in the village, go to him, he'll tell you anything you want to know about it. Scientists have settled in the north, they have requests for mutant samples. The thing is, of course dirty... Gut those beasts, but what can't you do for money, huh? Come on, knife in your hands and get the trophies, and I'll cover you for now. When you're done, let's move on to a pile of anomalies, stop at the radioactivity sign.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start2_0">
		<text>What's next?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start2_1">
		<text>Well, here we are. This is the death of all inattentive and careless - anomalies. Take something and throw it in front of you, so you can make sure everything is clear ahead. According to my detector, there's a "Jellyfish" artifact around here somewhere. Artifacts have both positive and negative properties, and in this case, we're pretty lucky. Here's my old detector, you can use it to detect some other artifacts, but don't forget to return it later, it's pretty expensive. Also take this one, you can take it all at once before you go in there. Oh, I almost forgot. Be careful when you come into contact with those "rocks" with your bare hands. They can hit you so hard that the dental filling will fly off, and you'll ruin your equipment. The artifacts are radioactive, and I don't recommend keeping them in your bare hands for a long time, and your items in the backpack will be irradiated, until you put them in a container, so here we must act quickly and accurately. There's a box nearby, you can put your stuff there temporarily. Come on, I'll cover you from here, don't get in trouble!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start3_0">
		<text>Look, I found it!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start3_1">
		<text>Well, keep it for yourself, it has the ability to absorb different types of radiation, but it won't hurt you right now. I don't advise to shine with these trinkets here, there are a lot of people who want to rob you to the skin, so keep in mind. And do not carry these artifacts with you in your pockets, if you do not want to shine at night like a garland. Listen to my advice and you will make a good stalker. That's it, let's go back to the village, we'll give a hint there.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_0">
		<text>Wow, I can see why everyone's so eager to get in here. It's all clear on the artefacts, what's next?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_1">
		<text>And here's what's going to happen, I'm going to take this stone away from you, come on, come on. I'll save you from trouble, and you'll thank me later. Give me back my detector and knife, because I'm too fond of them, you can keep the trophies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_2">
		<text>Leave me something, I helped you fight back too.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_3">
		<text>Don't make me say it twice. Give me back the knife, the detector and the artifact. Did I mess with you for nothing? Covering for you, setting yourself up. Come on, come on, don't waste time if you want to stay in this village.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_4">
		<text>I can't find where I put your knife.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_5">
		<text>Do not test my patience, return my knife.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_6">
		<text>I can't find where I put the artifact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_7">
		<text>You think I'm stupid? You think I didn't see you try to hide it? Get it over here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_8">
		<text>I think I lost your detector.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_9">
		<text>Nice try, but it's not gonna work, give it back to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_10">
		<text>Here, take your stuff!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fanat_kmb_1_start4_11">
		<text>Very good. Come as soon as you get settled in here, I have one more thing for you. Here's a knife sharpening stone for you, you'll need it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zat_b3_stalker_tech_start_mlr_0">
		<text>Hey, stalker. You need something?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_hello_0">
		<text>A? Is that you...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_heal_0">
		<text>I need medical attention.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_heal_1">
		<text>Well, let me see...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_heal_2">
		<text>Don't make laugh, everything is fine with you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_heal_3">
		<text>[further...]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_heal_4">
		<text>Well, that's it, you can go.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_1_0">
		<text>Hi, is there a special job?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_1_1">
		<text>Of course there is, I saw how many zombies gathered here in a landfill? Very strange, before this was not. In general, now I will give you the coordinates of the largest cluster of these creatures, and you will clean everything up there thoroughly. Well how?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_1_2">
		<text>Come on</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_1_3">
		<text>No, I don't want anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_1_4">
		<text>Hold the coordinates. Be careful there.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_2_0">
		<text>Everything is ready, oh, and there were many of them there ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gar_4_2_zombie_mlr_squad_2_1">
		<text>Oh well done. From Yantar, the creature must be a rod. By the way, did you know that there is a direct road to the "wild territory" from here? If not, give me a PDA - I'll outline how to get there. Well, do not forget the reward.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barmen_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_0">
		<text>Tell me about yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_1">
		<text>Oh, yes I'm here someone like a local bartender or a food manager, as you prefer. We can say that I am one of the few who participated in the liquidation of the accident at the nuclear power plant. I'm not local, but I decided to go to the zone under the contract. There is no experience, ha.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_2">
		<text>And how was it there?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_3">
		<text>Yes, I was still an conscript, I was only lucky to measure the general background with the guys, and to participate in the “sweeps” of radiation. Here about those who heard at the station, yes - they were lucky to be in the ass. What a man there, even the equipment died from the radiation, so you estimate and they threw off this graphite with shovels from the roof. Although radiation is a strange thing, whom it doesn't spare, and Dyatlov survived and went to the bunk.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rogovets_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_0">
		<text>Tell me about yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rogovets_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_1">
		<text>I'm a military medic, contracted to come here and almost immediately I was assigned to the "Farwater Group" after some training. We got stuck in Pripyat once after an operation collapsed, well, whoever was left alive... then an SBU officer helped us, and then they took us away. I can't get one case out of my head: our direct superior sent me and a couple of lads to a kindergarten where, according to preliminary data, there was a device which disturbed radio communication. When we got there, I don't know what came over me, I wasn't myself, I couldn't see where the guys had gone, I couldn't see, I was like a blur in front of my eyes. So right there in the kindergarten I found some goddamn refrigerator and climbed in. Then I heard an explosion right above me and immediately felt better, but the fridge was locked for some reason and I couldn't get out without help. I don't remember if I locked myself in or if a poltergeist was holding the door...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rogovets_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_2">
		<text>And then what, why didn't quit?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rogovets_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_3">
		<text>Yes, I need the money, otherwise why else would I have come here. And the doctors are good, and not so good in the army now. At least they didn't demote me for failing the operation, but they didn't praise me either, unlike the Major, who by the way is also hanging around here somewhere in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rogovets_about_himself_1_6_army_mlr_4">
		<text>All right, good luck with that. Now I'll know and I won't go to that kindergarten again.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="rogovets_heal_1_6_army_mlr_0">
		<text>Buddy, can you patch me a little?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_killer_0">
		<text>Hey, I dug up a recorder somewhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_killer_1">
		<text>Military? Come on. It's a good thing, take the money for it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_freedom_0">
		<text>I found a flight recorder here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_freedom_1">
		<text>So, come on here. Let's see what these bastards are plotting.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_csky_0">
		<text>Now, I found this recorder under the rubble of a helicopter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_csky_1">
		<text>Great find, maybe we can find the cause of these air raids on the marshes.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_haron_0">
		<text>Brother, I dug up an onboard recorder here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_haron_1">
		<text>Give it here, let's see what the military is up to this time.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_owl_0">
		<text>Are you interested in helicopter recorders?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_owl_1">
		<text>Of course, give it here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_army_0">
		<text>I picked up a recorder from a helicopter crash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_reward_army_1">
		<text>Thank you, give it here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night_0">
		<text>Hey, don't you trade info about stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night_1">
		<text>At a flea market, almost everyone is being traded. Six thousand and I will mark you the coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night1_0">
		<text>I need information about stashes, I have money %c[255,238,153,26][6000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night1_1">
		<text>Catch the coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_barman_mil_7_7_0">
		<text>Do you have information on the location of any stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barman_mil_7_7_1">
		<text>Oh, of course! There's been a lot of people here. I don't want to go around the Zone on my own, so I'm selling for six and a half for a tip.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_barman_mil_7_7_1_0">
		<text>I need information about the places of stashes, I have money %c[255,238,153,26][7000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barman_mil_7_7_1_1">
		<text>Here are stash coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat_0">
		<text>Hello, can you find information about the location of some stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat_1">
		<text>You can find everything, and you have the money? Thanks to the information from the PDA shaft, and I don't fucking need those schemes. Eight grand for this one, and no less.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat1_0">
		<text>I need information about the stashes, I have the money. %c[255,238,153,26][8000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat1_1">
		<text>Catch the coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_7_4_bandit_trader_0">
		<text>Howdy, man. You don't mess around with information about different stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_7_4_bandit_trader_1">
		<text>And where did you smell it from? Yeah, well, as far as the pahan goes, it's settling. Anyway, 7K and it's yours.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_7_4_bandit_trader1_0">
		<text>I need information on the locations of the stashes, I have the money... %c[255,238,153,26][7000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_7_4_bandit_trader1_1">
		<text>Here are the coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_barmen_0">
		<text>Hello, barman. Can I get some information on the location of some stash from you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barmen_1">
		<text>Yes, I often have stalkers in the bar as a thank-you or just drunk talk about their schemes, but do not think that it will cost you cheap, even though I do not know what may be there. 7000 and the stash is yours.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="information_about_stash_barmen1_0">
		<text>I need information about the hiding places, I have the money. %c[255,238,153,26][7000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barmen1_1">
		<text>Catch the coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="tech_a18_meet_dialog_0">
		<text>Hey, you're a local supply man, right? Do you provide any services?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tech_a18_meet_dialog_1">
		<text>Oh, what a provider I am now. No, I'd rather need the services. Come back a little later, I can give you a job looking for different ammunition and weapons for our guys.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="tesak_meet_dialog_0">
		<text>Hey, what are the mercenaries doing here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tesak_meet_dialog_1">
		<text>We're stuck, man. You're not going forward for a reason, we can't back down either. Not only are the tracks cut off, but Dushman's also very angry with us, I guess he won't miss an opportunity to get even with us.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tesak_meet_dialog_2">
		<text>What happened?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tesak_meet_dialog_3">
		<text>Performed some order of the customer, but failed. The military liquidated most of ours, the bitches and all the information from the lab near here were raked out. I don't want to talk about it in general. If you're looking for a job, you can find it from me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="grifon_meet_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello, I saw your message. Why are you so kind all of a sudden?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="grifon_meet_dialog_1">
		<text>Why are you doing this out of the blue? Don't abuse our hospitality. We've got business on the beard, that's all. Because of the military who used to hang around here, we lost some important people, and we never managed to find the information we needed and access to some places. If we go back to Dushman, he will tear off our genitals and make us eat them, so we have settled here for now, and I see no point in feuding with loners.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="grifon_meet_dialog_2">
		<text>And what kind of help do you need?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="grifon_meet_dialog_3">
		<text>All kinds of things. We don't have any supplies or equipment here, just what's left of the intermediaries to do the operation. You can also talk to our supply man, he'll share some excess equipment with you for a fee. And by the way, if you decide to get out of this hole, my guys can help. We've already done an extensive study of the local underground network.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_find_inf_inx_8_mlr_1_0">
		<text>Is there any special work?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_find_inf_inx_8_mlr_1_1">
		<text>Got it. We actually came here for the information from the X-8 laboratory, it's in the local KBO, it's enough to go down to the "minus first floor" in the elevator, but we were prevented by the damned military. And now we're in such a deplorable position because of them. We don't care about Dushman, but maybe there's still some paperwork left. That's how we'd have thought about getting out of here by now. I'd go there with the guys, but there's not enough of us left, and we've got to get out of the goddamn zone somehow. \nI suggest you go should go to X-8, what's left of it, and you'll make good money at the same time. Okay with that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_find_inf_inx_8_mlr_1_2">
		<text>I agree.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_find_inf_inx_8_mlr_1_3">
		<text>No.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_find_inf_inx_8_mlr_2_0">
		<text>That's all we got.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_find_inf_inx_8_mlr_2_1">
		<text>Well, I'll tell you straight up, it's not much, but there are interesting things. And it's not hard to find a buyer for that kind of good. Here, take your fee:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_0">
		<text>Greetings brother. Do you know shorter ways to move to our advanced bases?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_1">
		<text>I know and can ask the brothers to show, but not for free of course. Here are our bases: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The vicinity of Jupiter</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_list_0">
		<text>Remind me of our routes and the cost of moving.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_list_1">
		<text>Listen: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat [1000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The vicinity of Jupiter [1000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_0">
		<text>Take me away.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_1">
		<text>Where, brother?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_2">
		<text>On the outskirts of Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_3">
		<text>In the vicinity of Jupiter %c[255,238,153,26][1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_l11pri_mon_haron_4">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_red_forest_mon_0">
		<text>Do you have any information on how to get to our main bases as quickly as possible?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_red_forest_mon_1">
		<text>I can ask the brothers to show, but for the donation. Here are our bases: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat\n%c[255,238,153,26]• The vicinity of Jupiter \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Central Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_red_forest_mon_list_0">
		<text>Remind me of our routes and the cost of donations.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_red_forest_mon_list_1">
		<text>Listen: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat [5000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The vicinity of Jupiter [6000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Central Pripyat [5000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_red_forest_mon_0">
		<text>I'm ready for a sortie.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_red_forest_mon_1">
		<text>Where, brother?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_red_forest_mon_2">
		<text>On the outskirts of Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][5000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_red_forest_mon_3">
		<text>In the vicinity of Jupiter %c[255,238,153,26][6000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_red_forest_mon_4">
		<text>To Central Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][5000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_red_forest_mon_5">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_prikbo_mon_0">
		<text>Do you know how to get to certain places as quickly as possible?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_prikbo_mon_1">
		<text>I can't take it myself, but the brothers will show you where to go. Only not for free. Look here: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The vicinity of Jupiter \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Central Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_prikbo_mon_list_0">
		<text>Please remind once again those places where you can take me and the material reward from me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_prikbo_mon_list_1">
		<text>Listen: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The vicinity of Jupiter [2000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Central Pripyat [1000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_prikbo_mon_mon_0">
		<text>I need to use your ways.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_prikbo_mon_mon_1">
		<text>Ok, choose:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_prikbo_mon_mon_2">
		<text>In the vicinity of Jupiter %c[255,238,153,26][2000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_prikbo_mon_mon_3">
		<text>To Central Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_prikbo_mon_mon_4">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_jupdepo_mon_0">
		<text>Brother, are there any secret paths nearby for faster and safer travel?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_jupdepo_mon_1">
		<text>But what about. I won't take it myself, but you can go with your brothers. Only now you have to donate money for the fraternity. But I think this does not depress you in the least. Here you are on the way: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red forest \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Central Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_jupdepo_mon_list_0">
		<text>Remind me of our routes and the cost of donations.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_jupdepo_mon_list_1">
		<text>Listen: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red forest [6000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat [2000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Central Pripyat [1000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_jupdepo_mon_mon_0">
		<text>Can we move forward?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jupdepo_mon_mon_1">
		<text>Of course, choose where:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jupdepo_mon_mon_2">
		<text>To the Red Forest %c[255,238,153,26][6000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jupdepo_mon_mon_3">
		<text>To the outskirts of Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][2000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jupdepo_mon_mon_4">
		<text>To Central Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jupdepo_mon_mon_5">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="remember_dyx_barter_0">
		<text>Remind me again what you can trade your vodka for?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remember_dyx_barter_1">
		<text>Here, look: \n5 bottles of "Cossacks" = 6 packs 9x18 \n5 bottles of "Cossacks" = 3 packs 5.45x39 \n10 bottles of "Cossacks" = 6 packs 5.45x39 \n10 bottles of "Cossacks" = 5 packs 12x70mm \n10 bottles of "Cossacks" = 2 packs of 7.62x54mm \n15 bottles of "Cossacks" + 7,000 UAH = 5 boxes for PKP \n20 bottles of "Cossacks" = "Beryl" vest.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr1_0">
		<text>Hey, what do you do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr1_1">
		<text>A new client. So, look, I don't care who you are or where you come from, you choose what you want from the list and wait exactly 24 hours until I get the goods. Also, I don't take no for an answer, I'm a serious man, I work without prepayment. Everything will be just in time, you can order no more than one sample.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr4_0">
		<text>How do you collaborate with Monolith and how do you manage to get such unique equipment?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr4_1">
		<text>If I'm not interested in who you are, then you shouldn't, right? Only for your reassurance I will say that I am an intermediary, and not some kind of reckless walker around the Zone, like Nimble when it comes to swag. It's just that you can be very lucky to say that you ended up here and I decided to work with you. And I'm very selective, believe me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_0">
		<text>I'd like to order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_1">
		<text>Choose what interests you:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_2">
		<text>Pistols</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_3">
		<text>"Steppe Eagle" - a more successful modification of the Desert Eagle, with manually adjusted parts. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 8000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_4">
		<text>Ok, expect messages on the PDA. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Order time: 24 hours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_5">
		<text>"Alpine" - a modification of the SIG220 with an increased capacity of the store. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 6500</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_6">
		<text>"Marsh" - a rapid-fire and slaughter barrel, is a modification of the USP pistol. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 7000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_7">
		<text>Shotguns / PP.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_8">
		<text>Look what I have for you, choose:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_9">
		<text>MP-5 "Frezer" - manual work. All TTX weapons are tightened. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 9500</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_10">
		<text>"Carabinier" - an army modification of the SPAS-12 with reduced recoil and automatic fire. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 11000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_11">
		<text>“Protecta” is an exclusive modification of the Striker shotgun. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 17000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_12">
		<text>I did not find what I was looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_13">
		<text>Sniper / Assault Rifles.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_14">
		<text>Look what I have for you, choose:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_15">
		<text>"Storm" - a modification of the OTs-14 "Thunderstorm" from special forces, the party secretly leaked to the masses. Of the advantages it is worth noting the increased capacity of the store \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 19000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_16">
		<text>H&K G36 is a rare thing in the area. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 14000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_17">
		<text>The FN-2000 is a Belgian, a rarity and a pretty good assault rifle. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 17000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_18">
		<text>"Surf" - an exclusive modification of the BCC "Vintorez", also from special specialists. He has a reduced rate of fire, but increased lethal force. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 20000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_19">
		<text>"SVU2-A" - a modification of the SVU with an increased rate of fire, took it from the "Freedom". \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 24000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_20">
		<text>SVD "Lynx" - an army modification, combining accuracy and lethal force. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 18000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_21">
		<text>Gauss gun. Trophy weapons, such in the Zone on the fingers count. Absolute accuracy and damage with an almost complete absence of recoil are included. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 150000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_22">
		<text>Equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_23">
		<text>Look what I have for you, choose:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_24">
		<text>Exoskeleton "Monolith" - the best combination of protective characteristics. Besides, you won't get such a thing anywhere else, unless of course you are a representative of the fraternity. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 100000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_25">
		<text>The exoskeleton of mercenaries is perhaps the most reliable means of protection. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 75000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_26">
		<text>Gangster exoskeleton. Exclusive in its purest form. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 65000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_27">
		<text>The Monolith jumpsuit with a closed breathing system, as in the case of an exoskeleton, is unlikely to be seen anywhere else. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 70000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_28">
		<text>Mercenaries bodysuit with a closed breathing system. Excellent protection against anomalies, a real rarity for the layman. \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Price: 50000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr2_29">
		<text>Nothing, I already changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_0">
		<text>I'm ordering.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_1">
		<text>Is money with you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_2">
		<text>Yes, come on my "Steppe Eagle".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_3">
		<text>Come again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_4">
		<text>Yes, come on my SIG-220 Alpine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_5">
		<text>Yes, come on my USP "March."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_6">
		<text>Yes, come on my MP-5 "Frezer".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_7">
		<text>Yes, come on my pump action Carabiner.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_8">
		<text>Yes, come on my Protecta shotgun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_9">
		<text>es, come on my OTs-14 "Storm".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_10">
		<text>Yes, come on my H&K G36.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_11">
		<text>Yes, come on my FN-2000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_12">
		<text>Yes, give me my BCC Surf.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_13">
		<text>Yes, give me my "SVU2-A."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_14">
		<text>Yes, give me my SVD "Lynx".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_15">
		<text>Yes, give me my "Monolith" exoskeleton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_16">
		<text>Yes, give me my exoskeleton of "mercenaries."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_17">
		<text>Yes, give me my bandit exoskeleton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_18">
		<text>Yes, give me my "Monolith" bodysuit with a closed system.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_19">
		<text>Yes, give me my bodysuit with a closed system.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_20">
		<text>Yes, give me my "Gauss" here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_special_trader_mlr3_21">
		<text>I forgot.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_jup_depo_start_0">
		<text>Hello, brother. I am engaged in the technical support of our brothers in the area.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_start_0">
		<text>Greetings. I fulfill His will, helping our fellow with equipment.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trucks_cemetery_bandit_mechanic_start_0">
		<text>Hey, brother. Patching up the drop/patching up the barrel is all for me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty_0">
		<text>They say you have interesting goods in exchange for patches?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty_1">
		<text>Of course! Look, dear, what I have here: \n210 rounds of 5.56 caliber = 20 patches \n50 rounds of 7.62 = 15 patches \n20 grenade launchers m209 = 50 patches \n"Freedom" scientific suit = 50 patches \n"Freedom" Exoskeleton = 65 patches \nUnique SVD = 100 patches</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_0">
		<text>I have patches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_1">
		<text>Make your choice: \n210 rounds of calibre 5.56 = 20 patches \n50 rounds 7.62 = 15 patches \n20 underbarrel grenades m209 = 50 patches \n"Freedom" Scientifim outfit = 50 patches. \n"Freedom" Exoskeleton = 65 patches \nUnique SVD = 100 stripes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_2">
		<text>210 rounds of 5.56 calibre</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_3">
		<text>50 rounds 7.62x54</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_4">
		<text>20 M209 underbarrel grenades</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_5">
		<text>Give me that scientific suit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_6">
		<text>Give me that exoskeleton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_7">
		<text>Give me SVD.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ashot_price_for_pathes_duty1_8">
		<text>I'm not taking anything, I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barter_povar_army_0">
		<text>I brought vodka.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_1">
		<text>Great, what you want?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_2">
		<text>6 packs 9x18mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_3">
		<text>3 packs 5.45x39mm FMJ</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_4">
		<text>1 pack 5.45x39mm AP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_5">
		<text>2 packs of 12x70 buckshot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_6">
		<text>2 packs of 7.62x39mm FMJ</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_6_1">
		<text>1 pack of 7.62x39mm AP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_7">
		<text>1 box for PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_8">
		<text>Give me "Beryl"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_9">
		<text>I changed my mind somehow.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_10">
		<text>The "package" has been delivered. There's a stash here at the base, behind the containers and boxes behind me, go get it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_povar_army_0">
		<text>Hey, did you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_1">
		<text>Local chef, kind of. Can't even make eggs, though, what can I do? It's an army. An army in the zone. I'm not much of a fighter, so they put me up. It's not really about that, though... by the way, I'm Spirit. Well, I've got a lot of alcohol on my plate, and the depressing guy's a bitch. It's also a place... Well, the scientists' camp is the main camp, and sometimes a check-up comes in here. So we've got a tight vodka supply, last time I saw you, the cattle were drained.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_2">
		<text>[next...]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_3">
		<text>All right, dude. I know it's tight with ammo here, Sakharov doesn't sell that! I can fit it, but it's Sovdepov's. Sorry. What a reservation I got to make, it's all mine. How's that? Anyway, it's my price:
		\nFor 5 bottle - 5 packs of 9x18 mm
		\nFor 5 bottle - 3 packs of 5.45x39 mm
		\nFor 5 bottle - 1 pack of 5.45x39 mm AP
		\nFor 5 bottle - 2 packs of 7.62x39 mm
		\nFor 5 bottle - 1 pack of 7.62x39 mm AP
		\nFor 5 bottle - 2 packs of 12x70 mm buck
		\nFor 5 bottle - 1 ribbon for PKM/PKP
		\nFor 15 bubbles the whole "Beryl"
		\nDon't think about it, I'm not that finished, the lion's share of the guys is gone. That's why they leave their gear in my stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_4">
		<text>Okay, I'll take that into account. Okay, thank you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_0">
		<text>What is this place?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_1">
		<text>This, guy, is flea market. And here we are, respectively, flea marketers. We trade little by little what God sent ... True, I will tell you the goods from me and really frank junk. But at least somehow floundering ... How did you come to trade, or so?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_2">
		<text>Are you the only merchant here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_3">
		<text>No, what are you! Here and other guys bargain, we just have a rule: large deals - only after sunset. In the afternoon, yes, I trade alone: I have both inexpensive goods and a little of it. But at night here the real life begins, because the goods are already going completely different.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_0">
		<text>Hey, who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_1">
		<text>Can't you tell by me? I'm a military man, Peregrine Falcon is my call sign. I'm helping our guys with equipment here. A part-time tech. It's broken, so bring it to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_2">
		<text>And do you need tools or flash drives?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_3">
		<text>No, come on! I've been provided with something: an electronic database in the bunker, and the best tools, and my education is not chicken. The equipment here is not simple, so it requires high-quality technical intervention... The old receiver has been repaired, but it's a bit of a mess. For about two years now, our guys have been lying in warehouses, and he's broadcasting their voices, yes... And you wanted to fix what? You know, we don't trust anybody here, first show yourself, build a reputation, then come over.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_4">
		<text>Well, that's the zone, it can do anything ? Anyway, I get it, good luck here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_talking_0">
		<text>Hey, who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_talking_1">
		<text>I'm a military nurse, at least I used to be. They call me Aspirin, I can fix it quickly, but about the serious injuries... ...it's either a helicopter or the Zone will save you. But we don't agree on helicopters very often.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_talking_2">
		<text>Do you sell drugs?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_talking_3">
		<text>Quiet! There you see, the general is standing right there. We've got some so dodgy that they're selling the group's property, but I'm not one of them. But I'll help you as much as I can. Okay, I have to go to work...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_talking_4">
		<text>Go ahead.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_dialog_0">
		<text>Heal me a little.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bar_dolg_medic_hello_0">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="brain_on_staff_1_0">
		<text>Professor, is there anything you're interested in that might be stronger than the rest?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_1_1">
		<text>Yes, there is a deal. I need fresh samples of the controller's brain for a more in-depth study of the psi phenomenon. Anyway, look what I have to offer for that: \n10 scientific kits \n10 army medical kits \nApplication module \n3 anabiotics.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="brain_on_staff_0">
		<text>Here's controller brain, Professor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_1">
		<text>Okay... I can offer you 3 scientific medkits for that, either the 4 army medkits, Artefact Application Container or 2 anabiotics. Select your choice:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_2">
		<text>I will take 3 scientific medkits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_3">
		<text>I will take 4 army medkits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_4">
		<text>Better give me Artefact Application Container, this is what I need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_5">
		<text>Anabiotics would be very useful to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_on_staff_6">
		<text>Oh, I probably changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="first_meet_to_barman_mil_7_7_0">
		<text>Oh, hi. I'm looking you have a canteen or ... bar?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="first_meet_to_barman_mil_7_7_1">
		<text>Well, the canteen in the Zone have only Duty, thruts to say nobody's seen it. Greetings here, man - my name is Cooker, I'm in charge of the local cooks, after the Cook in the minefield, hehehe.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="talk_to_barman_mil_7_7_about_lottery_0">
		<text>Do you have anything interesting here in the bar?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_barman_mil_7_7_about_lottery_1">
		<text>Besides Russian roulette? I collect stripes. You need to bring as many rare stripes as possible and I'll give you something for it. If you bring 10, then of course I won't give much. But if a half an hour, wow! But by the way, there is more demand for scientists and a monolith. "Svobodovskie" by the way are not quoted, I have them so full.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_barman_mil_7_7_about_lottery_2">
		<text>And what do you do with them all?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_barman_mil_7_7_about_lottery_3">
		<text>I embroider a plaid from them! Well, of course you have questions, man.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_0">
		<text>I have patches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_1">
		<text>Great, which ones?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_2">
		<text>"Clear Sky", 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_3">
		<text>"Mercenaries", 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_4">
		<text>"Stalkers", 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_5">
		<text>"Scientists", 10 pieces in total.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_6">
		<text>"Bandits", 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_7">
		<text>"Duty", 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_8">
		<text>"Monolith", 10 pieces in total.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_9">
		<text>"Army", 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_10">
		<text>"Clear Sky", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_11">
		<text>"Mercenaries", 50 pieces</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_12">
		<text>"Stalkers", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_13">
		<text>"Scientists", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_14">
		<text>"Bandits", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_15">
		<text>"Duty", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_16">
		<text>"Monolith", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_17">
		<text>"Army", 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_18">
		<text>I may have changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_19">
		<text>Here, hold the bottle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_20">
		<text>Oh, good wine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_21">
		<text>Excellent liqueur.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_22">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_23">
		<text>Take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_24">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_25">
		<text>Here's the good stuff, it'll come in handy in combat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_26">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_27">
		<text>Full day meals.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_28">
		<text>From our count.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_29">
		<text>Would get drunk now...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_30">
		<text>Useful thing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_31">
		<text>For not loosing your brains somewhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_32">
		<text>Better leave it to the extreme.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_33">
		<text>If suddenly it's completely shitty in battle or seriously wounded - an irreplaceable thing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_34">
		<text>A good thing, if you throw in, then at least you will climb a vertical mountain.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_35">
		<text>Sadly, you don't get anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_36">
		<text>You're out of luck this time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_37">
		<text>Nothing this time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_38">
		<text>Excellent equipment for a great shooter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_barman_mil_7_7_mlr_39">
		<text>Perfect choice for long hauls.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_0">
		<text>Hey, man, what are you doing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_1">
		<text>Nothing, and you wanted something? My name is Leshim, by the way. We'll know each other. I'm a local guide and a scout.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_2">
		<text>And how do you like local intelligence, probably been to a lot of places?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_3">
		<text>Yeah, I've even been to the anomaly. When I was a hired gun, me and my squad got into a space bubble, so it's a long story.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_4">
		<text>Okay, I'm not gonna fill up on listeners. Good luck with that.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_list_0">
		<text>Where are you going, can I ask?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_list_1">
		<text>To the: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts [Rookie Village, 4500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Yantar [5000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_0">
		<text>Take me somewhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_1">
		<text>Choose:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_2">
		<text>Have you forgotten the money?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_3">
		<text>Here you are:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_4">
		<text>To the Outskirts %c[255,238,153,26][Rookie Village, 4500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_5">
		<text>Have you forgotten the money?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_6">
		<text>Here you go:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_7">
		<text>To Yantar %c[255,238,153,26][5000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_8">
		<text>Have you forgotten the money?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_9">
		<text>Here you are:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_10">
		<text>Forgot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_11">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_12">
		<text>Okay</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_0">
		<text>Hello, commander! I really, really need to fly somewhere, is this really possible to organize?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_1">
		<text>Really, but we won't just transfer tons of fuel to you. But as soon as we find out that you are an experienced soldier, you are always welcome. For the future: we fly to Agroprom, Amber and to the Dark Scape.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_list_0">
		<text>May I ask again, where do you fly?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_list_1">
		<text>To: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Agroprom [5000, military base] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Dark Scape [Fuel Station, 3000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Yantar [Scientific base, 10000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_vert_0">
		<text>I need a helicopter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_vert_1">
		<text>Where to?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_vert_2">
		<text>To Agroprom %c[255,238,153,26][military base, 5000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_vert_3">
		<text>To Dark Scape %c[255,238,153,26][Fuel Station, 3000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_vert_4">
		<text>To Yantar %c[255,238,153,26][Scientific base, 10000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_esc_mlr_military_vert_5">
		<text>I changed my mind, wait a moment.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_give">
		<text>Hey, can't you do anything with the flights? Well, in short, I have to go somewhere in case there's a flight on the way.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_give_0">
		<text>I can, but as long as you're not here to call you anything, don't even dream of it. That's how you become an experienced soldier, they'll talk about you, get lost. For the future, we only fly to Outskirts and Yantar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_list_0">
		<text>Can I ask you again where you are flying to?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_list_1">
		<text>Only on: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts [Southern checkpoint, 5000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Yantar [Scientific base, 7000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_vert_0">
		<text>I want to use the services of a pilot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_vert_1">
		<text>Now I'll check the schedule. Where to?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_vert_2">
		<text>To Outskirts %c[255,238,153,26][Southern checkpoint, 5000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_vert_3">
		<text>To Yantar %c[255,238,153,26][Scientific base, 7000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="guid_agr_mlr_military_vert_4">
		<text>Nowhere.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_marsh_csky_0">
		<text>Hi, what are you standing here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_marsh_csky_1">
		<text>Yes, there is no time to sit, I must be constantly in sight, since I am a local conductor. You don't look at my equipment, it's easier for me to move around like that. I can take you somewhere too, namely: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Observation post] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Water pumping] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Old Church] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Mechanical yard] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Cordon [Beginner Village] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Agroprom \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Bar</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_marsh_csky_list_0">
		<text>Can I clarify your routes again?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_marsh_csky_list_1">
		<text>To: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Observation post, 300] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Water pumping, 500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Old Church, 500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [Mechanical yard, 800] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts [Rookie Village, 1500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Agroprom [2000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Bar [4000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_0">
		<text>I want to use your services.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_1">
		<text>Ok where?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_2">
		<text>Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][Observation post, 300]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_3">
		<text>Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][Swamp Doctor's Shelter, 1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_4">
		<text>Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][Water pump, 500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_5">
		<text>Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][Old church, 500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_6">
		<text>Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][Mechanical Yard, 800]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_7">
		<text>To Outskirts %c[255,238,153,26][Rookie Village, 1500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_8">
		<text>To Agroprom %c[255,238,153,26][2000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_9">
		<text>To the bar %c[255,238,153,26][4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_marsh_csky_10">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_dv_bandit_0">
		<text>Whoa and who's this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_dv_bandit_1">
		<text>What the fuck are you looking at? I've been on the road all my life, and I'm standing here, too. I can take you someplace, too. Here:
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Garbage [hangar, 1500]
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Trucks cemetery [bandit parking, 1500]
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Cordon [factory, 4000]
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Army Warehouses [Freedom base, 4000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_list_0">
		<text>Remind me where we go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_list_1">
		<text>Here:
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Garbage [hangar, 1500]
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Trucks cemetery [bandit parking, 1500]
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Cordon [factory, 4000]
		\n%c[255,238,153,26]• Army Warehouses [Freedom base, 4000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_0">
		<text>All right, let's go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_1">
		<text>Where are we going?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_2">
		<text>To the Trucks cemetery. %c[255,238,153,26][1500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_3">
		<text>Cordon %c[255,238,153,26][factory, 4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_4">
		<text>Garbage %c[255,238,153,26][hangar, 1500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_5">
		<text>Army Warehouses %c[255,238,153,26][hangar, 4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_dv_bandit_6">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_pri_stalker_list_0">
		<text>Can I check your routes one more time?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_pri_stalker_list_1">
		<text>To: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• NPP [12000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Pripyat [3000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Suburbs of Jupiter ["Yanov"], 4000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Radar [8000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Jupiter Underground [1000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Zaton [through Garik, 4000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_0">
		<text>I want to use your services.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_1">
		<text>All right, where to?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_2">
		<text>To the Chernobyl NPP %c[255,238,153,26][12000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_3">
		<text>In the Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][3000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_4">
		<text>To the radar %c[255,238,153,26][8000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_5">
		<text>In the vicinity of Jupiter %c[255,238,153,26][4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_6">
		<text>To the Jupiter Underground %c[255,238,153,26][1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_7">
		<text>To Zaton %c[255,238,153,26][4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_pri_stalker_8">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_jup_0">
		<text>Hey, who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_jup_1">
		<text>Hey, bro. My name is Garik, I drive back and forth, mostly in the middle of the Zone. I'm gonna check in: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Bar \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Pripyat \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red Forest [Forester's home] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Zaton [Skadovsk] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Jupiter Underground</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_jup_list_0">
		<text>Can I clarify your routes again?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_jup_list_1">
		<text>To: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Bar [6000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Pripyat [3000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Outskirts of Pripyat [Laundry, 4000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Red Forest [Forester's home, 2500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Zaton [Skadovsk, 2000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Jupiter Underground [1500]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_0">
		<text>I want to use your services.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_1">
		<text>Great, where?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_2">
		<text>To the bar %c[255,238,153,26][6000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_3">
		<text>In Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][3000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_4">
		<text>On the outskirts of Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_5">
		<text>To the Red Forest %c[255,238,153,26][2500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_6">
		<text>To Zaton %c[255,238,153,26][2000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_jup_7">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_0">
		<text>Hey, what about you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_1">
		<text>Conductor Pilot at your service. There aren't a lot of places I can spend here, but it's sure to be a lot faster and safer.  I'll show you to: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Pripyat [through Garik] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The outskirts of Pripyat [through Garik] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Neighborhood of Jupiter ["Yanov" station]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_list_0">
		<text>Can I clarify your routes again?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_list_1">
		<text>To: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Pripyat [through Garik, 4000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• The outskirts of Pripyat [through Garik, 5000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Neighborhood of Jupiter ["Yanov" station, 2000]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_0">
		<text>I want to use your services.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_1">
		<text>Great, where?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_2">
		<text>To Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][4000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_3">
		<text>To the outskirts of Pripyat %c[255,238,153,26][5000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_4">
		<text>In the vicinity of Jupiter %c[255,238,153,26][2000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_5">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_bar_0">
		<text>Hi, what are you doing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_bar_1">
		<text>I'm a guide, here and there for a modest fee, they're calling me “Navigator”. Mostly greens, of course, use services, but experienced stalkers also do not neglect it. The agreement is this: you pay, I leave you at the designated area and come back. I will lead on: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Yantar \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Army Warehouses \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Garbage</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="meet_guid_bar_list_0">
		<text>Can I clarify your routes again?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_bar_list_1">
		<text>To: \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Yantar [3500] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Swamps [6000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Army Warehouses [1000] \n%c[255,238,153,26]• Garbage [700]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_0">
		<text>I want to use your services.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_2">
		<text>Great, where?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_3">
		<text>To Garbage %c[255,238,153,26][700]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_4">
		<text>To Army Warehouses %c[255,238,153,26][1000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_5">
		<text>To Yantar %c[255,238,153,26][3500]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_6">
		<text>To the Swamps %c[255,238,153,26][6000]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_bar_7">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_0">
		<text>Hi, why are you dressed up like a bandit?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_1">
		<text>Oh you. Hunter I, the truth you can understand - there are few of us left. I keep a small bar here, the places are safe and generally not bad, and if you have questions, ask. By the way, they call me a Butcher.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_2">
		<text>Who are the hunters in the "Zone"?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_3">
		<text>Well, we are doing pretty specific leisure here. We do not collect artifacts, do not adhere to any general views on the zone and do not try to unravel its secrets. We simply hunt mutants, and not because they, in our opinion, pose any threat, as it seems to “Duty,” but because we can and want to. Many of us were former hunters, both amateurs and professionals on the mainland, though many perished. \nAbout the cloak, by the way, did you notice, so it's much more convenient to hunt in them, and we try not to enter into armed conflicts, well, plus this is like a secret uniform or something.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_4">
		<text>And what can you offer?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_5">
		<text>Yes, what guys bring trophies, so I bargain. Well, and on the little things to others, provisions there for example, medicines and equipment. I can offer you a job hunting for all sorts of mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_6">
		<text>Got it, somehow I'll definitely take the task from you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_baraholka_hunter_trader_0">
		<text>Why is this place called "Flea market"?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_baraholka_hunter_trader_1">
		<text>Ooooh, but you didn't find such places on the mainland? Let's just say this place is something like a market, but an unusual market. In fact, there are large hucksters, like your Sidorovich is not there, the guys are trading who is rich than what and who pulled out what, but they are trading! At night, here you can catch some nishtyaki, by the way. And the flea market has a long history within this place. Previously, the guys gathered right in the ruins of the building nearby, though until the loners drove them away. These freaks did not like the fact that they traded artifacts, but not anyhow, but at cost! Recently, they decided to revive the past, the Reds still dug in at their bar, and the bandits did not know about this place. The benefit of the building is inconspicuous and quite comfortable, I don't even know where that steel door leads. Well, I later nailed to them, as I noticeably began to take combat skills ...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_0">
		<text>Tell me about some mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_1">
		<text>Well, then there are such cute rodents, they are popularly called "tushkanos." You saw them for sure. It does not seem to look dangerous, but in a flock they can easily bite even an experienced stalker, even a whole group. Here was such a case when a special unit of "Duty" went to clean the den of bloodsuckers. Well, count these idiots in a camp somewhere in the middle of the complex at the Agroprom, put down one sentry somewhere, and the other jerked off, well, there literally for 10 minutes no one guarded the sleeping people. Morning already means - it's time for the guys to wake up, but there is nobody. Well, something was wrong, they thought, they went into the room, and there the blood was covered - the sea and the throats of everyone were "bitten". Characteristic traces of jerboas appear, but they themselves have already fallen. The dog knows why they didn't stay for a meal, but to see smart nits. Well, the sentries still decided to go into the den themselves, and write off the deaths of their comrades as a bloodsucker. So they disappeared, and their handheld computer picked up a stalker, but with a new story came to the neighing bar. So that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_2">
		<text>Well, every rookie encounters dogs at the cordon, not to mention on the mainland. They aren't much different from their, let's say, "prototypes". Blinded only, but it's not reassuring, because the other senses have become more sharp. Especially their sense of smell. They attack such inexperienced novices at once, as well as more experienced stalkers, in turn, with their agility and suddenness.\n So listen to the story. Someone in the bar was trying to steal some sausage at night. They got the whole place on edge, the guards got beaten up, whatever the hell they were doing. They even invited the Duty men to guard, and see who it is stealing, well, they sure as hell saw a dog that ran through a hole in the fence, and shot it. In the morning, the depressed stalker comes to the bar, asks about the dog, and the bartender immediately figured it out and told him to go to the Duty. That's how it was, the dude came from mainland with this dog through the cordon, it's his pet. Well, they went through a lot together, and he's also an orphan, and then this happened. Since then, who is so clever to cross the cordon with his animals, go back, or let his "friend" for dinner to brothers-stalker. Otherwise there is nothing to frighten already nervous people. By the way, the sausage was stolen by a local drunk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_3">
		<text>There are dogs, but there are pseudo-dogs. Why pseudo? Yes, they are only partially similar to dogs, well, because of the ability of some to affect the human brain in the most negative way, causing him to hallucinate. The dog knows whether they came from ordinary dogs, from wolves, or is this some kind of secret experiment, at least the experiments of scientists did not illuminate anything in this area. These creatures jump, be healthy, can bite a person's throat in flight, and these phantoms of them. If you are already lucky enough to run into such a psi-mongrel, then you should carefully monitor it and its copies, take the most careful one, which is not in a hurry to enter the battle and hit it. This will be the original, because these creatures are very intelligent, there are even legends that they can be tamed. The Dog of the Swamp Doctor, as an example to you, you can ask about him in the Swamps.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_4">
		<text>Let's talk about snorts. The most common theory is that these are former military men who guarded ChEZ even before the second explosion, and so "digested" their brains to a mushy state. Something similar to zombies, only these and animals have something, primitive such. Crawl on all fours, very flexible creatures that can jump up and hook for several meters, and even worse, cling to a stalker on the fly and gobble up. Another theory says that some gas is tested, which explains the gas masks put on them. The blow came out, who on the earth had evaporated so directly from his post, but someone had a hard time underground, and this gas escaped because of a failure in some secret complex. And someone generally believes that they simply like to put these gas masks on their faces in the face, because they feel more like people, well, they have this type of fetish.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_5">
		<text>About zombies I can. Well, here it is a fairly common phenomenon, although unlike a cheap American kintz, many of these “dummies” retained some human habits and know how to use weapons, even kept their speech. True, their phrases are in most cases incoherent. Sakharov will tell you more about their passage, he has long been studying the phenomenon of psi radiation. For the most part, they are led by controllers and used by them for various purposes, though he rarely eats his "boobs" as food. There is also a more typical subspecies of these creatures, which is popularly called “civilian” because they cannot use weapons, though it's more difficult to kill such ones, they need to damage the ligaments while ordinary zombies can even cry out pain. \ nIt is very likely that some types of civilian zombies come from secret laboratories, this can easily be determined by the remains of clothes. Apparently, this is a uniform of experimental subjects and this theory is confirmed by the information that Tagged obtained in his wanderings through underground complexes, and later other stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_6">
		<text>And let me tell you about bloodsuckers. Creepy creatures with tentacles at the mouth, humanoid type. Presumably a mutation of a person, well, that's how I am - I misinterpreted scientists. In fact, you can't make out any nicerta, and despite the jokes around the campfire, they are asexual and have no genitals. How they reproduce is also unknown, for it is hardly possible to leave such a “footprint” in a person in a couple of hours or days. Of course, it's better to shoot these creatures in the most toothy mouth, because if you cling to it, it will suck out so much blood that you lose consciousness in an instant. Complicated by the fact that they have an excellent disguise, somehow becoming invisible, however, experiments conducted by scientists did not reveal anything, except that their tentacles secrete special glands that prevent blood coagulation. Such a creature as soon as you notice will be rushing around you, winding circles until you get tired or waste your ammunition. Beginners are found with empty shops and characteristic injuries. You better find a place higher or cling to some object so that you do not sneak up behind and look at both, because suddenly this bastard appears in front of you, but squeeze your weapon and shoot harder. The best tactic if he found you alone. Running away from them is problematic.And let me tell you about bloodsuckers. Creepy creatures with tentacles at the mouth, humanoid type. Presumably a mutation of a person, well, that's how I am - I misinterpreted scientists. In fact, you can't make out any nicerta, and despite the jokes around the campfire, they are asexual and have no genitals. How they reproduce is also unknown, for it is hardly possible to leave such a “footprint” in a person in a couple of hours or days. Of course, it's better to shoot these creatures in the most toothy mouth, because if you cling to it, it will suck out so much blood that you lose consciousness in an instant. Complicated by the fact that they have an excellent disguise, somehow becoming invisible, however, experiments conducted by scientists did not reveal anything, except that their tentacles secrete special glands that prevent blood coagulation. Such a creature as soon as you notice will be rushing around you, winding circles until you get tired or waste your ammunition. Beginners are found with empty shops and characteristic injuries. You better find a place higher or cling to some object so that you do not sneak up behind and look at both, because suddenly this bastard appears in front of you, but squeeze your weapon and shoot harder. The best tactic if he found you alone. Running away from them is problematic.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_7">
		<text>Burers. There are such creatures that are legendary even sooner, the existence of which is much better for many not to know, otherwise you can run into fear. The best advice I can give is not to hang around dungeons and all sorts of raw empty complexes, including laboratories, because these creatures love such places. But recently they have been noticed everywhere and this is primarily due to the actions of the Tagged, who turned off the burner. Chimeras, for example, also lived only close to the center of the zone, but then they suddenly migrated sharply and increased their population. Apparently, someone who runs all this in the center of the zone has influence over these creatures and used them as a kind of Cerberus on the last approaches to his "citadel". If you've got into trouble and couldn't escape, I advise you to take care of your head, since they have relatively powerful telekinesis, they can also send a directed impulse and knock you down, they can take your weapons away or exhaust you, influencing gravity in some way . They look like fat and nasty dwarfs who like to wear huge boots that make characteristic sounds and black cloaks, oddly enough, stitched to them almost in size. I think that they, too, are a consequence of experiments in secret laboratories. \nThere are also different subspecies of these creatures. For example, fiery or electric, like poltergeists. In general, some agree that poltergeist is an evolutionary step of the burer. However, if an electric poltergeist affects you only by telekinesis, then an appropriate type of burer can easily throw ball lightning at you or an entire electra, the size of a substation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_8">
		<text>But the jokes are really bad with the controllers, these creatures have a stable psi-background and can manipulate the consciousness of any person. Without appropriate protection, it is strictly forbidden to climb them, and indeed it is better to bypass such places. Most likely they will simply burn your brains out without even steaming over zombies in order to immediately prepare juicy chops from you. There are legends that they even know how to talk, but I believe that this is just nothing more than legends. But their mental abilities do not have to be challenged. Sometimes they can skillfully set up ambushes, and by the way, they often go alone, hungry for food to see or philosophize in their crazy minds there. \nI had to deal with this myself. Stalker came to us once and said that they say so and so, on Rostock in one of the complexes the creature somehow strange settled. He wanted to speak closer and closer, but his head started to hurt wildly so that the weapon almost fell out of his hands, so he spat on this matter, writing everything off to some area with radiation. Well, we went there, so we go in and my head too has begun to crack! Well, we've prepared it yet, we have drunk special tablets. I look, and there a figure in the darkness of a man sits, let's shoot me there, and she disappeared. And then once this bastard turned out to be behind my back, so I shot. I only heard from the edge of my ear a far, far somewhere painfully familiar voice and was dumbfounded. Vasyuk shot his friend. Then we still got rid of this creature, but with pleasure I had already tied up and opened a bar here. I wasn't killed by a miracle by the way, I was lucky that Ryzhiy had a strong mind on this matter, well, he dumped him to the North for such an occasion.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_9">
		<text>Have you seen cats? Oh, Christmas trees. That only a zone with domestic animals does not. They had the whole thyroid swollen from radiation and left these vile tumors, I don't know why cats ... Well, these creatures are shorter than the steel, their claws are sharper and they run like mad - this isn't for you to remove a house bastard from a tree, and those must be chased, fitting effort. Cats, these creatures are free and you can meet them anywhere, so look at the surroundings more often, or else he will come running, grab your careless one in the ass and grab a piece.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_10">
		<text>Many here do not believe in paranormalism, and indeed everyone has a different faith here. Some have their own strengths, some have all kinds of Masters there, and some have alien intervention. But certainly not in God. However, there is still such a monster called "poltergeist", because how else to call translucent flying garbage that throws objects at you? True, this mutant does not have anything similar to religious themes on the topic of restless souls. He is killed in a completely ordinary way, he doesn't react to salt (we already had one that we checked) and looks like a flying electric, or less often a fire essence. Electric, like a burer, is showering you with all kinds of objects, but the fiery one is already capable of somehow creating jets of fire right in front of you, similar in effect and parameters to frying. Shoot directly at the essence - you will not miss, but it is very difficult to kill him because of his speed and maneuverability. \ nThere have been times that stalkers of a black or smoky poltergeist have seen. Reliably nothing is known about its properties, but this is a rather rare instance, and in many ways probably because meeting with such means death in the vast majority of cases, and killing this is even more difficult, because the smoke is much less localized and its core can be tracked very very difficult.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_11">
		<text>There are also creatures about whom many tales of bonfire are stacked. And these are kinks. Creatures of a humanoid type with a hypertrophied arm and neck, with their own hand they can easily break your chest, while the “usual” one does not show abnormal properties. There were many stories that kinks often like to make contact with stalkers and ask for all kinds of garbage from a tin can to imported toothpaste. If you are not lucky and you did not have the necessary things, then be prepared for battle or death. Often they die, because the kinks come into contact more often in a situation favorable to them, for example, if you are a loner and he already holds you with his bucket-shaped hand behind. If you have the desired item, then it's better not to rock the boat and give him what he asks for, and then go in peace for all four, he will not touch you. Well these are stories. Some freaks even leave provisions in places where they last saw a kink, in vain translating usable products.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_12">
		<text>Here is another psvedogiant. Usually, his growth does not exceed human, but his powerful paws can cause a local earthquake, which is why the people called him that. Until recently, again, nothing was known about him, and most likely we are again facing a laboratory geek. Thanks to those assholes who like to rummage around underground complexes and do not close the door behind them. In the North, too, there was a hero, either a military man, or some SBUshnik who did not close the steel door under a local substation. How is it ... "Iron Forest", sort of. Since then, these giants have been observed even in the vicinity of the Jupiter plant. In appearance, it can be determined that “this” was once a man because of the legs hanging down behind the creature's skin and some other features. It's terrible, but do not be frightened of it, since it will most likely just knock you down and crush you. And do not take his clumsy appearance into account, he never falls and does not go astray. Before going to the area where for the last time such a creature was seen, it is best to grab a pair of grenade launchers and a machine gun, since the skin and bones of this mutant show excellent resistance to small arms, and the creature itself is very tenacious.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_13">
		<text>The chimera can rightfully be called the top of the food chain of the zone. Why? This is a very smart creature, mostly a night predator that can fly at you from a distance of several tens of meters. The four-legged mutant has two heads, for which he received his nickname. Also very strong and sharp claws, capable of breaking even the skin of a pseudo-giant. They emit a characteristic roar in a jump, they also resemble a person in some way, they met such zones mainly in the North in open places, in the presence of any objects. As the local hunter, St. John's wort, told, they have their own sphere of influence, where they rest, and later they hunt at night. \nThere is also its subspecies, namely the black chimera. Such darkness cannot be discerned at all and this makes it much more dangerous for relatives (ordinary people have almost human skin color), they also say that it is stronger and more enduring. It's impossible to run away from the chimera, it's better to find some narrow room that will reduce its ability to maneuver or try to jump to the side while it flies towards you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_14">
		<text>Boars and flesh. \nThe flesh is a sample of the eerily mutated pig (as scientists have shown), rather slow and weak, only a complete moron can get under its "wedge-shaped" paws, which she will certainly break through almost any vest. \nBoars are not much different from their congeners outside the zone, except bigger and more dangerous. And the hooves are much stronger and can cut through any fabric without any problem, just like human flesh. All you have to do is jump aside when that carcass comes at you about a couple of meters away from hitting its fangs. Often the meat of both boars and flesh is eaten, if the possibility of radiation poisoning is minimized.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_monsters_trader_hangar_15">
		<text>Dwarves. \nThank you for helping me gather information about them, look what I sketched: \nThey live mostly in underground complexes that have been used in one way or another for human experimentation. They appear to be the result of such experiments. They have supernatural power, good speed and are most often attacked by a group. So far, only one subspecies of dwarf has been discovered - smoked. Dirty, burned out of radiation mutants with their characteristic radiation, it is better not to let them near you without a "Twisted" or "Bubble" in the pocket.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="request_to_no_trade_dialog_0">
		<text>Is there somewhere you can buy equipment wholesale?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="request_to_no_trade_dialog_1">
		<text>Of course you can, but now no one will have business with you and sell anything at cost. If you become more experienced, people will be more confident in you and then you can look at the wholesale dealers to buy things.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="request_to_no_trade_dialog_monolith_0">
		<text>My brother, can I get my gear wholesale?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="request_to_no_trade_dialog_monolith_1">
		<text>Of course you can, but not right away. Get more experience, and then I'll do business with you, or we'll have every bullet counted.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_0">
		<text>I'd like to buy some equipment in bulk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_1">
		<text>What are you interested in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_2">
		<text>Medicines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_3">
		<text>Provisions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_4">
		<text>Ammunition.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_5">
		<text>Choose:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="low_level_of_buy_equpments_6">
		<text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="in_freedom_0">
		<text>Tell me about "Freedom".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="in_freedom_1">
		<text>Well, we are actually one of the strongest groups in the Zone, heh. We are holding back the barrier, we are trying to keep the bastards from the "Duty" here, because our goals are essentially very different. We want to coexist with the Zone in the best sense of the word and believes that it is a gift to humanity. You ask how? Yes you look around! All this is like in a fairy tale. Anomalies that famously violate the laws of physics, creatures with amazing "properties", which I think should not be destroyed. Perhaps you can somehow coexist with them, or at least borrow something from them. However, we do not recognize the “official” approach to the Zone. Scientists may be engaged in a noble cause, but you know that all these gifts will be deposited with some oligarchs, but what about ordinary people? So we just want to give publicity to these miracles of the Zone and make it so that they are not afraid, but respected. Can you imagine how we and only WE can advance in development? And even worse, the heads of government can develop some kind of weapon, and if they understand the phenomenon of psi radiation ... \nWe basically have no rules here, but some discipline is still needed for simple survival, therefore During operations, our soldiers obey the teams of senior and experienced in the unit. But all this is nothing more than a necessity. Did I interest you? You can join our ranks, good fighters will not hinder us very much.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="in_freedom_1_0">
		<text>I want to join your ranks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="in_freedom_1_1">
		<text>Ohhh dude! I respect you. Entrance means we have "free", take the starting equipment and blow on the embrasure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="in_freedom_1_2">
		<text>Thank you, good luck.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="out_freedom_0">
		<text>I want to leave the group.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="out_freedom_1">
		<text>OK, man, this is your choice. Sorry if we offend you. Go, I will inform ours.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="monolith_show_path_0">
		<text>Hello, brother. Don't you know of any hidden ways?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_1">
		<text>I know one, but no offense, for one gift of "monolith" called "Flash" I will tell you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_2">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_3">
		<text>Wait, I don't have anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_4">
		<text>I know and I'll mark "monolith" as "moonlight" for one gift.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_5">
		<text>Wait, I don't have anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_6">
		<text>I know, brother. But I will not share until I have received a gift called "Soul."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_7">
		<text>Wait, I don't have anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_8">
		<text>No offense, but I'm only gonna mark it for "Twisted".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_9">
		<text>Wait, I don't have anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_10">
		<text>No, I don't know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_show_path_11">
		<text>I don't know, brother.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_about_lottery_0">
		<text>There's a lot to do here, it's fucking boring.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_about_lottery_1">
		<text>What suckers do not stick? I have one scam. You can tear off stripes from someone for the sake of burning stripes and win good equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_barman_dar_mlr_about_lottery_3">
		<text>Keep it for yourself, you'll need it if you keep bullying guys. Let's see what's going on.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_0">
		<text>I have patches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_1">
		<text>Go ahead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_2">
		<text>Clear Sky, 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_3">
		<text>Mercenaries, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_4">
		<text>Stalkers, 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_5">
		<text>Scientists, 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_6">
		<text>Freedom, 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_7">
		<text>Duty, 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_8">
		<text>Monolith, only 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_9">
		<text>Army, 10 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_10">
		<text>Clear Sky, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_11">
		<text>Mercenaries, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_12">
		<text>Stalkers, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_13">
		<text>Scientists, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_14">
		<text>Freedom, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_15">
		<text>Duty, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_16">
		<text>Monolith, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_17">
		<text>Army, 50 pieces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_18">
		<text>I probably changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_19">
		<text>Here, take your art.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_20">
		<text>Hold on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_21">
		<text>Take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_22">
		<text>Keep your art.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_23">
		<text>Lucky, you fucking.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_24">
		<text>Take the goods.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_25">
		<text>Here, take a good art.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_26">
		<text>And you are lucky! Radiation kit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_27">
		<text>Good art. Here you go:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_28">
		<text>Two whole arts! Well, you're crazy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_29">
		<text>You're gonna get me so fucked up, geez.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_30">
		<text>You're lucky.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_31">
		<text>You get the anomaly crawl kit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_32">
		<text>Look what a cool art I get!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_33">
		<text>This is luck!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_34">
		<text>Fucked up!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_35">
		<text>Fuck you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_36">
		<text>Bad luck for you, horseshit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_37">
		<text>No way.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_38">
		<text>Ooh, nice gear. And it's fucking yours!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_bandit_barman_dar_mlr_39">
		<text>Here's your major set:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="buy_perehod_0">
		<text>Greetings. Do you happen to know any information about hidden passageways?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_1">
		<text>Yeah, I know a few... But you do realize that no one gives information for free in the Zone, right? For 8,000, I can tell you and show you in your PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3">
		<text>It's a little expensive... Someday later.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_0">
		<text>I'd buy information about transitions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_1">
		<text>I know there's a couple... I'll mark your PDA for one Moonlight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_2">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_3">
		<text>Wait, I don't have anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_4">
		<text>I know, I know. Let's have one "Soul" and I'll mark it in your PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_5">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_2_6">
		<text>Wait, I don't have anything.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_0">
		<text>I'd like to find information about transitions, I really need it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_1">
		<text>I know, I know. Give one "Soul" and I will mark it in your PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_2">
		<text>Hold on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_3">
		<text>Wait, I have nothing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_4">
		<text>Do not be offended, but only for the “twist” I will mark it to you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_5">
		<text>Hold on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_3_6">
		<text>Wait, I have nothing.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="buy_perehod_4_0">
		<text>Greetings. Do you happen to know information about hidden passages?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_4_1">
		<text>Ask the merchants, they probably know, but I do not.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_4_2">
		<text>No, I do not know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="buy_perehod_4_3">
		<text>I don't know, but they definitely are.</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>