<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_axe">
	    <text>Hatchet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]Hatchet - a tool that has been used for thousands of years to work with wood. In ChEZ it is used by stalkers for cutting brushwood, less often for finishing large mutants. It is a formidable weapon in the hands of a skilled stalker.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] battle \n%c[0,109,117,7] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] chopping down any creatures \n%c[0,18,18,165] • %c[default] used as:%c[0,170,170,170] tool for camp deployment \n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] disassembling various equipment: boots, backpacks, - as an auxiliary tool</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe2">
	    <text>Fire axe</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe2_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]Fire axe - used to complete fire panels and stands. In the CEZ, it is used by stalkers to cut down tailings, less often to achieve large mutants. It is a formidable weapon in the hands of a skilled stalker.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] battle \n%c[0,109,117,7] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] chopping down any creatures \n%c[0,18,18,165] • %c[default] used as:%c[0,170,170,170] tool for camp deployment\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] disassembling various equipment: boots, backpacks, - as an auxiliary tool</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe3">
		<text>Hunting axe</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe3_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]Hunting axe is a tool that has been used for thousands of years to cut down wood, as a weapon and even as a ceremonial object. The axe has many different shapes, but usually consists of a colon with a handle. In the Zone, an axe can mean both life and death.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] battle \n%c[0,109,117,7] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] mutant skining \n%c[0,18,18,165] • %c[default] used as:%c[0,170,170,170] tool for camp deployment\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] disassembling various equipment: boots, backpacks, - as an auxiliary tool</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-fmj">
		<text>.45 ACP FMJ rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-fmj_s">
		<text>.45 ACP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-fmj_descr">
		<text>The .45 calibre full metal jacket round has enjoyed popularity for more than a hundred years thanks to its heavy bullet and a relatively small propelling charge. As a result, the bullet in this round is relatively slow but highly accurate and provides considerable stopping power.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]I\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12.7x55-fmj">
		<text>12.7x55 STs-130 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12.7x55-fmj_s">
		<text>12.7x55mm STs-130</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12.7x55-fmj_descr">
		<text>12.7x55 mm STs-130 - Russian rifle with subsonic bullet speed, designed by TSKIB SOO for low-noise and free of charge engagement of protected targets and manpower in heavy armored vests at ranges up to 600 meters.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]very strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_12.7x55_ap">
		<text>12.7x55mm STs-130 VPS rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_12.7x55_ap_s">
		<text>12.7x55mm STs-130 VPS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo_12.7x55_ap_descr">
		<text>Large-caliber sniper cartridge STs-130 VPS (high penetration capability) is designed to engage silent fire of enemy's live force protected by heavy SIBs (5-6 levels of protection according to GOST R50744-95) at ranges up to 200 meters or located behind various obstacles (car trim, door, glass, fence, etc.) at ranges up to 600 meters, as well as to engage light and unarmoured vehicles.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]V\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]very strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.92x33_fmj">
 		<text>7.92x33mm Mauser rounds</text>
 	</string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.92x33_fmj_s">
 		<text>7.92x33mm Mauser</text>
 	</string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.92x33_fmj_descr">
 		<text>The 7.92x33mm Mauser cartridge was adopted in the first half of the last century by the German Empire, and then by the Third Reich. It was one of the most popular cartridges during two world wars. However, nowadays it is primarily used for hunting and sporting events.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]AIII\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	 </string>
	<string id="ammo-7.92x57_fmj">
 		<text>7.92x57mm FMJ rounds</text>
 	</string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.92x57_fmj_s">
 		<text>7.92x57mm FMJ</text>
 	</string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.92x57_fmj_descr">
 		<text>7.92x57mm FMJ - German rifle and submachine gun unitary cartridge with bottle-shaped sleeve with no protruding edge. Used mainly for long-range shooting, this cartridge is of higher quality than standard cartridge.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	 </string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_fmj">
		<text>7.62x51mm NATO rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_fmj_s">
		<text>7.62x51 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_fmj_descr">
		<text>7.62x51 NATO - army version of .308 round, which was used by NATO forces as a standard round until 5.56mm ammunition was introduced during the Vietnam War in the 70s. Nowadays, these cartridges are most often used by mercenaries around the world. 7.62x51 is a typical handgun caliber, but can also be used in sniper rifles.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]III\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_ap">
		<text>7,62x51mm DU rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_ap_s">
		<text>7,62x51mm DU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x51_ap_descr">
    <text>7.62x51 depleted uranium cartridges are produced and used by private military organizations around the world. The need to develop a DU-version of this cartridge arose during large-scale secret military operations against drug cartels in some countries.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-hydro">
		<text>.45 ACP Hydra-shock rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-hydro_s">
		<text>.45 Hydra-shock</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-hydro_descr">
		<text>Non-standard type of cartridge for .45 ACP (11.43x23 mm) caliber - half shell bullet with expansive hollow point and steel core. This combination of half shell and armor-piercing bullet has both advantages and disadvantages of both types of cartridges.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]II\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]very strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-ap">
		<text>.45 DU rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-ap_s">
		<text>.45 DU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-11.43x23-ap_descr">
		<text>Chuck with depleted uranium core in .45 ACP caliber (11.43x23 mm). Since its first use in combat conditions, depleted uranium has been widely criticized in the international community - rumors of its harmful effects and radiation poisoning have been the main reason for the banning of depleted uranium. The bullet's core is self-sharpening, allowing it to be used against armored targets. Uranium heats up as it penetrates the target and inflicts additional damage with burns, but this process certainly doesn't lead to radiation exposure. This ammunition is actively used only by the U.S., and less effective versions are sometimes used in several other countries.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]above average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-357-hp">
		<text>.357 HP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-357-hp_s">
		<text>.357 HP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-357-hp_descr">
		<text>.357 HP is an extended bullet cartridge. The purpose of such cartridges is to slow down the penetration of the bullet, but at the same time to cause great internal tissue damage. \n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]above average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-357-incendiary">
		<text>.357 Incendiary rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-357-incendiary_s">
		<text>.357 Incendiary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-357-incendiary_descr">
		<text>This ammunition uses phosphorous to pierce the target. Phosphorus-supplied cartridges were first used during the First World War. At present, incendiary ammunition is used only by a small number of organizations, because not every weapon is capable of firing this type of ammunition. This ammunition is of medium quality and is sold at a very reasonable price. They do not explode when hit, but provide a reliable hit to the target.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IIIA\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong\n %c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] tracer ammo</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-338-lapua">
		<text>.338 Lapua Magnum rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-338-lapua_s">
		<text>.338 Lapua Magnum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-338-lapua_descr">
		<text>.338 Lapua Magnum is a specialized bottle-type cartridge with no protruding edge, designed for long-range army sniper rifles. The wars in Iraq and Afghanistan made this battle-tested ammunition quite affordable. The .338 Lapua Magnum ammunition is a dual-purpose cartridge: anti-personnel and anti-tank, but the antitank capability is very limited.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-338-du">
		<text>.338 DU rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-338-du_s">
		<text>.338 DU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-338-du_descr">
		<text>.338 DU with depleted uranium core based on .338 Lapua Magnum cartridge. The ammunition was designed for private military organizations based in Iraq, which were opposed by numerous armored targets, mainly tanks stolen from Pakistan and infantry in bulletproof vests sold by sympathizers from the Middle East. To stop the supply of modern equipment to insurgents, three major private military organizations conducted a joint operation against arms dealers and suppliers in Iraq and Tajikistan. The .338 DU cartridge was designed to combat the armored targets involved in the operation. This cartridge is extremely rare because of the trade agreement between the companies involved in its creation, but is highly valued by those working in the military private sector. \n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]V\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x70-buck">
		<text>12x70 Buckshot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x70-buck_s">
		<text>12x70 Buckshot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x70-buck_descr">
		<text>The usual cartridge of the 12th caliber, equipped with a shot with a diameter of 6 mm. At close range it has a huge lethal and stopping effect. Designed for firing smoothbore weapons and shotguns.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]above average\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] a flying cloud of fractions, short effective range</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x76-zhekan">
		<text>12x76 Slug</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x76-zhekan_s">
		<text>12x76 Slug</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x76-zhekan_descr">
		<text>12-gauge cartridge with a shellless bullet. Usually used for hunting large animals, but it is also suitable for other purposes: its heavy bullet does not penetrate, but actually squeezes the bulletproof vests.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]AIII\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x76-dart">
		<text>12x76 Dart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x76-dart_s">
		<text>12x76 Dart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-12x76-dart_descr">
		<text>Cartridge of the 12th caliber with a heavy shellless bullet. Usually used for hunting large animals, but suitable for other purposes. His heavy bullet actually pushes through bulletproof vests.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]AIII\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-ap">
		<text>5.45x39mm AP (7N22) rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-ap_s">
		<text>5.45x39 AP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-ap_descr">
		<text>An army cartridge 7H22 of 5.45x39 mm caliber with an armor-piercing bullet is used in automatic rifles of many countries participating in the Warsaw Pact. Inside the bullet is an armor-piercing core made of tool steel grade U12A. Effective against body armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-fmj">
		<text>5,45x39mm FMJ (7N10) rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-fmj_s">
		<text>5,45x39mm FMJ</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.45x39-fmj_descr">
		<text>The army 7N10 round of 5.45x39mm caliber with high penetration bullet is used in automatic rifles of many countries-participants of the Warsaw Pact. It has reduced recoil impulse and increased direct shot range by 100 m, providing better accuracy than the old 7.62x39 mm cartridge.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]AIII\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ap">
		<text>5.56x45mm AP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ap_s">
		<text>5.56x45mm AP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ap_descr">
		<text>The main armor-piercing cartridge of NATO troops of 5.56x45mm caliber with increased penetration, known under the index SS190 / M855. Effective against body armor. It is widely used in firearms of armies and special services of Western countries.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ss190">
		<text>5.56x45mm SS190 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ss190_s">
		<text>5.56x45mm SS190</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.56x45-ss190_descr">
		<text>A service cartridge of 5.56x45mm NATO forces for aimed fire in bursts, developed on the basis of hunting cartridges. Known as SS109. It has excellent ballistic characteristics.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]II\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] reduced penetration\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] increased soft tissue fragmentation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-7n1">
		<text>7.62x54mm 7N1 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-7n1_s">
		<text>7.62x54mm 7N1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-7n1_descr">
		<text>7.62x54mm sniper cartridge with combined lead-steel core, specially designed for SVD. Unlike a machine-gun cartridge, 7H1 provides good accuracy and excellent penetration.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54_7n14">
		<text>7.62x54mm 7N14 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54_7n14_s">
		<text>7.62x54mm 7N14</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54_7n14_descr">
		<text>A specially designed modernized sniper cartridge of 7.62x54mm with an SNB armor-piercing bullet. The bullet is equipped with a combined core of lead and hardened steel grade U12A, capable of penetrating body armor and small obstacles. Compared with a standard cartridge of the same caliber, it has a lightweight tail section, which provides greater accuracy and improved ballistic performance.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]V\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-ap">
		<text>7.62x54mm AP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-ap_s">
		<text>7.62x54mm AP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-ap_descr">
		<text>Inexpensive armor-piercing machine gun cartridge of 7.62x54mm caliber. Due to its design features, it is unsuitable for shooting with sniper rifles, therefore it is used as ammunition for the PKM machine gun. This cartridge has increased power and, thanks to the steel core, has a very good piercing ability. Powerful cartridge for powerful weapons.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-pp">
		<text>Belt with 7.62x54mm PP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-pp_s">
		<text>Belt with 7.62x54mm PP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-pp_descr">
		<text>Non-dispersible metal belt with cheap 7.62x54 mm armor-piercing machine-gun rounds. Due to its design features it's unsuitable for sniper rifles, so it's used as ammunition for PKM machine gun. This round has an increased power and, thanks to the steel core, has a very good penetration. Powerful cartridge for powerful weapons.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-r">
		<text>7.62x54mm R rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-r_s">
		<text>7.62x54mm R</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x54-r_descr">
		<text>Inexpensive cartridge rifle caliber 7.62x54mm R, adopted by the Russian Empire at the turn of the 19th century and continued to be used in the USSR even after the end of World War II. The cartridge was originally designed for 7.62mm Mosin rifles, very popular now in the Zone. Despite its low cost, it has good penetration characteristics, not inferior to modern types of ammunition. It can also be used as a cheap alternative to ammunition for the PKM machine gun.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]III\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-fmj">
		<text>9x18mm FMJ rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-fmj_s">
		<text>9x18mm FMJ</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-fmj_descr">
		<text>Cartridge with a shell bullet - with a steel core and a lead shirt under a metal shell. It has a good stopping effect, but is ineffective against body armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]II\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]below the average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-pmm">
		<text>9x18mm +P+ rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-pmm_s">
		<text>9x18mm +P+</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-pmm_descr">
		<text>Cartridge with bullet increased stopping action 7N16. European marking +P+ means "very high pressure in the barrel." Compared to a conventional cartridge, the bullet speed is increased by 30%. Ineffective against body armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]I\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]above average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-ap">
		<text>9x18mm RG028 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-ap_s">
		<text>9x18mm RG028</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x18-ap_descr">
		<text>RG028 - a cartridge used to penetrate light armor. The purpose of the creation of WG028 was to counter opponents in personal protective equipment; for this reason, the cartridge is equipped with a hardened steel core. Unfortunately, the cartridge itself does not greatly exceed the standard 9x18, but only has increased penetration.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IIIA\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]below the average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-fmj">
		<text>9x19mm FMJ rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-fmj_s">
		<text>9x19mm FMJ</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-fmj_descr">
		<text>Standard 9x19 mm cartridge with shell bullet. It has good ballistic characteristics and is inexpensive to manufacture. Particularly popular due to the fact that an international convention prohibits the use of expansive bullets in battle. Ineffective against body armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]I\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-pbp">
		<text>9x19mm PBP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-pbp_s">
		<text>9x19 9x19mm PBP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-pbp_descr">
		<text>A half-shell bullet with an expansive notch has a high stopping effect and is not prone to ricochets. It is used mainly as a "police" ammunition and in civilian personal protective weapons. It is ineffective against body armor because of its low penetrating potential.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]I\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-ap">
		<text>9x19mm AP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-ap_s">
		<text>9x19mm AP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x19-ap_descr">
		<text>Armor-piercing bullet with a steel core. Designed to improve the penetration ability of pistols and submachine guns. It is used mainly by anti-terrorist and special police units when they encounter opponents protected by bulletproof vests.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]III\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]below the average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss190">
		<text>5.7x28mm SS190 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss190_s">
		<text>5.7x28mm SS190</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss190_descr">
		<text>The 5.7x28 (SS190) round was developed by the Belgian Fabrique Nationale specifically for the FN P90 submachine gun in the mid-1980s. This round was later used in "Five SeveN" pistol. The cartridge has a higher penetration power than other pistol cartridges. The bullet reaches muzzle velocity of up to 716 m/s and can penetrate body armour. The stopping power of the bullet is three times that of the 9x19mm bullet.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]III\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]below the average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss195">
		<text>5.7x28mm SS195 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss195_s">
		<text>5.7x28mm SS195</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-5.7x28-ss195_descr">
		<text>SS195LF (1.8 g, 720 m / s) - cartridge with an expansive bullet, has a lower breakdown ability than the SS190, but with a large stopping effect and lethal force.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]I\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x39-ap">
		<text>9x19mm SP-6 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x39-ap_s">
		<text>9x39 SP-6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x39-ap_descr">
		<text>The subsonic armor-piercing "automatic" SP-6 cartridge is equipped with a semi-shell bullet with a partially open core made of hardened steel. Requires the use of a silencer to ensure silent shooting. Distributed in some countries participating in the Warsaw Pact. Extremely effective against body armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]above average\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] subsonic cartridge\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] significant reduction in bullet path over long distances</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x39-pab9">
		<text>9x39mm SP-5 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x39-pab9_s">
		<text>9x39mm SP-5</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-9x39-pab9_descr">
		<text>The subsonic “sniper” cartridge SP-5 is equipped with a bimetallic shell. The cavity behind the steel core is filled with lead. Requires the use of a silencer to ensure silent shooting. Distributed in some countries participating in the Warsaw Pact. Effective against body armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]III\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]above average\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] subsonic cartridge\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] significant reduction in bullet path over long distances</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-m209">
		<text>Grenade M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-m209_s">
		<text>M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-m209_descr">
		<text>Grenade grenade launcher M203 caliber 40 mm. The radius of the effective area of destruction by fragments is about 3.5 m. It can also be used in the integrated grenade launcher complex FN F2000.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]average\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]4.1 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]28 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]95 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (explodes on impact)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-og-7b">
		<text>Projectile OG-7V</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-og-7b_s">
		<text>OG-7V</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-og-7b_descr">
		<text>High-explosive fragmentation projectile for a grenade launcher. With the help of the RPG-7 launcher, it allows you to hit an enemy who has hidden behind at a distance exceeding the throwing range of a hand grenade.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]high\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]5.6 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]41 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]153 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (explodes on impact)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-vog-25">
		<text>Grenade VOG-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-vog-25_s">
		<text>VOG-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-vog-25_descr">
		<text>Fragmentation ammunition for GP-25 "Bonfire", GP-30 "Shoes", RG-6 " Dwarf" grenades, combining grenade and projectile charge in a cartridge case. The grenade is muzzle-loading, i.e. i's fed into the barrel through the barrel.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]average\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]3.6 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]20 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]81 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (explodes on impact)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-vog-25p">
		<text>Grenade VOG-25P</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-vog-25p_s">
		<text>VOG-25P</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-vog-25p_descr">
		<text>Shot with a "bouncing" fragmentation grenade equipped with a VGM-P fuse with a bouncing charge and a pyrotechnic delayer. Upon hitting the obstacle the round bounces and explodes in the air at a height of about 1.5 meters. Compared to the VOG-25, the bouncing ammunition is more effective against a lying and entrenched enemy.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]average\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]3.6 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]20 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]81 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]present (bounce on impact)</text>
	</string>
  	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_ap">
		<text>7.62x39mm M43 rounds</text>
	 </string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_ap_s">
 		<text>7.62x39mm M43</text>
	 </string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_ap_descr">
 		<text>Ammunition 7.62x39 M43, made in China, with a bullet of increased penetration ability, which is often referred to as "7.62x39 CN." The cartridge has a soft steel core that increases penetration. This Chinese ammunition (in principle, like all other M43 cartridges) is currently banned for import into the United States, as federal law classifies it as armor-piercing. This classification is based on the materials and design of the bullet, and not on its ability to penetrate armor.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IV\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	 </string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_fmj">
 		<text>7.62x39mm FMJ rounds</text>
 	</string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_fmj_s">
 		<text>7.62x39mm FMJ</text>
 	</string>
 	<string id="ammo-7.62x39_fmj_descr">
 		<text>The 7.62x39mm cartridge with an all-metal shell is one of the most popular ammunition used, especially in Africa and the Middle East. Many call it the "Bullet of the Revolution" in connection with its frequent use by both terrorists and criminal organizations. Due to the huge penetration ability of this cartridge, the military of all countries had to strengthen the armor protection of their units, since the probability of encountering this munition in combat situations is very high.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]AIII\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	 </string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p">
		<text>7.62x25mm P rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p_s">
		<text>7.62x25mm P</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p_descr">
		<text>Soviet pistol cartridge 7.62mm, now known as 7.62mm Tokarev. The bullet has a lead core and a steel shell clad with tompak. The initial velocity of the bullet is 420 m / s, the energy is 510 J. In order to more reliably connect the bullet to the sleeve made of brass, the bullet was fixed in the sleeve with a circular crimp of the sleeve barrel followed by roll. In the warehouses of the military units of the Armed Forces of the Russian Federation there is still a very large number of these cartridges. \n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]I\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-ps">
		<text>7.62x25mm PS rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-ps_s">
		<text>7.62x25 PS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-ps_descr">
		<text>7.62mm pistol cartridge with a steel core bullet (7.62 PS), weight 5.6 grams mm. Adopted in 1953. The cartridge has a bimetallic (GAU Index - 57-H-134C) or brass (GAU Index - 57-H-132C) sleeve. The stopping effect of the bullet was maximally close to the performance of the 9x19 mm Parabellum bullet.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]II\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]strong</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p41">
		<text>7,62x25mm P-41 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p41_s">
		<text>7,62x25mm P-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-7.62x25-p41_descr">
		<text>In 1941, the Red Army adopted the cartridge with an armor-piercing incendiary bullet with a steel core, under the designation "P-41". The head part of the PT bullet was covered with black varnish with a red stripe. In 1943, a cartridge with the tracer bullet “PT” began to be produced, which gave a red luminous trail at a distance of 350 - 400 meters.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]IIIA\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]below the average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p29">
		<text>USP-1 sight "Tyulpan"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p29_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] all weapons of the Warsaw Pact\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The USP-1 unified rifle scope is designed for aimed firing from AK-74N, AK-74M, AN-94 machine guns and RPK-74N and PKMN machine guns in the daytime and at night against luminous and illuminated targets. 1P29 - index of the sight USP-1 of the Main Artillery Directorate of the Ministry of Defense of the USSR. It was created as part of the Tulip ROC, from where it got its name.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]USP-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p59">
		<text>1P59 "Gyperon" sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p59_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] sniper rifles with dove tail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Ñhe series of Russian pancratic sights designed for target reconnaissance and target shooting with sniper rifles (SVD, SVDK, etc.). The whole series is designed according to the project "Breaker". Provides the possibility of sighting shooting at distances from 100 to 1300 m.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]10.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]1P59</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p78">
		<text>1P78 sight "Kashtan"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p78_descr">
		<text>The 1P78 sight is designed to equip machine guns and light machine guns. The sight has a magnification of 2.8X, the optical design is similar to the 1P77 sight. Designed by Central Design Bureau “Tochpribor” (Novosibirsk), chief designer - S.I. Mikhalenko.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]2.8x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn34">
		<text>1PN34 sight (NSPU)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn34_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] all weapons of the Warsaw Pact\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]NSPU (from Unified Night Sight Unified; GRAU index 1PN34) is a Soviet sublime night optical sight designed for aimed shooting from AK family assault rifles (AKMN-1, AKMSN-1, AK74N, AKS74N), RPK family machine guns (RPKN-1, RPKSN -1, RPK-74N, RPKS74N), PKM family machine guns (PKMN-1, PKMSN-1), SVDN-1 sniper rifles, RPG-7N1 hand-held anti-tank grenade launcher (RPG-7DN1) in conditions of natural night illumination at distances up to 400 m per person and up to 600 m in a tank. Developed by Orion NPO (then: Research Institute of Applied Physics of the USSR Ministry of Defense Industry). Production was established at the Novosibirsk Instrument-Making Plant.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]NSPU-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn93">
		<text>Sight 1PN93-4 "Baby"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn93_descr">
		<text>Night sight 1PN93-4 for SVD and SVDS sniper rifle is intended for observation of the battlefield and aiming in conditions of natural night illumination at ambient temperature from plus 50°C to minus 50°C and relative air humidity up to 100% (at temperature of 25°C). Side correction scales, rangefinder mesh, alignment mechanisms, brightness adjustment and automatic protection against backlight are provided in the sight design. The sight is mounted on a standard mount with a side plate for Russian small arms.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]NSPU-</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_acog">
		<text>ACOG 3.5x sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_acog_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Detachable riflescope designed for rifles of NATO countries. ACOG stands for Advanced Combat Optical Gunsight and belongs to the Trijicon family of optical sights. Sights of this type are mounted on a picatinny rail and have tritium illumination. This instance with a reticle USMC and a magnification of 3.5x.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]3.5x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]USMC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ac10632">
		<text>Barska ELECTRO SIGHT AC10632 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ac10632_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]ELECTRO SIGHT 1x22x33 collimator sight for quick aiming. Shockproof, suitable for all types of weapons with a picatinny rail. Selecting the brightness level of the illumination of the reticle (7 steps) allows you to use the sight at different levels of illumination.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ac11090">
		<text>Barska AC11090 Red Dot sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ac11090_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Inexpensive two-time indoor collimator sight RED DOT 2x30mm. Multilayer enlightenment optics. 100% waterproof. Resistant to fogging. Shockproof. Wide field of view, unlimited removal of the exit pupil. Suitable for NATO assault rifles and PP.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]2x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]Red Dot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_aimpoint">
		<text>Aimpoint Sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_aimpoint_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Aimpoint CompM2 is a rechargeable, compact small arms sight developed and manufactured by the Swedish company Aimpoint AB. It is a collimator sight with a target marker in the form of a red dot. The sight housing is made of aviation aluminum, the color is matte black. It allows mechanical adjustment of the brightness of the marker (4 positions for the dark and 6 for the light). The design of the sight provides for use in the dark in combination with a night vision device. Aimpoint AB claims that at ranges up to 50 m the scope is not affected by parallax.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_c_more">
		<text>C-MORE Railway Tactical sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_c_more_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]High-quality collimator sight, providing an unlimited field of view, eliminating obstruction and "tunnel vision" characteristic of sights of a tubular shape.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]XPS3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_coyote">
		<text>Collimator sight Coyote JH-406</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_coyote_descr">
		<text>The JH-406 Reflex is ideally suited for fast shooting, quick capture or shooting at a moving target thanks to an unlimited field of view, while both eyes can remain open, eliminating the feeling of tunnel vision.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]JH-406</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_delta">
		<text>DeltaPoint Sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_delta_descr">
		<text>The Leupold DeltaPoint is a compact sight for pistols with a red dot and a unique triangular mesh, it is extremely effective for accurate target shooting.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_eotech">
		<text>EOTech 552.A65 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_eotech_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The EOTech 512 holographic sight is the most popular in its class. This tactical sight is very popular among hunters. It is chosen by all those who need speed and versatility without the need for night vision. Low cost is an additional advantage. The EOTech 512 holographic sight refers to open sights, so the shooter can use both eyes during shooting. Using peripheral vision provides a larger field of view and allows you to instantly respond to an emerging target. It should be noted that the speed of fire with a holographic sight is much higher than with an optical one, therefore it is often used when shooting at moving targets. Another characteristic feature of the EOTech sights is that they can be used in any weather - in rain and snow, and in heavy fog. The sighting mark will be clearly visible even if the exit window is covered with snow or mud, or even broken. The sight allows the installation of additional equipment, such as a magnifier (magnifier). \n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]x1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_kobra">
		<text>"Kobra" sight EKP-1S-03</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_kobra_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] all weapons of the Warsaw Pact\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The Kobra sight provides confident aiming in natural light conditions (bright sunny day, deep twilight and moonlit night) due to the presence of 16 levels of manual brightness adjustment of the aiming mark. The location of the aiming mark and target in the same plane allows aiming with both one and two eyes, which creates an unlimited field of view for the shooter, and conduct effective high-speed shooting at quickly moving, small and suddenly appearing for a short time targets.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170] absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_okp-7">
		<text>OKP-7 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_okp-7_descr">
		<text>The original design of the OKP sights makes it possible to conduct targeted fire from unstable positions and in a rapidly changing environment, reduces fatigue, and also, if necessary, allows the use of a standard mechanical device. The main feature of the sight is the mount of the reflector without a mechanical frame that covers a significant part of the firing sectors. Reflector protection in extreme conditions is provided by a thin and durable metal visor that practically does not interfere with firing.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170] absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ekp_8_02">
		<text>"Kobra" sight EKP-8-02</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ekp_8_02_descr">
		<text>EKP-8-02 Kobra is an open red dot sight. Designed to hit fast-moving targets and solve transient tasks at close range in urban environments under various lighting conditions. Provides clear aiming at illumination from 104lx to 2-10lx (daylight, twilight and moonlight) from one or two eyes, is very effective when shooting from moving vehicles, and is also ideal for hitting fast-moving, small and spontaneously appearing targets.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170] absent (collimator)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pk-a">
		<text>PK-A sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pk-a_descr">
		<text>The PK-A collimator sight is a modern lightweight, sealed, easy-to-learn sight for Tiger hunting carbines with a side bar for mounting optical sights. The sight is designed to accurately target the AK-74N, RPK-74N, AKMN-1, RPKN-1 weapons when firing under various lighting conditions - in the daytime, at dusk, in conditions of poor visibility and rapidly changing illumination. The sight is sealed and filled with dry nitrogen to prevent fogging of the internal optical surfaces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pgo7b">
		<text>PGO-7V sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pgo7b_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] all weapons of the Warsaw Pact\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The PGO-7V is a soviet optical sight developed at the Tochpribor Central Design Bureau (Novosibirsk) to increase the accuracy of fire from RPG-7 and RPG-7D hand grenade launchers. It is a combination of optical elements with a prism wrapping system, placed inside a metal case. To prevent fogging of the lenses, the housing is sealed and filled with dry nitrogen. The design of the sight has a grid illumination system and a rangefinder scale, in addition, it is possible to enter lateral corrections and range corrections. The package includes a set of additional color filters.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170] x2.7\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pks">
		<text>PKC-07 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pks_descr">
		<text>The PKS-07 is a standard daytime sight for many of Russia's latest generation firearms, such as: SV-98 sniper rifle, L96A1, Sako TRG, VSSK "Vychlop", large-caliber automatic rifle ASh-12.\n When turned on, it uses the collimator effect to generating a highlighted aiming point. In the event of a battery discharge or failure, the red dot does not disappear, but turns black, and the scope remains operational.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170] x8\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_po4x34">
		<text>PO4x34 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_po4x34_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] weapons of the OTs-14 series\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]An optical sight of constant and variable magnification is mounted on a rifled weapon and is intended for aimed aiming it when firing. The sight is mounted on weapons using special brackets.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]4x34</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pn23">
		<text>PN23 "Saracin" sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pn23_descr">
		<text>The sight Saratsin is one of the latest developments of Novosibirsk Instrument-Making Plant and has been mass-produced since 2011. Its distinctive feature is light weight (670 g.) and dimensions. The sight body is made of aluminum alloy. The sight is equipped with EOS of generation 2+ or 3. The device can be used in twilight lighting and until almost total darkness (moonless cloudy night). In total darkness, all you need to do is turn on the built-in IR illuminator with a ball rotating mechanism, which allows you to continue monitoring and aiming regardless of the ambient light conditions. The swivel mechanism is designed to direct the illumination beam to the desired point.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]PN23</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso">
		<text>PSO-1M sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] all weapons of the Warsaw Pact\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The PSO-1M sight (Sniper Optical Sight) is a series of Soviet optical sights produced by the Novosibirsk Instrument-Making Plant. It was developed in 1964 as a standard sight for the SVD rifle. Later he began to be widely used on Kalashnikov rifles, light machine guns, special rifles and carbines. He got his recognition for durability, versatility and a very good thought-out type of reticle with a convenient range finder. This instance of fixed multiplicity 4.0x, which makes it suitable mainly for use over long distances. It is widespread in the countries of the Warsaw Pact, uses a dovetail mount.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]PSO-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso-1m2-01">
		<text>PSO-1M2-1 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso-1m2-01_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] all weapons of the Warsaw Pact\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]A special version of the PSO-1M sight with a reticle, designed specifically to simplify firing using low-speed, heavy subsonic cartridges of type 9x39. The grid marking and the special scale of the range finder make it easy to calculate the compensating environmental factors. There is a grid illumination in low light conditions. This set of properties allowed the use of such sights in special forces, most often with weapons OTs-14 "Thunderstorm" and AS "VAL". It is also a standard sight on the silent VSS Vintorez sniper rifle. Although its purpose is purely specialized, the sight has a standard dovetail mount and can be mounted on any other weapon of the Warsaw Pact countries.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]very good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]PSO-1-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pu">
		<text>PU sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pu_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] historical soviet weapon\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]PU (Universal Sight) - a standard optical sight of the Red Army during the Great Patriotic War. Designed for installation on a Mosin rifle and SVT-40. The design turned out to be so successful and reliable that this sight still enjoys well-deserved popularity. It has a fixed multiplicity of 3.5x, which makes it a good choice for conducting combat at medium and long distances.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]3.5x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]bearable\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]PU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_rakurs">
		<text>Collimator sight "Racurs-PM"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_rakurs_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The “Rakurs-PM” wide-angle collimator sight is designed for aimed firing at a range of direct shot from rifled and smooth-bore weapons. The presence of a grid backlight allows for targeted shooting at dusk and at night, provided that the target is visible. Illumination of the sight is carried out without batteries, based on the effect of emitting visible radiation of the phosphor. The sight housing is made of durable aircraft aluminum.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_specterDR">
		<text>ELCAN SpecterDR sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_specterDR_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Optical sight with variable magnification, designed to replace the 4-x ACOG sights from Trijicon.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]bearable\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SpecterDR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_tars101">
		<text>Trijicon TARS101 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_tars101_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The Trijicon Tactical Advanced Sight is an x3-15x variable zoom, 50mm illuminated lens for tactical and sporting rifles. Premium optics, precise settings and innovative sight systems allow users to hit targets at extreme distances.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]3.5x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]bearable\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]TARS101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_zf4">
		<text>ZF-4 sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_zf4_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] historic german weapon\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The ZF-4 (ZF-43) sight was created in Germany in 1943 on the basis of the Soviet PU optical sight. It was intended to equip regular troops to enable them to fight long distances. However, due to the insufficient number of produced sights, they were primarily provided with German snipers and elite units. To date, the ZF-4 remains quite popular in the Zone, since the weapons of the Second World War, for which it was developed, are still used here.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]2.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]bearable\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]ZF-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_galil">
		<text>Galil 4.0x sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_galil_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Galil AR automatic rifle\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Optical sight specially developed by Galil AR. A characteristic feature is the pylon-shaped reticle, which makes the sight suitable mainly for small and medium distances, since it covers the target at long distances. This instance has a fixed ratio of 4.0x and can be used for aimed fire at medium and long distances.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat">
		<text>SUSAT 4.0x sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT is an optical sight developed and widely used by the British Army during the Cold War, later also adapted by many other countries of the Western Bloc. A characteristic feature of the SUSAT is a pylon-shaped reticle, which makes the sight suitable mainly for small and medium distances, since it covers the target at long distances. This instance has a fixed ratio of 4.0x and can be used for aimed fire at medium distances.
\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]4.0x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_custom">
		<text>SUSAT Adjustable sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_custom_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT is an optical sight developed and widely used by the British Army during the Cold War, later also adapted by many other countries of the Western Bloc. A characteristic feature of the SUSAT is a pylon-shaped reticle, which makes the sight suitable mainly for small and medium distances, since it covers the target at long distances. This instance of the MERA type is equipped with optics of adjustable multiplicity with the possibility of independent adjustment.
\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]adjustable\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_dusk">
		<text>SUSAT 1.6x Twilight sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_dusk_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT is an optical sight developed and widely used by the British Army during the Cold War, later also adapted by many other countries of the Western Bloc. A characteristic feature of the SUSAT is a pylon-shaped reticle, which makes the sight suitable mainly for small and medium distances, since it covers the target at long distances. This instance of high contrast is designed for close combat in low light conditions.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]1.6x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] High contrast sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_night_vision">
		<text>SUSAT 1.6x Night sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_night_vision_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT is an optical sight developed and widely used by the British Army during the Cold War, later also adapted by many other countries of the Western Bloc. A characteristic feature of the SUSAT is a pylon-shaped reticle, which makes the sight suitable mainly for small and medium distances, since it covers the target at long distances. This instance with an integrated night vision device is designed for special forces.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]1.6x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Built-in third generation NV\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Require additional power</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_x1.6">
		<text>SUSAT 1.6x sight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_x1.6_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] Picatinny rail\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT is a telescopic sight developed and widely used in the British Army during the Cold War, later also adapted by many other Western Bloc countries. A characteristic feature of SUSAT is its pylon-shaped reticle, which makes the sight suitable mainly for short and medium range applications, as it overlaps the target at long range. This 1.6x fixed multiple is intended for close combat.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Zoom: %c[0,170,170,170]1.6x\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Glass condition: %c[0,170,170,170]good\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reticle Type: %c[0,170,170,170]SUSAT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_silencer">
		<text>Silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_silencer_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] none\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silencer.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_9mm">
		<text>Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_9mm_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 9mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silencer for weapons of 9mm caliber. Archaic in design and at the same time quite effective. Contains a tightly packed brass wire roll inside. In front of the device is a set of rubber diaphragms with holes for the passage of a bullet. Silencer is used in close combat against lightly armored opponents and for silent killings.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_45">
		<text>Silencer .45ACP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_45_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] .45 caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silent firing device for pistols of the .45 caliber.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]very high (pistol)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_pbs1">
		<text>Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_pbs1_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 7.62mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]PBS-1. A device for silent and flameless firing from a Kalashnikov assault rifle of 7.62 mm caliber. When installing a silencer, firing is carried out by ammunition cartridges with a subsonic bullet speed.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_pbs4">
		<text>Silencer PBS-4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_pbs4_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 5.45mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]PBS-4. A device for silent and flameless firing from a 5.45 mm shortened Kalashnikov assault rifle (AKS-74U).\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_tgp-a">
		<text>Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_tgp-a_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 5.45mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silencer tactical flame arrester “TGP-A-5.45” for 5.45 mm AK-series assault rifles and RPK-74 machine guns. The silencer design lacks a rubber shutter and there is no need to use cartridges with a subsonic bullet speed. However, firing accuracy when installing it is slightly impaired.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_nato">
		<text>Silencer NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_nato_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] .45, 5.56mm, 7.62mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]The device for silent and flameless firing for assault rifles of NATO standard 5.56x45 caliber, as well as for pistols and submachine guns of 11.43x23 caliber.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_kzrzp">
		<text>Silencer KZRZP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_kzrzp_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 7.62mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Device for soundless and flameless firing from SVD.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_atg">
		<text>Silencer ATG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_atg_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 5.56mm, 7.62mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silencer tactical assault rifle (ATG) is designed to reduce the sound and flame of a shot when firing from 5.56 mm AK101 and AK102 Kalashnikov assault rifles, as well as 7.62 mm AK103 and AK104 Kalashnikov assault rifles.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_9a91">
		<text>Silencer for 9A-91/VSK-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_9a91_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 9x39mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silent firing device for assault rifles 9A-91 and VSK-94.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_6p9">
		<text>Silencer 6P9</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_6p9_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 9mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silent firing device for the PB pistol (6P9).\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_vihr">
		<text>Silencer for SR-3M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_vihr_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 9x39mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silent firing device for machine gun SR-3M.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]very good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_gemtech">
		<text>Silencer GemTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_gemtech_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 9mm .45 caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silent firing device for Glock and FN FNP pistols.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_aps">
		<text>Silencer for APS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_aps_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 9mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Silent firing device for APS.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]average</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_57">
		<text>Silencer 5,7x28mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_57_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 5.7mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Device for silent and flameless firing for FN P90.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_sr25">
		<text>Silencer SR-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_sr25_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] 7.62mm caliber\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]Device for silent and flameless firing from a self-loading sniper rifle SR-25.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]good</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_f1">
		<text>F-1 Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_silencer_svu">
		<text>Silencer for SVU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_silencer_svu_descr">
		<text>\n%c[default]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] SVU rifle\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]This specially designed three-chamber silencer is not designed to completely silence an IED shot, as it does not use subsonic ammunition. Its main purpose is to reduce and "smear" the sound of the shot to make it difficult for the enemy to detect the shooter. The feature of this device is a very effective muzzle brake, which can reduce the recoil force by about 40%. However, such capabilities are achieved at the cost of reduced initial velocity of the bullet, significantly reducing the potential damage to the weapon.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sound muffling: %c[0,170,170,170]low\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] reduce impact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_f1_descr">
		<text>A hand-held anti-personnel defensive grenade. Designed to defeat manpower in defensive combat. Due to the large radius of the shrapnel, it can only be thrown for cover.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]high\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]4.2 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]48 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]380 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]~4 seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher">
		<text>GP-25 "Fire" underbarrel grenade launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_descr">
		<text>Single loaded, muzzle loaded grenade launcher for automatic rifles of Warsaw Pact countries. Self-propelled grenade launcher, with manual safety and automatic latching in case of improper installation. The equipment is fitted with VOG-25 ammunition.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Muzzle speed: %c[0,170,170,170]~76 m/sec\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Range of flight: %c[0,170,170,170]~300 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reload speed: %c[0,170,170,170]low\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Ammunition: %c[0,170,170,170]VOG-25 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203">
		<text>M203 underbarrel grenade launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203_descr">
		<text>Modification of the M203 single-shot grenade launcher with three inches shortened barrel and Picatinny bar mount. Thanks to the change of mounts, this model has found a very wide application all over the world. Despite its more modern design, it has mainly the same characteristics as its Soviet GP-25 counterpart.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Muzzle speed: %c[0,170,170,170]~76 m/sec\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Range of flight: %c[0,170,170,170]~300 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reload speed: %c[0,170,170,170]low\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Ammunition: %c[0,170,170,170]M203 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_ag36">
		<text>H&K AG36 underbarrel grenade launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_ag36_descr">
		<text>It is a 40mm single shot grenade launcher, developed by German arms company Hekler & Koch, primarily for use with the G36 rifle. It operates on the same principle as the standard M203 grenade launcher, while retaining its range characteristics.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Muzzle speed: %c[0,170,170,170]~76 m/sec\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Range of flight: %c[0,170,170,170]~300 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reload speed: %c[0,170,170,170]low\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Ammunition: %c[0,170,170,170]M203 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grenade_rgd5">
		<text>RGD-5 Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgd5_descr">
		<text>Soviet offensive hand grenade, refers to antipersonnel shrapnel hand grenades of remote action type. It means that it is designed to hit the enemy personnel with shrapnel from the hull when it explodes.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]average\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]3,2 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]43 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]240 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]~4 seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgn">
		<text>RGN Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgn_descr">
		<text>RGN (hand grenade offensive) - antipersonnel shrapnel shock and distance. Designed to defeat the living force in combat. The grenade fragmentation strike radius is 15 m, possible engagement radius is 35 m. \n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]average\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]3,2 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]15 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]200 (small shrapnel)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]~2 seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_thermite">
		<text>Thermite Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_thermite_descr">
		<text>A hand-held incendiary grenade (or thermite grenade) that intensively generates heat during an explosion (2200 degrees Celsius) due to an abundant thermal reaction in which powdered aluminum reacts with iron oxide to form a stream of molten iron and aluminum oxide. Filled with 600 or 800 grams of thermite.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]average (thermal damage)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]4.6 m\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]~4 seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgdm">
		<text>Smoke grenade RDG-M "Smoke"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgdm_descr">
		<text>The RDG-M "Smoke" instant-action hand grenade is designed to disguise internal affairs officers and internal servicemen from aimed fire of the enemy during special operations. Provides instant setting of a smoke masking curtain. The smoke curtain is opaque in the visible wavelength range for the entire time of existence, and at the time of formation in the infrared range. The grenade is equipped with a phosphorus-based smoke composition. There is no explosive charge in the grenade, which ensures the absence of fragments that can cause injury.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosive force: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Blast radius: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] The radius of fragmentation: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Number of fragments: %c[0,170,170,170]is absent\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Explosion Delay: %c[0,170,170,170]~4 seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vssk">
		<text>VSSK «Vyhlop»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vssk_descr">
		<text>VSSK "Vyhlop" (Special Large-caliber Sniper Rifle) is a silent large-caliber sniper rifle made according to the bullpup layout. The main purpose of VSSK is a low-noise and flameless defeat of lightly armored and unarmored vehicles, as well as manpower in personal protective equipment (including heavy bulletproof vests) at ranges up to 600 meters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, AC11090, PKS-07, C-MORE, EOTech, Coyote JH-406, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] integrated silencer 12.7mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak9">
		<text>AK-9</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak9_descr">
		<text>AK-9 is a shortened assault rifle, created by IzhMash designers on the basis of AK-74M, for arming special forces of the armed forces and the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Russia. The weapon has been in development since 2005. Tentatively, since 2010 all work on this sample has been discontinued; the Kalashnikov concern is currently developing a promising automatic machine for a 9x39 mm cartridge called AMB-17.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1, 1PN34\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer ATG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12">
		<text>AK-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_descr">
		<text>AK-12 - Kalashnikov assault rifle of the 2012 model, the development of the Kalashnikov concern. The weapon controls are significantly redesigned for the convenience of users, the fuse-translator flag has been changed and duplicated on the left side, a slide delay has been introduced, the button of which is also located on both sides. Another innovation is the use of Picatinny rails. One of the main features of the AK-12 was the increased ergonomics of the weapon compared to the AK-74M caliber 5.45x39 and the AKM caliber 7.62x39. The work carried out increased the accuracy of fire, the reliability of the functioning of the mechanisms of weapons and increase the service life. The AK-12 uses automation with a long stroke of the gas piston and a rotary shutter, the bolt group and the trigger mechanism were significantly improved in comparison with the AK-74. The weapon is equipped with a new telescopic plastic butt, folding in both directions and adjustable in length and height of the cheek. The central axis of the barrel channel AK-12 is in line with the butt, as is the case with AR-15 assault rifles, which reduces the recoil shoulder and ultimately increases the accuracy of fire.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1">
		<text>AK-12 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1_descr">
		<text>AK-12 - Kalashnikov assault rifle of 2016 model. It differs quite significantly in appearance and design of a number of important components from the previous version of the AK-12, shown in 2015. The design of the assault rifle has been revised both to eliminate a number of identified shortcomings and problems, and to improve its technological capabilities, taking into account the wishes of the military. This model is fitted with a tactical grip.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer Osprey</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn57">
		<text>FN Five-seveN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn57_descr">
		<text>The FN Five-seveN is a self-loading pistol designed and manufactured by the Belgian company Fabrique Nationale of Herstal. The name is a combination, on the one hand Five-seveN is “5-7” (5.7 is the caliber of the weapon, which is .224), and on the other, the first and last letter of the name, written in capital letters, is the abbreviation of Fabrique Nationale. Five-seveN is a full-sized self-loading pistol made according to the scheme with a half-free shutter, which uses 5.7 ? 28 mm cartridges. Polymers are widely used in its design, it is becoming increasingly popular in the civilian market, and the characteristics of the pistol also made it popular in special forces and other similar fields.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pp2000">
		<text>PP-2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pp2000_descr">
		<text>PP-2000 is a Russian 9-mm submachine gun developed by the design team of the Tula Instrument Design Bureau under the direction of V.P. Gryazev and A.G. Shipunova. PP-2000 is positioned as a weapon for law enforcement units operating in urban conditions, as well as a personal self-defense weapon for certain categories of military personnel. In 2006, serial production of PP-2000 for the Ministry of Internal Affairs of the Russian Federation began. The case is made of high strength plastic. The barrel channel is chrome-plated, it can also be equipped with a silencer, a collimator or an optical sight, a universal aiming strip is installed on the cover of the serial receiver.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vityaz">
		<text>PP-19-01 "Vityaz"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vityaz_descr">
		<text>A variation of PP-19 with a 30-charge sector magazine chambered for 9x19 mm, developed in 2004. It is used for arming patrol services, traffic police, intra-departmental security, and units of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of the Russian Federation.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90">
		<text>FN P90</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_descr">
		<text>FN P90 - Belgian submachine gun (personal self-defense weapon), developed in 1986-1987 by the company FN Herstal. It was developed primarily for tankers and drivers of military vehicles and vehicles. It has a progressive and comfortable ergonomic design. Specifically for the P90, a cartridge of the 5.7x28 mm SS190 type was developed, which has a high breakdown power and a low degree of rebound. The bullet of this cartridge develops a muzzle velocity of up to 715 m / s and is capable of breaking through a titanium / Kevlar armored vest that meets NATO CRISAT requirements up to 20 meters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .57</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bizon">
		<text>PP-19 "Bizon"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bizon_descr">
		<text>In 1993, Kalashnikov and Dragunov (the younger ones) made the first version of a new submachine gun called the PP-19 Bizon. It was developed under the "Makarov" cartridge 9x18 (both standard and high-pulse, modernized). Its distinguishing feature is the presence of a screw (from the German "screw" - "snail") underbarrel magazine with a capacity of 64 rounds. The PP-19 automation is based on the recoil of the free shutter, the trigger mechanism is trigger, along with the fuse borrowed from the AK-74. Fire is conducted from a closed shutter, which increases the accuracy of single shots. On the original PP-19 model, sighting devices are installed that are identical to those on the AKS74U assault rifle.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil">
		<text>Galil AR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_custom">
		<text>Galil AR (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_modern">
		<text>Galil AR (modern)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_worn">
		<text>Galil AR (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_descr">
		<text>Galil is an Israeli assault rifle developed by designer Israel Galili on the basis of the Finnish assault rifle Valmet Rk 62, which, in turn, is a variant of the Kalashnikov assault rifle. From the point of view of the internal structure, Galil is similar to a Kalashnikov assault rifle except for the use of another cartridge. Automation works by removing part of the powder gases from the bore through a gas outlet drilled at an angle of 30 degrees back directly into the gas chamber. The gas piston is chrome plated. The shutter handle, unlike the Kalashnikov assault rifle, is bent up so that it can be used with both hands. On the left above the pistol grip there is an additional flag of the fuse-translator of the firing modes. The production of Galil automatic rifles for the Israeli army was discontinued in 2006, and in 2007 the Galil were finally removed from service with the IDF (some remained in service with the guard of honor and some non-military units).\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight Galil 4x (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44">
		<text>StG 44</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_new">
		<text>StG 44 (new)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_alt">
		<text>StG 44 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_old">
		<text>StG 44 (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_worn">
		<text>StG 44 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_descr">
		<text>German submachine gun developed during the Second World War. About 450 thousand units were produced. Among the machines of the modern type was the first development, mass-produced. From the submachine guns (PPSh, etc.), which were massively used in the Second World War, it was distinguished by the ability to conduct aimed fire at a significantly longer range, primarily due to the use of the so-called intermediate cartridge, more powerful, and with better ballistics than pistol cartridges used in submachine guns. In the Zone, this machine is popular among beginner stalkers and novice stalkers of all groups.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ZF4\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 7.62x39\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_worn_descr">
		<text>German submachine gun developed during the Second World War. About 450 thousand units were produced. Among the machines of the modern type was the first development, mass-produced. From the submachine guns (PPSh, etc.), which were massively used in the Second World War, it was distinguished by the ability to conduct aimed fire at a significantly longer range, primarily due to the use of the so-called intermediate cartridge, more powerful, and with better ballistics than pistol cartridges used in submachine guns. In the Zone, this machine is popular among beginner stalkers and novice stalkers of all groups.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ZF4\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr25">
		<text>SR-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr25_descr">
		<text>The SR-25 is a self-loading sniper rifle developed by Eugene Stoner in the 1990s based on the design of the AR-15 rifle. Over 60% of the details in the design of the rifle are interchangeable with the AR-15. SR-25 has gas exhaust automation. The receiver is made of aluminum alloy - of two parts that are interconnected by transverse pins. The trigger mechanism makes it possible to fire single shots. The SR-25 rifle turned out to be quite successful, it provided high accuracy and therefore became popular both among civilian shooters in the USA and among police snipers. In the nineties, a variant of this rifle complete with an optical sight and a quick-detachable silencer of the same company was adopted by the US Navy Special Operations Forces under the designation Mark 11 Model 0 (Mk.11 Mod.0) sniper rifle.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer SR-25\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m60">
		<text>M60</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m60_descr">
		<text>M60 - an American unified machine gun, developed in the postwar years and adopted by the Army and Marine Corps in 1957. For design flaws and appearance received the nickname English. the pig - "pig." Despite the fact that the process of ousting the M60 with more advanced machine guns, such as the Belgian-designed M240, began in the 1980s, these weapons are still produced and are widely used, albeit primarily in the “second roles”. In terms of design, it was mainly a hybrid of two German-developed systems of the Second World War period - an automatic rifle FG-42 (automatic reloading with a gas engine) and a MG 42 machine gun (tape drive).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m249">
		<text>M249 SAW</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m249_descr">
		<text>M249 SAW - a variant of the FN Minimi light machine gun for the US Army 5.56? 45 mm caliber manufactured by FN Herstal (Belgium), mass production began in the 1980s. The machine gun entered the service in the armed forces of several countries, among them: Australia, Belgium, Canada, France, Greece, Spain, Italy, Indonesia, Malaysia, New Zealand, Thailand, Sweden, the United Kingdom and the United States of America (M249 SAW). Weapons are currently manufactured at FN Herstal factories.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan">
		<text>AN-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_camo">
		<text>AN-94 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_worn">
		<text>AN-94 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74">
		<text>AK-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_modern">
		<text>AK-74 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_worn">
		<text>AK-74 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_rusty">
		<text>AK-74 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dynamo_hand_name">
		<text>Portable Hand Generator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dynamo_hand_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]The device is a home-made portable generator with a manual drive. It is based on a single-phase asynchronous motor, from some old electrical appliance. The generated voltage passes through a step-down transformer to a rectifier assembled on Soviet D242 diodes to the Portable Power Unit. Self-excitation of the generator occurs due to the capacitor connected to the auxiliary winding of the motor. The charge is carried out by rotating the rotor through a worm gear at a nominal speed of 1300-1500 rpm. The device is equipped with an American ammeter, manufactured by WESTON ELECTRICAL INSTRUMENT. Due to its design, it has a rather large weight, but is still very much appreciated in the Zone. Some craftsmen can modify this device.\n \n%c[default]SPECIFICATIONS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rated engine power 40W\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] the life of the motor and gear bearings is limited\n%c[0,153,255,255]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_eot">
		<text>AK-74 «Eotech»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_duty">
		<text>AK-74M (Duty camouflage)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_camo">
		<text>AK-74M (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_custom">
		<text>AK-74M (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_worn">
		<text>AK-74M (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74">
		<text>AKS-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_worn">
		<text>AKS-74 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_rusty">
		<text>AKS-74 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak101">
		<text>AK-101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak101_camo">
		<text>AK-101 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak102">
		<text>AK-102</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103">
		<text>AK-103</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103_camo">
		<text>AK-103 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak104">
		<text>AK-104</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u">
		<text>AKS-74U</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_custom">
		<text>AKS-74U (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_worn">
		<text>AKS-74U (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_rusty">
		<text>AKS-74U (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_snag">
		<text>AKS-74U Snag</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta">
		<text>Beretta 92F</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_camo">
		<text>Beretta 92F (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_modern">
		<text>Beretta 92FS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_alt">
		<text>Beretta 92FS (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_worn">
		<text>Beretta 92F (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_rusty">
		<text>Beretta 92F (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16">
		<text>TOZ-66 (sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_alt">
		<text>TOZ-66 (enhanced sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_worn">
		<text>TOZ-66 (worn sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_rusty">
		<text>TOZ-66 (rusty sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_descr">
		<text>When you need an inexpensive short-range weapon that will be effective and lethal, many novice stalkers resort to sawing off the buttstock and barrels on the easy-to-acquire TOZ-66 double-barrel. This makes the gun light and maneuverable, but at the expense of accuracy and range.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full">
		<text>TOZ-66</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_alt">
		<text>TOZ-66 (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_worn">
		<text>TOZ-66 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_rusty">
		<text>TOZ-66 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_descr">
		<text>As a powerful weapon that every stalker can afford, the TOZ-66 is reliable and efficient. However, it is a large and bulky hunting gun, so many stalkers prefer to spend their blood money on a modern gun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_duplet">
		<text>Duplet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_duplet_descr">
		<text>This is an amazing and reliable weapon made by an unknown master in the Zone. Despite the shortened barrel, it has good lethal force and a good firing range, while maintaining good accuracy. It shows itself very well against mutants, in capable hands it is able to fill up a boar with a couple of shots. It feels very comfortable in the hands, and the scrolling butt can be adjusted to a convenient distance. There is no opportunity to put any sights, but this is not a hindrance for a seasoned hunter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_izh43">
		<text>IZh-43</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_izh43_short">
		<text>IZh-43 (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_izh43_descr">
		<text>IZh-43 - Smooth-bore double-barreled hunting rifle with a horizontal arrangement of the barrel block, connected in the breech by clutch, and the length of the connection of the trunks is carried out by the lower and aiming bars. The intra-shotgun, internal triggers are made in a monoblock with strikers, and have a rebound. In the process of upgrading the gun, the hammer with the strikers began to be carried out separately. The gun has modifications with external devices for cocking and smooth descent of the mainsprings, made in the form of external false skin. For other options with two triggers, there is the possibility of a smooth descent of the trigger from the combat cock by means of a fuse. In addition, there is a model with one trigger. There are no interceptors, a safety mechanism with automatic inclusion during a platoon blocks the sear and the triggers. The coil springs are twisted cylindrical. The gun is available with or without selective type ejectors. The trunks have constant muzzle constrictions and interchangeable chokes, for different purposes of application. The magnitude of the constant constriction is standard - a full choke and pay, except for .410 caliber rifles, and IZH-43 barrels with 76 mm chamber (Magnum) can have a cylindrical drill. The barrel unit is locked by sliding the locking bar on two barreled hooks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41">
		<text>PPSh-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_new">
		<text>PPSh-41 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_rednew">
		<text>PPSh-41 (new)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_old">
		<text>PPSh-41 (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_worn">
		<text>PPSh-41 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_descr">
		<text>A submachine gun developed by the Soviet designer Georgy Shpagin, adopted in 1941 and actively used in the Great Patriotic War, as well as in many armed conflicts of the post-war period. In the USSR, it was withdrawn from service in 1951 and replaced by a Kalashnikov assault rifle, but after that it was still used for a long time by various armies or armed groups around the world, for example, in the wars in Korea and Vietnam, and from recent conflicts on both Afghan and Iraq.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_worn_descr">
		<text>A submachine gun developed by the Soviet designer Georgy Shpagin, adopted in 1941 and actively used in the Great Patriotic War, as well as in many armed conflicts of the post-war period. In the USSR, it was withdrawn from service in 1951 and replaced by a Kalashnikov assault rifle, but after that it was still used for a long time by various armies or armed groups around the world, for example, in the wars in Korea and Vietnam, and from recent conflicts on both Afghan and Iraq.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] unable to attach silencer\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133">
		<text>MP-133</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_worn">
		<text>MP-133 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_rusty">
		<text>MP-133 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_descr">
		<text>MP-133 - Russian smoothbore gun, which is used for various types of hunting, sports shooting, security and self-defense. The gun was developed on the basis of the IZH-81 gun and has been mass-produced by the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant since 2000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153">
		<text>MP-153</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_worn">
		<text>MP-153 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_rusty">
		<text>MP-153 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_descr">
		<text>MP-153 is a Russian self-loading smoothbore shotgun, popularly called "murka", which is used for various types of hunting, sport shooting, law enforcement and self-defense. It is developed and produced in series at the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant (MP index means Mechanical Plant-Mechanical Plant). The shotgun is fitted with automatic bolt action: after the last cartridge is fired, the bolt stops at the rearmost position, which simplifies and speeds up the subsequent reloading and signals to the shooter about spent ammunition. The MP-153 rifles are quite popular in Russia, due to their affordable price and good reliability and survivability. The disadvantages of the gun are sometimes attributed to its slightly higher weight than its competitors.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_duty">
		<text>Colt M1911 (Duty camouflage)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_merc">
		<text>Colt M1911 (Mercenare camouflage)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_camo">
		<text>Colt M1911 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_custom">
		<text>Colt M1911 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_modern">
		<text>Colt M1911 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_alt">
		<text>Colt M1911 (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_new">
		<text>Colt M1911 (new)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_worn">
		<text>Colt M1911 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_rusty">
		<text>Colt M1911 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt_kimber">
		<text>Colt «Kimber Desert Warrior»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45">
		<text>FNP-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45_custom">
		<text>FNP-45 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45_worn">
		<text>FNP-45 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45">
		<text>FNX-45 «Tactical»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_custom">
		<text>FNX-45 «Tactical» (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_alt">
		<text>FNX-45 «Tactical» (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75">
		<text>CZ-75</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_custom">
		<text>CZ-75 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_auto">
		<text>CZ-75 Automatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_worn">
		<text>CZ-75 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock">
		<text>Glock 19</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_custom">
		<text>Glock 19 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_modern">
		<text>Glock 19 (Gen.3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_worn">
		<text>Glock 19 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_18">
		<text>Glock 18c (Gen.4)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_grach">
		<text>MP-443 "Grach"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_grach_worn">
		<text>MP-443 "Grach" (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle">
		<text>Desert Eagle .357 Caliber</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_custom">
		<text>Desert Eagle .357 Caliber (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_modern">
		<text>Desert Eagle .357 Caliber (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_worn">
		<text>Desert Eagle .357 Caliber (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_descr">
		<text>Desert Eagle is the world's most popular large-caliber pistol, gaining great fame for its size, power and ability to add technical accessories and optics to the body. A super weapon designed specifically for the 0.357 Magnum cartridge to compete with revolvers of the same caliber for long-range sport shooting. Developed by the American company Magnum Research, the Desert Eagle uses a gas-operated mechanism normally used in rifles. This allows the gun to use much larger caliber bullets than in traditional semiautomatic pistols. The disadvantages of this weapon include its considerable size and heavy weight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble">
		<text>Desert Eagle .45 ACP «Steppe Eagle»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_descr">
		<text>Desert Eagle .45 ACP is a more powerful version of the world's most popular large-caliber pistol, which has achieved great fame for its size, power and ability to add technical accessories and optics to the body. Developed by the American company Magnum Research, the Desert Eagle uses a gas-operated mechanism normally used in rifles. This allows the gun to use much larger caliber bullets than in traditional semiautomatic pistols. The disadvantages of this gun include its considerable size and heavy weight. All components on this barrel are perfectly tuned to achieve the highest accuracy for a pistol of this type, and thanks to the integrated muzzle compensator the recoil was significantly reduced. This weapon was brought to the Zone by stalker Logan Williams. Disguised as a journalist-photographer, he managed to reach the center of Pripyat alone. His fate is currently unknown, but it is rumored that he works as an informant for many secret agencies about the Exclusion Zone.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] collimator scope Delta Sight (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000">
		<text>FN F2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_camo">
		<text>FN F2000 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_custom">
		<text>FN F2000 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_worn">
		<text>FN F2000 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_nimble">
		<text>FN F2000 EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_famas">
		<text>FAMAS F1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_famas_descr">
		<text>FAMAS - an assault rifle developed by the MAS arms factory in Saint-Etienne) is a 5.56 mm French assault rifle with a bullpup layout. The unofficial name is "cleler." A lot of “orders” were made by the mercenary Hog, holding this rifle in his hands.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_famas_g2">
		<text>FAMAS G2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_famas_g2_descr">
		<text>The FAMAS G2 rifle, developed in 1994, differs from its FAMAS F1 prototype mainly in the store’s receiver that meets NATO standards for stores from the American M16 assault rifle with a different magazine catch device. Another, most noticeable externally, difference is the handle bracket for protecting the shooter's leading hand, instead of the usual trigger guard, similar to the Austrian AUG rifle. The G2 rifle was adopted by the French Navy and Navy special forces in 1995. It has some of the best continuous combat features of all rifles in the Zone.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer for caliber 5.56x45\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal">
		<text>FN FAL</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_descr">
		<text>FN FAL - NATO firearms manufactured in Belgium by Fabrique Nationale de Herstal. One of the most recognized and widely used automatic rifles. FN FAL was originally developed for 7.92x33mm interim rifle, which was used by Germans during World War II, then prototypes were developed for .280 British cartridge. Later it was converted to NATO 7.62x51mm cartridge, which was adopted as a single cartridge for NATO countries. Because of its prevalence and widespread usage among the militaries of many NATO and first world countries during the Cold War, it received the title "The right arm of the Free World"..\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, C-more Railway Tactical, EOTech, ELCAN SpecterDR\n \n\n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] Silencer NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnc">
		<text>FN FNC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnc_descr">
		<text>FN FNC (Fabrique Nationale Carabine - FN carbine) is a Belgian assault rifle created by the Fabrique Nationale de Herstal weapons company to replace the obsolete FN FAL, after failing with the first version of the weapon under a low-pulse 5.56 mm NATO FN CAL cartridge. The rifle is very rare , in the zone there are no more than 2-3 pieces, where they got it, that is still a mystery.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_far15">
		<text>FAR-15 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_far15_descr">
		<text>Modified by Fulton Armory, the AR-15 rifle has better parts, a telescopic stock and a modified flame arrester. Forest camouflage is applied to this sample.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[255,1,255,255] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, PN23 \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203 \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] integrated silencer</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2">
		<text>M16A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_descr">
		<text>The M16A2 assault rifle is a variant of the M16A1 rifle, adapted for the SS109 / M855 cartridge. Differences from M16A1 are as follows: a hardened barrel with a 1: 7 rifling pitch, improved sights, spaced up to 800 m, a new forend and a butt made of impact-resistant polyamide, replacing the continuous fire mode with a regime with a cut-off queue after 3 shots (armed with the marine hull Infantry received the option M16A2 with the possibility of continuous fire), a new arrester with slots only in the upper part (which compensated for the withdrawal of weapons up). The new rifle began to be equipped with light plastic stores for 30 rounds.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mosin">
		<text>Mosin rifle arr. 1891/30</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mosin_rusty">
		<text>Mosin rifle arr. 1891/30 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mosin_descr">
		<text>Lightly frayed Mosin rifle. 7.62mm Mosin rifle arr. 1891/30 was produced in the period from 1930 to 1945 as a standard weapon of the Soviet infantry. It was also successfully used during the Great Patriotic War as a sniper with an installed 4-fold PE optical sight or 3.5-fold PU.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116]• %c[default] sight PU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40">
		<text>SVT-40</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_modern">
		<text>SVT-40 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_worn">
		<text>SVT-40 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_rusty">
		<text>SVT-40 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_descr">
		<text>The 7.62mm self-loading rifle of the Tokarev system of the 1940 model was adopted by the Red Army to replace the 7.62 mm sniper rifle of the 1891/30 model. in the year 1940. The rifle works on the principle of the removal of gases from the bore with a short stroke of the gas piston. Locking is carried out by skewing the shutter in a vertical plane. The bed is compound. Trigger mechanism - trigger. The fuse locks the trigger. SVT-40 sniper rifles were widely used mainly for firing at remote targets that appear in the sniper's field of vision for a short time.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116]• %c[default] Sight PU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_a545">
		<text>A-545</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_a545_descr">
		<text>A 5.45x39 mm automatic rifle, developed at the Kovrov Mechanical Plant under the leadership of Stanislav Ivanovich Koksharov, based on an automatic machine of the Konstantinovna system (SA-006). The design uses a scheme with balanced automation based on a gas engine, which allows more controlled automatic fire. In small batches, these weapons were manufactured for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. It differs from AEK971 with a retractable butt.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech, Racurs PM, Trijicon TARS101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971">
		<text>AEK-971</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971_camo">
		<text>AEK-971 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971_worn">
		<text>AEK-971 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971_descr">
		<text>A 5.45x39 mm automatic machine developed at the Kovrov Mechanical Plant under the leadership of Stanislav Ivanovich Koksharov based on an automatic machine of the Konstantinov system (SA-006). The design uses a scheme with balanced automation based on a gas engine, which allows more controlled automatic fire. In small batches, these weapons were manufactured for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971_camo_descr">
		<text>A 5.45x39 mm automatic rifle, developed at the Kovrov Mechanical Plant under the leadership of Stanislav Ivanovich Koksharov, based on an automatic machine of the Konstantinov system (SA-006). The design uses a scheme with balanced automation based on a gas engine, which allows more controlled automatic fire. In small batches, these weapons were manufactured for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. Specifically, this model is painted in light beige with red stains, belongs to the group "Debt". Some mechanisms were manually enumerated or replaced with more reliable ones, the parts were fitted tightly to each other, as a result of which the pressure inside the barrel increased, and with it the muzzle velocity of the bullet.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk">
		<text>RPK</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk_worn">
		<text>RPK (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk_descr">
		<text>7.62mm Kalashnikov light machine gun (RPK, GRAU Index - 6P2) is a Soviet light machine gun based on the AKM assault rifle. Adopted by the Soviet army in 1961. He replaced the Degtyarev light machine gun, as preferred from the point of view of unification with other adopted small arms. The RPK light machine gun was adopted by the armies of more than 20 countries. Some countries produce versions or copies. For example, in Yugoslavia machine guns of the “Kalashnikov system” 72B1 were produced under the cartridge 7.62x39, which differed in the finned part of the barrel length, and 72AV1, which had a metal butt.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74">
		<text>RPK-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_worn">
		<text>RPK-74 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_descr">
		<text>A light machine gun developed in the mid-seventies to replace the RPK machine gun with a cartridge of 7.62x39 mm as part of the transition to a small arms system with a low-pulse cartridge of 5.45x39 mm. It is built on the basis of the AK-74 assault rifle, but has a store with a larger capacity.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vsk94">
		<text>VSK-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vsk94_worn">
		<text>VSK-94 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vsk94_descr">
		<text>The VSK-94 silent sniper rifle was created in the Tula KBP (Instrument Design Bureau) on the basis of the small-sized 9A-91 assault rifle as a cheaper alternative to the 9mm VSS Vintorez special sniper rifle.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer for 9A-91/VSK-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks">
		<text>SKS-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_modern">
		<text>SKS-45 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_worn">
		<text>SKS-45 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_descr">
		<text>The Soviet self-loading carbine designed by Sergei Simonov was adopted in 1949. Replaced in the early 1950s at the front line of military service with an AK automatic, it remained in reserve for decades and is still used as a ceremonial and ceremonial weapon.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight PU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type63">
		<text>Type 63</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type63_descr">
		<text>Type 63 - a Chinese automatic rifle based on the SCS to replace the Type 56 self-loading carbine. The locking mechanism was borrowed from the Type 56 assault rifle (licensed version of the AK). Receiver - milled (for weapons of early release) or stamped (for late release). Instead of a non-removable SKS store, sectorial stores with 20 or 30 rounds of ammunition are used, however, the possibility of equipping an empty magazine from clips without separation from weapons remained. There was an opportunity to shoot in bursts. Discontinued by the PLA in 1978 due to low efficiency.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight PU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98">
		<text>Karabiner 98 «Kurz»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_descr">
		<text>During World War II, a number of Karabiner 98k rifles with good accuracy were selected and equipped with a PO4x34 optical sight. These rifles were used by Nazi Germany as sniper rifles. In skilled hands, they had an effective firing range of up to 1000 meters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight PO4x34n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO (after modernization)\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ksvk">
		<text>KSVK</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ksvk_descr">
		<text>KSVK is a Russian large-caliber sniper rifle created by the team of designers of the V. A. Degtyarev factory in Kovrov based on the SVN-98 rifle. It is not a self-loading large-caliber magazine weapon, arranged according to the bullpup scheme. The barrel is locked with a longitudinally sliding rotary bolt, powered from a detachable box magazine with 5 rounds. The rifle is equipped with a standard side bar for mounting sights and can be equipped with various day and night sights. In addition, the rifle has open sights as a reserve. Folding bipods are located under the barrel on a special bracket, a powerful muzzle brake-compensator is located on the barrel, the butt is equipped with a wooden pad under the cheek and a rubber recoil pad-shock absorber. \n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight POSP 8x42D (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ash12">
		<text>ASh-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ash12_descr">
		<text>ASh-12 is a Russian large-caliber assault machine, created at TsKIB SOO for the needs of special forces of the FSB of Russia along with a VSSK sniper rifle. It is a weapon-cartridge complex, since a new large-caliber cartridge 12.7x55 mm SC-130 was developed for it at TsKIB SOO.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, C-MORE, EOTech\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wpn_kriss_name">
		<text>KRISS Vector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wpn_kriss_descr">
		<text>KRISS Vector is a submachine gun developed by Transformational Defense Industries. It uses a semi-free shutter system that directs the slide-movable slide group downward at a large angle. This system is called Kriss Super V. The main task of the designers of this weapon was to achieve the highest possible accuracy in bursts using .45 ACP rounds, which have a high stopping effect on the bullet, but at the same time minimize the dimensions and total weight of the submachine gun. Engineers at Transformational Defense Industries, Inc. (TDI) decided to use the patents of the French designer Renaud Kerbrat to achieve their goals. Tests of prototypes of this weapon were launched in 2005. The test results showed that when firing from a TDI KRISS Super V submachine gun, the tossing up of weapons when firing in line is insignificant, which ensures high accuracy of automatic fire and excellent controllability of the weapon during firing. In these parameters, the TDI KRISS Super V submachine gun is significantly superior to such samples as the German 11.43 mm HK UMP45 submachine gun.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS:\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g43">
		<text>Gewehr 43</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g43_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]Gewehr 43 is a German 7.9-mm self-loading rifle from World War II, which is a modification of the earlier Gewehr 41 rifle with a modified exhaust system, similar to that of the Soviet SVT-40 rifle. Equipped with a ZF-4 optical sight, this is a fairly effective sniper rifle of the time.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight ZF-41\n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_garand">
		<text>M1 Garand</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_garand_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]M1 Garand - an American self-loading rifle from the Second World War. The M1 Garand rifle became the world's 4th self-loading rifle, adopted for service and the first adopted as the main infantry weapon. Reliable and accurate, it served the US forces in World War II and the war in Korea. General Patton once called this rifle "the greatest warfare ever created." Garand is still popular in the civilian weapons market. The rifle mechanism works on the principle of removal of powder gases through a transverse hole in the barrel wall. The gas piston is fixedly attached to the gate frame. The locking of the shutter by turning occurs when the shutter is rotated around the longitudinal axis and two shutter protrusions enter into the grooves of the receiver. The trigger mechanism is a trigger, a fairly simple device, subsequently often copied in a more or less altered form, when disassembling a weapon, it was completely separated from the receiver. The rifle had a very successful and subsequently often replicated fuse in the form of a lever-flag in the front of the trigger guard, for arming, it moved backward, inside the trigger guard, so that the shooter could easily detect by touch whether the rifle is on guard. If necessary (for example, in the event of a misfire), the trigger could be cocked without “jerking” the shutter by pulling the back of the trigger guard down and forward behind the special ring - another evidence of how much attention the creators of the rifle paid to the convenience of handling weapons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m24">
		<text>M24 SWS «Green Dragon»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m24_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]The US Army sniper rifle M24 SWS (Sniper Weapon System - Sniper Weapon System) is based on the Remington 700 and is technically a magazine rifle with a longitudinally-sliding rotary bolt. It has a Leupold Ultra M3A 10x40 optical sight, a barrel made of specially treated stainless steel and a composite stock adjustable for the arrow.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sniper scope M24 (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_trg_sako">
		<text>Sako TRG-42</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_trg_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]The sniper rifle produced by the Finnish arms company SAKO. TRG-42 is not a modified version of the existing rifle, but a fully developed from scratch model. Consistently high accuracy and reliability made it popular in shooting competitions and military operations requiring sniper support.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska ES AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, Trijicon TARS101\n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590">
		<text>Mossberg 590A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590_worn">
		<text>Mossberg 590A1 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590_descr">
		<text>The Mossberg 590 smoothbore gun was created by the American company O.F. Mossberg & Sons in the mid-1970s as a “militarized” modification of their popular Mossberg 500 shotgun. Militarization included hardening a number of weapon parts, installing a barrel cover to protect hands from burns, a more resistant matte finish on the outer surfaces to protect against wear and corrosion, a metal trigger bracket - the base of the trigger unit. The Mossberg 590 is a magazine shotgun. Recharging with a movable fore-end (pump-action), a tubular non-replaceable magazine, located under the barrel. Locking the barrel - mounted on the shutter swinging larva for the breech. The receiver is made of aluminum alloy. The fuse is located on top of the back of the receiver and is equally convenient for righties and lefties.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590_camo">
		<text>Mossberg 590A1 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590_camo_descr">
		<text>The Mossberg 590 camouflaged shotgun. Militarization included hardening a number of weapon parts, installing a barrel cover to protect hands from burns, a more resistant matte finish on the outer surfaces to protect against wear and corrosion, a metal trigger guard - the base of the trigger unit. The Mossberg 590 is a magazine shotgun. Recharging with a movable fore-end (pump-action), a tubular non-replaceable magazine, located under the barrel. Locking the barrel - mounted on the shutter swinging larva for the breech. The receiver is made of aluminum alloy. The fuse is located on top of the back of the receiver and is equally convenient for righties and lefties. The weapon is camouflaged.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4">
		<text>M4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_worn">
		<text>M4 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_descr">
		<text>An assault rifle created in the USA on the basis of M16A2 originally for arming crews of combat vehicles and equipment calculations. Despite this, the US Special Operations Command (US SOCOM) accepted this machine as a single unit for all American special operations forces. At present, the entire US Army is switching over to it, since the greater convenience of a shortened carbine in modern conditions, when most of the army are motorized infantry, crews of military vehicles and auxiliary troops, is a very serious advantage. The main differences between M4 and M16A2 are a shorter barrel and a retractable telescopic butt.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1">
		<text>M4A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_freedom">
		<text>M4A1 (modified)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_camo">
		<text>M4A1 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_custom">
		<text>M4A1 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_worn">
		<text>M4A1 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_descr">
		<text>In 1996, by order of special operations forces based on the M16A3 rifle, a similar M4A1 carbine was developed, characterized by a return to fully automatic fire instead of a fire mode with a cut-off of 3 shots. The M4A1 modification, in addition to a short barrel and a telescopic stock, received a removable carrying handle and, accordingly, a replaceable sight (optical, collimator or night sights can be installed). From a technical point of view, the models M4 and M4A1 almost do not differ from the corresponding variants of the M16A2 and M16A3 rifles.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m14">
		<text>M14 EBR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m14_descr">
		<text>The Mk 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle, an “advanced combat rifle,” is an American Marxman rifle created by special operations of the US Navy based on the M14 rifle. Used by a number of special forces of the Navy, including SEAL. The main differences from the M14: a new bed (developed by Smith Enterprises), a telescopic butt, a pistol grip, several Picatinny rails and some “commercial” components, for example, a new precision barrel and gas cylinder.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 7.62\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Aimpoint, AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech, Coyote JH-406, Trijicon TARS101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16">
		<text>M16</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16_worn">
		<text>M16 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16_descr">
		<text>M16 (the official designation is Rifle, Caliber 5.56 mm, M16) is an American automatic rifle of 5.56 mm caliber, developed on the basis of the AR-15 rifle and adopted in the 1960s. In 1964, the M16 rifle was officially adopted, replacing the M14. In 1966, all American units in Vietnam armed with a new rifle. The rifle proved to be an extremely unreliable type of small arms. In general, it should be recognized that by the beginning of the 1970s, the M16 rifle was a full-fledged combat weapon with a number of significant advantages (well, of course, it also had drawbacks). Compared to the main enemy of the M16 on the world stage - the Kalashnikov assault rifle (AKM), the M16 had greater accuracy and accuracy in firing single shots, was more comfortable and convenient to use. On the other hand, the M16 required much more thorough care, better ammunition. In reliability under especially difficult conditions (pollution, dusting), the AKM also exceeded the M16. M16 and its variants to date remain the main weapon of the American infantry. This is one of the most common models of small arms in the world - more than 8 million copies have been produced.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp412">
		<text>MP-412 Rex</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp412_descr">
		<text>MP-412 Rex is a Russian-made revolver chambered for .357 Smith end Wesson Magnum (9x33 mm) and .38 Smith end Wesson Special (9.1x29 mm). Designed at the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant in the late 1990s. Designed for export (REX - Revolver for Export), but did not go into mass production. This new IzhMekh revolver is distinguished by two main features - an edging frame in the style of Smith-Wesson of the late XIX - early XX century, and a polymer frame, more precisely - its lower part together with a handle. The upper part of the frame holding the barrel is steel. The revolver has a switchable ejector, in the on state it ejects spent cartridges from the drum when the frame is opened (when the ejector is off, the cartridges only partially extend from the drum).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz65">
		<text>Skorpion vz.65</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz65_camo">
		<text>Skorpion vz.65 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz65_worn">
		<text>Skorpion vz.65 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz65_rusty">
		<text>Skorpion vz.65 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz65_descr">
		<text>Skorpion - Czechoslovak automatic pistol, was developed to arm tankers, signalmen and military personnel of other specialties. Scorpio was adopted by Czechoslovakia in 1961 (hence the designation vz.61 - vzor 61, that is, the 1961 model). Option vz.65 changed to 9x18mm PM cartridge, which is very common in the Zone, so this weapon can be found very often.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz65_rusty_descr">
		<text>The rusted Skorpion vz.65, judging by the look of it, was poorly looked after. Scorpio - Czechoslovakian automatic pistol, was developed to arm tankers, signalmen and military personnel of other specialties. Scorpio was adopted by Czechoslovakia in 1961 (hence the designation vz.61 - vzor 61, that is, the 1961 model). This variation of vz.65 changed to 9x18mm PM cartridge, which is very common in the Zone, so this weapon can be found very often.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45">
		<text>HK UMP 45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_custom">
		<text>HK UMP 45 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_worn">
		<text>HK UMP 45 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_descr">
		<text>The UMP submachine gun (Universal Machinen Pistole - a universal submachine gun) was developed in addition to the rather expensive MP5 as a cheaper and somewhat more modern version and was introduced in 1996. With .45 ACP cartridges, it has a higher stopping power, but also a stronger recoil. Because of this, for better control of automatic fire, the rate of fire was significantly reduced compared to the MP5.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18">
		<text>GSh-18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_custom">
		<text>GSh-18 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_worn">
		<text>GSH-18 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_descr">
		<text>Russian pistol, developed in the late 1990s at the Tula Instrument Design Bureau. The name was given by the first letters of the names of the designers under whose guidance it was designed: Vasily Petrovich Gryazev and Arkady Georgievich Shipunov, and the number "18", which means the capacity of the store. Serially produced since 2001, it is offered for export. In 2000, the GSH-18 was adopted by the special forces of the Ministry of Justice of the Russian Federation, in 2001 - the weapons of special forces and certain categories of employees of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of the Russian Federation. In 2003, according to the results of the competition for a new army pistol capable of replacing the Makarov pistol in service, it was adopted by the Russian army. With armor-piercing cartridges 7N21 and 7N31 it is capable of piercing an 8-mm steel sheet at a distance of 20 meters.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak">
		<text>AK</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks">
		<text>AKS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm">
		<text>AKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_worn">
		<text>AKM (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms">
		<text>AKMS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_worn">
		<text>AKMS (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak_descr">
		<text>The 7.62mm Kalashnikov assault rifle (AK) is an assault rifle adopted by the USSR in 1949. AK and its modifications are the most common small arms in the world. According to available estimates, this type (including licensed and non-licensed copies, as well as third-party developments based on AK) includes up to 1/5 of all small arms firearms available on Earth.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] installation of sights is not possible due to the lack of dovetail mounts\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks_descr">
		<text>AKS (GRAU Index - 56-A-212M) - AK variant with a folding metal butt, intended for the airborne troops. It was adopted simultaneously with AK. Originally produced with a stamped receiver, and since 1951 - milled due to the high percentage of marriage during stamping.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] installation of sights is not possible due to the lack of dovetail mounts\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_descr">
		<text>The AKM (Kalashnikov upgraded) is an upgraded version of the AKM assault rifle. Although it was replaced in 1970 by the AK-74 in the Soviet army, the AKM remains the most widely used version in the world.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_descr">
		<text>AKM variant with folding buttstock. The buttstock mounting system was changed in relation to the AKS (folding down to the receiver). This modification was designed specifically for paratroopers.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s">
		<text>Saiga-12S</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_worn">
		<text>Saiga-12S (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_descr">
		<text>“Saiga-12S” is a shotgun version with a folding plastic butt, a fire control handle (like an AK assault rifle) and a hunting type forearm. Barrel length 580 or 680 mm. Sights - the front sight and the rear sight (or an adjustable sighting strip on special order) are located above the gas outlet pipe.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12">
		<text>Vepr-12 "Hammer"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12_descr">
		<text>Vepr-12 "Hammer" is a Russian smooth-bore self-loading carbine developed on the basis of the design of the Kalashnikov light machine gun. Designed for hunting, sporting events (usually for practical shooting in the open class), self-defense, as well as use as a service weapon. It is a direct competitor to the Saiga-12 series guns. Vepr-12 smoothbore guns inherited the general layout and device of the RPK light machine gun, with a gas vent mechanism and locking by turning the bolt, however, the bolt group and the receiver were redesigned taking into account the use of rifle cartridges, and the trigger mechanism was deprived of auto descent.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12">
		<text>AA-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_custom">
		<text>AA-12 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_camo">
		<text>AA-12 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_descr">
		<text>AA-12 (Auto Assault-12) - automatic shotgun - shotgun, created by Maxwell Atchisson on the basis of earlier development Atchisson Assault Shotgun. The main difference between AA-12 and AAS is the use of gas exhaust automation, which is typical for machine guns, automatic rifles and machine guns, due to the possibility of using more powerful cartridges. Also, the design of the trigger and receiver, completely made with the butt and forend, was changed. Like its predecessor, the shutter rolls back to the butt. The new receiver consists of left and right halves, fastened to each other with pins. The translator of firing modes is located near the trigger and allows firing in single or continuous bursts. A special feature of the gun is the “recoil momentum accumulation”, similar to the Ultimax 100 machine gun. The essence of this solution is the interaction of two return springs, stretching the recoil momentum in time. Later, using the ideas of Atchisson in South Korea, the USAS-12 automatic shotgun was developed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_wa2000">
		<text>Walther WA 2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_wa2000_descr">
		<text>WA2000 (Walther Automat 2000) - a sniper rifle developed by the Walther arms concern. The rifle is made according to the “bullpup” scheme, which made it possible to preserve the barrel length characteristic of sniper rifles, but to reduce the total length of the weapon. WA-2000 is a self-loading rifle, the automation of which operates due to the removal of powder gases from the bore. A total of 176 rifles were fired (where it came from in the Zone is another question).\n \n %c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] integrated sight Schmidt and Bender 2,5-10x56</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tt33">
		<text>TT-33</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tt33_modern">
		<text>TT-33 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tt33_worn">
		<text>TT-33 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tt33_rusty">
		<text>TT-33 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wpn_tt33_descr">
		<text>The cult Soviet TT-33 pistol is an improved version of the TT-30 semi-automatic pistol, developed in 1930 to replace the obsolete revolver of the Nagan system arr. 1895 year. Despite the fact that the production of the TT-33 in Russia continued from 1933 to 1954, some copies are still in service and are assembled in Third World countries. The TT pistol is distinguished by its simplicity of design and, therefore, the low cost of production and ease of maintenance. Atypical for pistols, a very powerful cartridge provides an unusually high penetrating ability and muzzle energy of about 500 J.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33">
		<text>OTs-33 "Pernach"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33_worn">
		<text>OTs-33 "Pernach" (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33_rusty">
		<text>OTs-33 "Pernach" (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33_descr">
		<text>The OC-33 pistol was developed in the mid-1990s at the TsKIB SOO (Central Design Bureau of Sports and Hunting Arms) under the leadership of I.Ya. Stechkin to replace the outdated and long discontinued APS pistol design of the same author. Currently, in connection with the inclusion of TsKIB SOO into the Tula Instrument Design Bureau, the production and promotion of OTs-33 is carried out by KBP. In small quantities, the OC-33 is in service with various units of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of the Russian Federation. Compared to the Stechkin APS pistol, the OTs-33 is distinguished by improved characteristics, simpler design and more convenient handling. It is possible to install PBS and other accessories.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer APS (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: DeltaPoint</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33_rusty_descr">
		<text>The OC-33 pistol was developed in the mid-1990s at TsKIB SOO (Central Design Bureau of Sports and Hunting Arms) under the guidance of I.Ya. Stechkin to replace the outdated and long discontinued APS pistol design of the same author. Currently, in connection with the inclusion of TsKIB SOO into the Tula Instrument Design Bureau, the KBP is engaged in the production and promotion of OC-33. In small quantities, the OC-33 is in service with various units of the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. Compared to the Stechkin APS pistol, the OTs-33 is characterized by improved characteristics, a simpler design and more convenient to handle. It is possible to install PBS and other accessories.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105">
		<text>AK-105</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_descr">
		<text>Compact Kalashnikov assault rifle "Sotoy" series, designed to replace the AKS-74U in the units of the Russian army and law enforcement agencies. It is a modification of the AK-74M and differs from it by a shortened barrel and a flame arrester. The machine is made with a folding butt. Butt, mag, forend, barrel and pistol grip are made of plastic and have high impact resistance and resistance to external influences. The use of protective coatings provides high corrosion resistance of metal parts. The AK-105 has a side rail for mounting optical and night sights.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak109">
		<text>AK-109</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak109_descr">
		<text>Aleksandrov-Kalashnikov AK-109 assault rifles (7.62x39mm) was developed at the Izhevsk Machine-Building Plant based on the AK103 assault rifle. They are distinguished by the presence of balanced automation, also used in the AL-7 and AEK-971 models. Balanced automation significantly improves the accuracy of firing bursts from unstable positions, in comparison with the AK74M - by 15-20%. The AK-109 has a side bar for mounting optical and night sights.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1">
		<text>G3 SG1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1_worn">
		<text>G3 SG1 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza">
		<text>OTs-14-4A "Groza"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_descr">
		<text>The automatic grenade launcher system, 70% unified with automatic machines of the AKS-74U type (the main differences are the caliber 9x39 mm, the layout of the bullpup and wider possibilities for modernization). Designed for arming rapid response units. We greatly appreciate the military and stalkers for the ability to reliably hit an enemy protected by body armor or located in a shelter. It can be assembled in 4 different configurations, depending on the combat mission. The version of the assault rifle common in the Zone is equipped with the GP-25 grenade launcher.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight PO4x34, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_tactical">
		<text>OTs-14-2A "Groza" tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_tactical_descr">
		<text>Tactical automatic grenade launcher system, 70% unified with automatic machines such as AKS-74U. Designed for arming rapid response units. We really appreciate the military and stalkers for the ability to reliably hit an enemy protected by body armor or located in a shelter. It can be assembled in 4 different configurations, depending on the combat mission. This modification is equipped with a caliber 5.45x39mm, equipped with a silencer and tactical handle.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, PO4x34\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] 5.45x39mm integrated silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_nimble">
		<text>OTs-14-1A "Groza-1"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_nimble_descr">
		<text>One of the options for the advanced OTs-14-4A. In the "Groza-1" version, the rate of fire, flatness and capacity of the store were improved thanks to the use of a lighter cartridge of 7.62x39 mm caliber. This type of machine was produced only in small pilot batches for special units of the Ministry of Internal Affairs.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight PO4x34\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa">
		<text>Browning Hi-Power</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_alt">
		<text>Browning Hi-Power (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_worn">
		<text>Browning Hi-Power (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_rusty">
		<text>Browning Hi-Power (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_descr">
		<text>A modified model of the gun of the first half of the 20th century, which is as reliable, accurate and powerful as the original model. This model has gained a reputation as one of the best pistols of the 20th century and is very popular among stalkers.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_rusty_descr">
		<text>A rusted Browning pistol, but still just as reliable, accurate and powerful. This model has gained a reputation as one of the best pistols of the 20th century and is very popular among stalkers.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis">
		<text>OTs-02 “Kiparis”</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis_worn">
		<text>OTs-02 “Kiparis” (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis_descr">
		<text>OTs-02 “Kiparis” - a submachine gun developed in 1972 by order of the Ministry of Defense of the USSR (OKR “Shrub”) by the designers of TsKIB SOO of the city of Tula N. M. Afanasyev, D. P. Pleshkov and N V. Trukhachev. The layout was based on the layout of the Czechoslovak Scorpion Vz.61 submachine gun of the 1961 model. Automation OTs-02 "Kiparis" works due to the release of a free shutter. Trigger trigger mechanism allows a single and automatic fire. The shot is fired with a closed shutter, which increases the accuracy of the fire. Sights of the open type, consist of a front sight with a namushnik and an adjustable rear sight. Magazine box, with the arrangement of cartridges in two rows. To increase the stability of the weapon, a folding butt is used, which in the stowed position folds over the receiver. The cartridge cases are thrown up and back.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23">
		<text>KS-23M "Drozd"</text>
	</string>   
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_descr">
		<text>The carbine KS 23M "Drozd" (Special carbine Special 23 mm Modernized) was developed for arming the police and internal troops of Russia. The reloading mechanism works like a pump-action shotgun from a longitudinally sliding fore-end fixedly connected to the bolt. Cartridges are fed from a tubular magazine with four cartridges located under the barrel. The barrel channel is rifled; when fired, it is locked by turning the shutter. The pistol grip and forend are made of black plastic.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_custom">
		<text>MP5A3 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_alt">
		<text>MP5A3 (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_worn">
		<text>MP5A3 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_nimble">
		<text>MP5A3 «Frasier»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5">
		<text>MP5A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd">
		<text>MP5SD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_custom">
		<text>MP5SD (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_new">
		<text>MP5SD (new)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_worn">
		<text>MP5SD (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_descr">
		<text>The MP5A3 is a variant of the MP5 equipped with a sliding metal butt. This submachine gun is deservedly very popular due to its reliability, ease of use and high firing accuracy. Adopted by the army and police units of many countries, he appeared on the black market and eventually reached the Zone.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_nimble_descr">
		<text>A prototype submachine gun based on the HK MP5A3 model. Designed as the next generation, it is ahead of its predecessor due to its higher caliber, rate of fire and accuracy.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer Gemtech (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_descr">
		<text>The MP5SD submachine gun was developed based on the MP5A2 design for use by special army and police units. The MP5SD submachine gun is manufactured in versions with a permanent stock - MP5SD2 and folding - MP5SD3, or even without a stock - MP5SD4. This weapon differs from conventional MP5 in the presence of an integrated silencer. Shooting is carried out with standard 9mm Parabellum cartridges, which have a supersonic muzzle velocity. In order to reduce the initial velocity to a subsonic level, there are 30 holes in the barrel walls that divert part of the powder gases into the expansion chamber of the muffler.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] integrated PBS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp7">
		<text>H&K MP7 A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp7_descr">
		<text>H&K MP7 A1 is a submachine gun developed in the early 2000s by the German company Heckler & Koch. According to the classification adopted by NATO, it is assigned to a new class of firearms - personal defense weapons (English Personal Defense Weapon, PDW). MP7 is configured as a small submachine gun, the magazine is inserted into the pistol grip, the stock is folding, telescopic, in front there is a folding additional handle. MP7 automation is built according to the scheme with a gas engine with a short stroke of the gas piston, locking is carried out by turning the shutter. Some features of the HK G36 machine are used in the design, for example, the widespread use of polymeric materials, similar automation, and the USM design.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, EOTech, C-MORE, AC11090, Coyote JH-406\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb">
		<text>PB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_custom">
		<text>PB (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_worn">
		<text>PB (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_descr">
		<text>Adopted in 1967, the silent PB pistol (GRAU 6P9 index) was developed on the basis of the Makarov pistol for arming army reconnaissance groups, as well as personnel of the KGB of the USSR. The gun uses an integrated silencer, which reduces the speed of the bullet to subsonic.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 6P9</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps">
		<text>APS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_worn">
		<text>APS (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_descr">
		<text>\n%c[0,170,170,170]A pistol developed in the late 1940s and early 1950s by designer I. Ya. Stechkin and adopted by the Armed Forces of the USSR in 1951, simultaneously with a Makarov pistol. APS is designed to equip officers directly involved in hostilities, as well as for soldiers and sergeants of some special units.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer APS (after modernization)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta">
		<text>Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_camo">
		<text>Armsel Protecta (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_custom">
		<text>Armsel Protecta (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_worn">
		<text>Armsel Protecta (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_rusty">
		<text>Armsel Protecta (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_aim">
		<text>Armsel Protecta (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_aim_descr">
		<text>Smoothbore combat shotgun revolving scheme, designed to provide high firepower to paramilitary units. Today, already outdated in comparison with the domestic Saiga-12 and the American AA-12, in the 1980s, the Protecta shotgun was a revolutionary weapon. The main advantages are the large capacity of the store and the practical rate of fire, but the fee for this is the impressive dimensions and weight of the weapon, coupled with a low reload speed. It is rare in the Zone, and is mainly used for cleaning enclosed spaces. This model is deeply modernized, the parts are tightly fitted to each other, the energy of the shot due to increased pressure in the channels has increased significantly. Demonstrates good accuracy and lethality at the expense of rate of fire, the collimator of the Swedish company Aimpoint AB is also installed on the model.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Reflex Sight «Aimpoint» (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usas12">
		<text>USAS-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_nimble">
		<text>Armsel Protecta (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_nimble_descr">
		<text>Smoothbore combat shotgun revolving scheme, designed to provide high firepower to paramilitary units. Today, already outdated in comparison with the domestic Saiga-12 and the American AA-12, in the 1980s, the Protecta shotgun was a revolutionary weapon. The main advantages are the large capacity of the store and the practical rate of fire, but the fee for this is the impressive dimensions and weight of the weapon, coupled with a low reload speed. It is rare in the Zone, and is mainly used for cleaning enclosed spaces. This modified sample, according to some information, belonged to a tankman called Tank, but little is known about this stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rg6">
		<text>RG-6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rg6_descr">
		<text>A revolver-type grenade launcher is used to increase the infantry firepower in urban combat. It was used in some local conflicts, for example, the war in Chechnya. The front loading drum chambers are formed by six rifled barrels identical to those used in under-barrel grenade launchers. Designed to fight the enemy in shelters and firing on areas, it is also useful when attacking well-guarded objects or in battle with especially tenacious creatures.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m79">
		<text>M79</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m79_descr">
		<text>M79 - a single-shot 40-mm grenade launcher, adopted by the US Army in 1961. Developed in the period 1951-1961 by the American corporation Springfield Arsenal (English Springfield Armory). The unofficial name is “elephant gun”.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_soc94">
		<text>SOK-94 "Vepr"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_soc94_descr">
		<text>The self-loading rifled carbine SOK-94 "Vepr" was developed on the basis of the 7.62 mm RPK light machine gun in 1995 by the design team of the Molot machine-building plant. Designed for commercial and amateur hunting for large and medium animals. It is not common in the zone, because of the ease of use and the availability of a cartridge, it can become a good weapon for a beginner stalker.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm">
		<text>PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_descr">
		<text>Manual modification of an army machine gun with tape power. Despite the high mass and unsatisfactory accuracy of the battle, I found myself quite widely used in the Zone. It is mainly used to suppress an enemy that is superior in numbers and when clearing the logs of mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zulus">
		<text>Zulu's PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zulus_descr">
		<text>This machine gun belonged to Zulus. The peculiarity of this sample lies in the particularly reliable design of the return mechanism. Modifications increased the mass of weapons, although for the previous owner this was not a problem. A collimator sight is also installed on the machine gun, which allows you to quickly aim the target at the desired target.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] reflex sight Kobra EKP-1C-03 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp">
		<text>PKP "Pecheneg"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_descr">
		<text>7.62mm machine gun PKP "Pecheneg" (GRAU Index - 6P41) is the Russian single machine gun developed on the basis of PKM. Designed to engage enemy manpower, fire and vehicles, air targets. Designed by TsNIItochmash. The machine gun uses a system of forced air cooling of the barrel due to the energy of powder gases. An adjustable gas vent allows the operation of Pecheneg in any climatic conditions. The barrel has an external ribbing and is enclosed in a metal casing. Powder gases, leaving the trunk, create a rarefaction zone in the front of the casing. In the rear part of the casing, special ventilation windows are made. Thus, during firing along the barrel, cold air is continuously pumped. Constant barrel cooling reduces dispersion during firing and also increases barrel longevity. In general, Pecheneg retained up to 80% percent of the common parts with PCM (receiver with all the mechanisms, the machine), and the increase in fire efficiency was from 150% with fire from the machine to 250% with fire from the bipod (according to the developers).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpd">
		<text>RPD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpd_descr">
		<text>7.62mm Degtyarev light machine gun (RPD, GRAU Index - 56-P-327) is a Soviet light machine gun developed in 1944 with a cartridge of 7.62x39 mm. The RPD was one of the first weapons adopted for service under the cartridge of the 1943 model. From the beginning of the 1950s to the mid-1960s, it was the main weapon to support the separation level, and then gradually began to be replaced by the PKK, more preferred in terms of unification. However, the RPD is still in the warehouses of army reserves. Like many other types of Soviet weapons, RPDs were widely exported to countries friendly to the USSR, and also produced abroad, for example, in the PRC under the designation Type 56. Some US firms, such as DC Arms, produce upgraded RPDs. Modernization includes a telescopic butt, forend with Picatinny rails, ergonomic bipod, plastic handle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7">
		<text>RPG-7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220">
		<text>SIG P220</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_custom">
		<text>SIG P220 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_worn">
		<text>SIG P220 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_rusty">
		<text>SIG P220 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_nimble">
		<text>SIG P220 «Alpine»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_nimble_descr">
		<text>Unique SIG P220 model. It was released by a small batch on the order of an unknown special forces. This modification is characterized by a barrel made of especially strong steel and a polymer barrel casing.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3">
		<text>HK G3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3_worn">
		<text>HK G3 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3_descr">
		<text>HK G3 (German: Gewehr 3 - Rifle 3) - German automatic rifle, adopted by the army of Germany in 1959. G3 is built on the basis of automation with a half-free shutter having a L-shaped. The cocking handle and the front elongated end of the shutter are located in a cylindrical casing installed above the barrel, resembling a gas outlet pipe. The rifle is characterized by high reliability and ease of use, however, it has a number of small parts in the design that may be lost during incomplete disassembly. An additional advantage of the G3 over its competitors - the Belgian FN FAL and the American M14 - was a lower price, due to the large number of stamped (and later plastic) parts, as well as a simple design .. In 1997, it was replaced by a 5.56 mm NATO automatic machine HK G36.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar">
		<text>FN SCAR-L</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_custom">
		<text>FN SCAR-L (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_new">
		<text>FN SCAR-L (new)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_worn">
		<text>FN SCAR-L (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_descr">
		<text>FN SCAR (Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle - a special assault rifle for special operations forces) is a weapon system developed by the American division of the Belgian company FN Herstal to participate in the competition for the creation of a new machine for USSOCOM fighters in 2004.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar20m">
		<text>FN SCAR SSR Mk.20</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar20m_descr">
		<text>The rifle was developed by the American division of the Belgian company Fabrique National Herstal. At its core, this type of weapon is nothing more than more accurate and devoid of the ability to conduct automatic fire of the FN SCAR-H Mk.17 rifle. Traders, as always, were surprised where they came from such a rare weapon.</text>
    	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550">
		<text>SIG 550</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_camo">
		<text>SIG 550 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_custom">
		<text>SIG 550 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_worn">
		<text>SIG 550 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_rusty">
		<text>SIG 550 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_descr">
		<text>Representative of a relatively new assault rifle family. Due to its high reliability, combat accuracy and ease of use, it is one of the best weapons of this class. It is equipped with a side-folding butt of a skeletal type and light aluminum bipod on the bottom of the plastic forearm. It is rare in the Zone and costs a lot of money. Usually seasoned stalkers specially order it for themselves.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_rusty_descr">
		<text>Representative of a relatively new assault rifle family. Due to its high reliability, combat accuracy and ease of use, it is one of the best weapons of this class. It is equipped with a side-folding butt of a skeletal type and light aluminum bipod on the bottom of the plastic forearm. It is rare in the Zone and costs a lot of money. Usually seasoned stalkers specially order it for themselves.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_sniper">
		<text>SG 550-S «Sniper»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_sniper_descr">
		<text>A sniper version of the popular Swiss automatic rifle. The SG 550-S is the middle ground between a sniper rifle and an assault rifle, having the strengths of both types of weapons. On the other hand, it also suffers from flaws, such as insufficient stopping power and accuracy (for a sniper rifle) and lack of automatic fire. Nevertheless, it remains one of the favorite weapons in the ChEZ among mercenaries and stalkers-masters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight Kahles ZF95 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_strelok">
		<text>SG 550 (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_strelok_descr">
		<text>Although this instance of the assault rifle was obviously not released yesterday, it is clear that the previous owner handled the weapons carefully. The rifle is completely moved and its details are carefully adjusted to each other, which allowed to slightly increase the lethal force. The letter “C” and 16 small crosses are neatly carved on the butt. It must be made to order by a stalker named Shooter.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552">
		<text>SG 552 «Commando»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_worn">
		<text>SG 552 «Commando» (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_descr">
		<text>A compact version of the SIG SG 550 assault rifle, with a 226 mm barrel, designed for special police units. Unlike the SG 550, the return spring is behind the bolt frame and acts directly on it, and not on the gas piston rod. The machine has a modified flame extinguisher and can be equipped with Picatinny rails for installing additional accessories.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ace21">
		<text>Galil ACE-21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ace21_descr">
		<text>The family of assault rifles (assault, automatic rifles) Galil ACE is designed and manufactured by the Israeli weapons company IWI Ltd. The Galil ACE family of assault rifles is based on the design of the Galil assault rifle, which in turn is a development of the AK Kalashnikov assault rifle. The Galil ACE assault rifle line focuses on the ergonomics of the weapon, the convenience of its use and completing with additional accessories, as well as its flexibility of use - the Galil ACE line of weapons includes the three most common types of ammunition in the world (5.56x45 NATO, 7.62x39 M43 and 7.62x51 NATO ), in various options for barrel length. The main differences from its predecessors were the transfer of the shutter cocking handle to the left side of the weapon (now you can conveniently turn the shutter with your left hand without taking your right hand from the fire control handle), a bolt delay appeared in the design of the weapon, the machine received Picatinny rail-type integral rails for installing optics and accessories as well as an adjustable telescopic butt.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sv98">
		<text>SV-98</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sv98_descr">
		<text>SV-98 (GRAU Index - 6V10) - Russian store sniper rifle, created in 1998-2000. a team of designers led by Vladimir Stronsky and mass-produced by the Izhmash concern. SV-98 is designed to defeat the appearing, moving, open and unmasked, unprotected and equipped with individual armor protection of enemy personnel at ranges up to 1000 m. The rifle is in service and is used by the Ministry of Internal Affairs units.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer KZRZP\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska ES AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, PN23 "Saracin", ELCAN SpecterDR, Trijicon TARS101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd">
		<text>SVD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_worn">
		<text>SVD (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_rusty">
		<text>SVD (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_descr">
		<text>Originally intended for infantry snipers in every Soviet infantry squad, the SVD was not the weapon of a separate specialized sniper brigade. Being relatively easy for a sniper rifle, well balanced and having a semi-automatic shooting mode, the accuracy of the SVD shows good, but not outstanding results. Effective firing range up to 800 meters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer KZRZP (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_rusty_descr">
		<text>Originally intended for infantry snipers in every Soviet infantry squad, the SVD was not the weapon of a separate specialized sniper brigade. Being relatively easy for a sniper rifle, well balanced and having a semi-automatic shooting mode, the accuracy of the SVD shows good, but not outstanding results. Effective firing range up to 800 meters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_nimble">
		<text>SVD "Lynx"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_nimble_descr">
		<text>A variant of the SVD unit assembly sniper rifle. Outwardly, it does not differ much from the standard sample, but in practice it demonstrates a much more impressive ratio of accuracy and lethal force.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight 1P59 Hyperon (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer KZRZP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_s">
		<text>SVD-S</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_s_descr">
		<text>SVD-S variant SVD for the airborne troops with a folding butt and a shortened but thickened barrel; established in 1991, adopted in 1995, entered the Zone in small batches.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer KZRZP\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] integrated bipods C-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu">
		<text>OTS-03 SVU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_worn">
		<text>OTS-03 SVU (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_descr">
		<text>The OTs-O3 SVU is a modernized version of the SVD sniper rifle, originally developed for the Airborne Troops of the USSR, but did not go into production. The rifle was later adopted by Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs already in early 1990s. Designed in compact bullpup configuration, the SVU is fitted with powerful muzzle brake-compensator, which reduces recoil and loudness of the shot.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer SVU (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_nimble">
		<text>OTS-03 SVU-A</text>
	</string>S
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_nimble_descr">
		<text>Shortened sniper rifle with increased rate of fire is the most compact version of the family of SVU / SVD rifles. Its unique feature is an automatic firing mode, added on demand of the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. Although this weapon is not intended for close combat, automatic mode of fire is useful in extreme cases when sniper is detected by enemy. The downside of the reduced size is the reduced accuracy and speed of the bullet. To compensate for the strong recoil during automatic firing, the SVU-A is equipped with an integrated muffler silencer, which is also an effective muzzle brake.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer SVU (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1">
		<text>L96A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1_worn">
		<text>L96A1 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1_descr">
		<text>Accuracy International L96A1 Tross / Arctic Warfare is a British-made sniper rifle, developed at Accuracy International. It was adopted by British Army in mid-1980s as the L96 rifle. The rifle is fitted with Leupold Mark 4 fixed x10 telescope sight. This rifle is technically a 5-round (.308 caliber) rotary bolt action rifle. The cartridges are fired from 5 or 10 rounds box magazines. This rifle is a high-precision, high-end tactical rifle, which has proven itself in the most difficult conditions in various armies of the world. Depending on the cartridge and barrel, it has a range of bullets from 0.4 to 0.7 MOA. In other words, with some cartridges, the AW base model stacks five shots from 100 meters in a circle of 11.6 to 20.3 mm.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska ES AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, ELCAN SpecterDR, PN23, PKS-07, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] silencer NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1m">
		<text>L96 AWSM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1m_descr">
		<text>Accuracy International L96A1 Tross / Arctic Warfare is a British-made sniper rifle, developed at Accuracy International. It was adopted by British Army in mid-1980s as the L96 rifle. The rifle is fitted with Leupold Mark 4 fixed x10 telescope sight. This rifle is technically a 5-round (.308 caliber) rotary bolt action rifle. The cartridges are fired from 5 or 10 rounds box magazines. This rifle is a high-precision, high-end tactical rifle, which has proven itself in the most difficult conditions in various armies of the world. Depending on the cartridge and barrel, bullets range from 0.4 to 0.7 MOA. In other words, with some cartridges, the AW base model stacks five shots from 100 meters in a circle from 11.6 to 20.3 mm. L96 AWSM is a variant of the AWS under .338 Lapua Magnum cartridge.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight Leupold Mark 4 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m98b">
		<text>Barrett M98B "Bravo"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m98b_descr">
		<text>The M98V sniper rifle was developed from scratch by American company Barrett Firearms. Using ".338 Lapua Magnum" cartridges, fed from detachable box magazine, the M98B provides impressive accuracy and excellent stopping power even at extreme range.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight Leupold Mark 4 (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer SR-25 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34">
		<text>TOZ-34</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_custom">
		<text>TOZ-34 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_worn">
		<text>TOZ-34 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_rusty">
		<text>TOZ-34 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez">
		<text>TOZ-34 (sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_custom">
		<text>TOZ-34 (custom sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_worn">
		<text>TOZ-34 (worn sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_rusty">
		<text>TOZ-34 (rusty sawn off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_descr">
		<text>TOZ-34 cutter, with sawn off barrels for better maneuverability. The TOZ-34 was developed by talented designers of Tula Arms Works N.I. Korovyakov and V.P. Ochnev in 1965. Affordable price, high killing power and the ability to fire from both barrels at the same time quickly made this gun popular among beginners on the outskirts of the Zone. It was especially effective against mutants due to its high kill power.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_descr">
		<text>The vertical hunting shotgun, TOZ-34, was developed by talented designers of Tula Arms Works N.I. Korovyakov and V.P. Ochnev in 1965. Affordable price, high killing power and the ability to fire from both barrels at the same time quickly made this gun popular among beginners on the outskirts of the Zone. It was especially effective against mutants due to its accuracy and kill power.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, Trijicon TARS101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_rusty_descr">
		<text>Rusty vertical rifle, TOZ-34 was developed by talented designers of Tula Arms Works N.I. Korovyakov and V.P. Ochnev in 1965. Affordable price, high killing power and the ability to fire from both barrels at the same time quickly made this gun popular among beginners on the outskirts of the Zone. It was especially effective against mutants due to its accuracy and kill power.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel">
		<text>Unidentified weapon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel_descr">
		<text>Unidentified weapon sample. Clearly defective - pressing the trigger does not produce any result. The specimen is heavy and definitely high-tech. Apparently, it's not a firearm. Most likely, it works with electromagnetic fields. One can only speculate what destructive potential it has.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp">
		<text>USP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_custom">
		<text>USP (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_alt">
		<text>USP (modified)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_worn">
		<text>USP (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_match">
		<text>USP «Match»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble">
		<text>USP "March"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_descr">
		<text>Heckler & Koch USP is a self-loading pistol developed by the German company Heckler & Koch. It was first introduced in 1993. It is designed for police and army use. It features high survivability and reliability, as well as good firing accuracy. Size of the weapon, even in compact version, is quite high, and its center of gravity is massive, making it somewhat difficult to carry in concealed position.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_match_descr">
		<text>The USP Match is a purely sporting version of the gun. In addition to the long barrel, it had a special load near the muzzle part of the pistol, to reduce the drop of the barrel. The barrel has a polygonal cut, and the triggerguard is equipped with adjustable trigger force. The barrel was removed from production and replaced by the USP Elite in 1999.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble_descr">
		<text>The USP Match is a purely sporting version of the gun. In addition to the long barrel, it had a special load near the muzzle part of the pistol, to reduce the drop of the barrel. The barrel has a polygonal cut, and the triggerguard is equipped with adjustable trigger force. The barrel was removed from production and replaced by the USP Elite in 1999. According to available information, once belonged to a mercenary nicknamed Volkodav.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vihr">
		<text>SR-3M "Vihr"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_9a91">
		<text>9A-91</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez">
		<text>VSS «Vintorez»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_alt">
		<text>VSS "Vintorez" (enhanced)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_worn">
		<text>VSS "Vintorez" (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_descr">
		<text>Developed at the same time as the Val rifle, the Vintorez special sniper rifle is intended for low-noise sniper shooting. It is mainly used by special forces for silent and covert operations. Special 9x39 SP-5 and SP-6 subsonic ammunition is used for firing.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer VSS (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_nimble">
		<text>VSS "Strike"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_nimble_descr">
		<text>A special version of the famous VSS sniper rifle. This model has been deeply modernized. The internal mechanism was replaced by an improved one, which led to an increase in the muzzle velocity of the bullet and firing accuracy. Thanks to this, the effective range is increased and the flatness of heavy subsonic cartridges is improved. \n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer VSS (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther">
		<text>Walther P99</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_custom">
		<text>Walther P99 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_worn">
		<text>Walther P99 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz194">
		<text>TOZ-194</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz194_worn">
		<text>TOZ-194 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz194_rusty">
		<text>TOZ-194 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz194_descr">
		<text>TOZ-194 is a Russian pump-action shotgun developed in the mid-1990s based on the design of the TOZ-94 shotgun. It is made at the Tula arms factory. The gun is not self-loading, reloading is carried out by a movable forearm. A tubular magazine is located under the barrel. Handguard and pistol grip plastic, no stock. The sight is open, not adjustable. The advantages of TOZ-194 compared to the base TOZ-94 are its great versatility and capacity of the store, smaller dimensions and weight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_descr">
		<text>Nikonov's assault rifle "Abakan" AN-94 model 1994 based on the Kalashnikov system. The main distinguishing feature of the AN-94 before the AK-74 from the point of view of combat use is the introduction of an additional fire mode in bursts of 2 rounds with a high rate of fire. This mode of fire provides high accuracy and accuracy of hits, since the recoil momentum begins to act on the shooter after both bullets have left the barrel of the weapon. Used by special forces operatives and duty fighters to defeat the enemy in bulletproof vests over a relatively long distance.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_camo_descr">
		<text>Nikonov's camouflaged assault rifle "Abakan" AN-94 model 1994 based on the Kalashnikov system. The main distinguishing feature of the AN-94 before the AK-74 from the point of view of combat use is the introduction of an additional fire mode in bursts of 2 rounds with a high rate of fire. This mode of fire provides high accuracy and accuracy of hits, since the recoil momentum begins to act on the shooter after both bullets have left the barrel of the weapon. Used by special forces operatives and duty fighters to defeat the enemy in bulletproof vests over a relatively long distance.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_descr">
		<text>5.45mm Kalashnikov assault rifle, developed in 1970 by designer M.T. Kalashnikov and adopted by the USSR armed forces in 1974. It is a further development of AKM. The development of the AK-74 is associated with the transition to a new small-pulse cartridge of 5.45x39mm.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_rusty_descr">
		<text>5.45mm Kalashnikov assault rifle, developed in 1970 by designer M.T. Kalashnikov and adopted by the USSR armed forces in 1974. It is a further development of AKM. The development of the AK-74 is associated with the transition to a new small-pulse cartridge 5.45x39mm.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_descr">
		<text>In the mid-1980s, the designers of the Izhevsk Machine-Building Plant developed several models of the A-60 and A-61 universal modified Kalashnikov assault rifles. On the basis of the A-60 and A-61, one of the successful versions of the 5.45 mm Kalashnikov AK-74M assault rifle was developed. The design of the AK-74M Kalashnikov assault rifle almost completely repeats the AK-74 scheme and has no fundamental differences from the point of view of the internal structure. Having retained all the best qualities of Kalashnikov assault rifles, he acquired a number of new ones that significantly improved his combat and operational characteristics. In general, the design of the AK-74M embodied the idea of ??a “universal” machine that replaced four models at once - AK-74, AK-74N, AKS-74 and AKS-74N.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_descr">
		<text>Being a more accurate and reliable machine than AKM, AK-74 is still used in most countries of the former USSR. The AKS-74 is equipped with a folding metal butt and is intended primarily for the air assault infantry. In the Zone, this is the main weapon of military stalkers and many loners.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer TGP-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_rusty_descr">
		<text>Being a more accurate and reliable machine than AKM, AK-74 is still used in most countries of the former USSR. The AKS-74 is equipped with a folding metal butt and is intended primarily for the air assault infantry. In the Zone, this is the main weapon of military stalkers and many loners.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", 1PN93 "Baby", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, NSPU, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak101_descr">
		<text>The Kalashnikov assault rifle of the "100 series" AK-101 (GRAU Index - 6P43) is an export modification of the standard Russian automatic machine AK-74M. The main (and practically the only) difference between the AK-101 and the AK-74M is the caliber - the 100th series assault rifle uses 5.56mm (5.56x45 NATO) rounds of ammunition and the corresponding stores, the rest is identical.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer ATG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak102_descr">
		<text>The compact Kalashnikov assault rifle of the "100 series" AK-102 is based on the AK-101 full-size assault rifle, based on the AK-74M standard Russian army assault rifle. The main difference from the “full-sized” fellow was a shortened barrel with a special muzzle-flame damper and an altered reticle (having markings only up to 500 meters instead of 1000 for a full-sized sample). The assault rifle has a side-folding plastic butt and a standard bar located on the left side of the receiver for mounting optical sights.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer ATG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103_descr">
		<text>The Kalashnikov assault rifle of the "100 series" AK-103 (GRAU Index - 6P45) is an export modification of the standard Russian automatic machine AK-74M. The main (and practically the only) difference between the AK-103 and the AK-74M is the caliber - this 100th series assault rifle uses 7.62mm (7.62x39 M43) cartridges and corresponding stores (compatible with the stores of older AK / AKM assault rifles), otherwise the automata are identical.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Underbarrel grenade launcher GP-25 (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer ATG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_descr">
		<text>The compact Kalashnikov assault rifle of the "100 series" AK-104 is based on the AK-103 full-size assault rifle, based on the standard Russian-made assault rifle AK-74M. The main difference from the “full-sized” fellow was a shortened barrel with a special muzzle-flame damper and an altered aiming strip (having markings only up to 500 meters instead of 1000 for a full-sized sample). The assault rifle has a side-folding plastic butt and a standard bar located on the left side of the receiver for mounting optical sights.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer ATG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_descr">
		<text>The shortened machine gun AKS-74U was developed as the main weapon of Special Forces, Airborne Forces and special forces, as well as for crews of armored vehicles that require a compact, but at the same time powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is much more maneuverable in cramped spaces and vehicles than the full-sized AKS-74, however, a short barrel and a significantly lower muzzle velocity of the bullet lead to a small aiming range.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_snag_descr">
		<text>The shortened assault rifle AKS-74U was developed as the main weapon of Special Forces, Airborne Forces and special forces, as well as for armored vehicle crews that require a compact, but at the same time powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is much more maneuverable in cramped spaces and vehicles than the full-sized AKS-74, however, a short barrel and a significantly lower muzzle velocity of the bullet lead to a small aiming range. On this option, a magazine from RPK-74 for 45 rounds is installed.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Kobra EKP-1C-03 (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer PBS-4 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_rusty_descr">
		<text>The shortened machine gun AKS-74U was developed as the main weapon of Special Forces, Airborne Forces and special forces, as well as for crews of armored vehicles that require a compact, but at the same time powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is much more maneuverable in cramped spaces and vehicles than the full-sized AKS-74, however, a short barrel and a significantly lower muzzle velocity of the bullet lead to a small aiming range.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach sights\n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_rusty_descr">
		<text>M1911 was in service with the US military from 1911 to 1985. An incredibly reliable and durable gun that has been used for military, police and simple civil defense purposes around the world. It remains a fairly popular weapon to this day.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_descr">
		<text>M1911 was in service with the US military from 1911 to 1985. An incredibly reliable and durable gun that has been used for military, police and simple civil defense purposes around the world. It remains a fairly popular weapon to this day.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_duty_descr">
		<text>M1911 was in service with the US military from 1911 to 1985. An incredibly reliable and durable gun that has been used for military, police and simple civil defense purposes around the world. It remains a fairly popular weapon to this day. A distinctive feature of this sample is increased slaughter.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_merc_descr">
		<text>M1911 was in service with the US military from 1911 to 1985. An incredibly reliable and durable gun that has been used for military, police and simple civil defense purposes around the world. It remains a fairly popular weapon to this day. The gun has better accuracy and a more resource-intensive barrel compared to the usual M1911.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_camo_descr">
		<text>M1911 was in service with the US military from 1911 to 1985. An incredibly reliable and durable gun that has been used for military, police and simple civil defense purposes around the world. It remains a fairly popular weapon to this day. Specifically, this model of the gun is made in dark beige colors with red stains.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt_kimber_descr">
		<text>Enhanced Colt M1911A1 from Kimber. Automation works according to the pattern of using recoil with a short barrel stroke. The locking system is carried out using a descending barrel. Desert Warrior was created to conduct special operations of the US Marine Corps.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45_descr">
		<text>FN FNP45 is a self-loading pistol developed by FNH-USA (an American division of the Belgian company FN Herstal). The gun is built using recoil energy with a short barrel stroke. The barrel is locked with one combat ledge in the breech of the barrel through the window for ejecting sleeves in the bolt, the barrel is reduced during unlocking according to the Browning scheme, when the figured cut in the tide under the barrel interacts with a special steel insert in the frame. The frame of the gun is made of shockproof plastic, the shutter is made of stainless steel. In general, the gun is a combination of old, proven reliability and practicality, systems with the latest developments both in the field of design and in the materials and processing methods used.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_descr">
		<text>FNX family pistols are manufactured in the USA by FNH USA, the local division of the famous Belgian company FN Herstal. FN FNX pistols were developed in 2007-2009 to meet the requirements of the US Joint Combat Pistol Program to develop a new pistol for the US Armed Forces. This program was not successful, but the pistols created to meet its requirements were put into series for sale in the police and civilian arms markets in the United States and abroad. FN FNX uses automation with a short stroke of the barrel and its rigid locking by skewing the breech. Locking and unlocking occurs when the figured cutout in the tide under the barrel interacts with the insert of the weapon frame. The barrel engages with the bolt due to the interaction of the protrusion in its upper part with the window for ejecting cartridges.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] reflex sight FNX Tactical (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz52">
		<text>CZ 52</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz52_descr">
		<text>CZ vz.52 - self-loading pistol, developed in the early 1950s for the Czechoslovak army. The Cz52 pistol was developed by designer Jan Kratohvil together with his brother Yaroslav, employees of the Ceska zbrojovka Strakonice factory. Initially, the pistol was designed for the 9.19 mm Parabellum cartridge, but in the 1960s a decision was made to unify the ammunition in the Warsaw Treaty countries, as a result of which the pistol was redone for the 7.62x25mm cartridge. Automation works according to the pattern of using recoil with a short barrel stroke. The barrel channel is locked using two rollers and a locking slider located in the lower tide of the rear of the barrel and entering the internal recesses of the shutter-casing. Trigger mechanism - trigger type, single action, with a safety cocking trigger. On the left side of the frame there is a lever for the safety lock, which is also a lever for the safe descent of the trigger from the combat cock. The fuse has three positions. The lower one is “fire”, the upper one is the safe trigger release, and the middle one is the fuse. The built-in shutter latch locks the casing shutter in the extreme rear position after all cartridges are used up from the magazine. At the base of the trigger guard is a double-sided barrel lock. Sights consist of an unregulated front sight and a rear sight fixed in a dovetail groove, with the possibility of lateral amendments. On the bottom surface of the handle there is a magazine latch holding 8 rounds. \n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_auto_descr">
		<text>CZ-75 Auto - 1992 model, a fully automatic version with a barrel extended to 150 mm and the possibility of firing bursts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_descr">
		<text>The CZ 75 is a pistol developed in Czechoslovakia in 1975. It has become widespread throughout the world. Designed by the brothers Joseph and Frantisek Koucki in Ugorsky Brod. In 1977, mass production was launched. Automation works according to the pattern of using recoil with a short barrel stroke. Locking is carried out using the declining breech. The weapon has high firing accuracy due to the practically backlash-free movement of the shutter-casing, since the design of Charles Peter is used here - moving the shutter-casing not along the external but along the internal guides of the frame. Moreover, the guide grooves are made along the entire length of the frame, which makes the movement stable. It is very popular among various special services, both Czechoslovakia and other countries of the Warsaw Treaty, including the KGB of the USSR. This is due to the significantly higher combat and service and operational qualities of this weapon than the TT and full-time PM.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scorpion_evo3">
		<text>CZ Scorpion EVO 3 A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scorpion_evo3_descr">
		<text>CZ Scorpion EVO 3 A1 - a submachine gun designed in Slovakia under the name Laugo, manufactured in the Czech Republic by Ceska Zbrojovka Uhersky Brod. Serially produced since 2010. Scorpion Evo 3 works according to the usual scheme with a free shutter. Shooting is from a closed shutter, A1 has a shutter lag. Trigger trigger, allowing to fire in single, bursts with a cut-off of 3 rounds and continuous bursts. Translator of firing modes on both sides of the receiver. The receiver itself, the body of the trigger mechanism along with the pistol grip and forend are made of shockproof plastic. Butt folding and telescopic (adjustable in length). Below and on the side of the forend, as well as on top of the receiver are Picatinny rail. On the top bar are removable sights.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_descr">
		<text>Glock 19 is a self-loading pistol company Glock. It differs from the Glock 17 pistol in the shorter shutter-guard and pistol grip length, it has the same design as other Glock pistols (with the exception of the Glock 25 and Glock 28 pistols using a different automation principle - the principle of free shutter). Automation of the gun works on the principle of using recoil with a short course of the barrel, the bolt is unlocked when the barrel is skewed in the vertical plane due to the interaction of the figured groove in the tide of the breech of the barrel with the gun body. Glock 19 as well as other pistols of this manufacturer has high combat and operational qualities. Designed for the civilian arms market, as well as for arming various intelligence services and army officers, it has the firepower of a full-sized army weapon; currently the gun is used in the police, special units and armed forces of various countries of the world.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_18_descr">
		<text>Glock 18c is an Austrian-made Glock automatic pistol, chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum caliber. Glock 18 aroused the interest of police and military forces, but it did not gained the expected popularity, due to its low automatic fire efficiency, even in comparison with rather compact submachine guns. The Glock 18 inherited all the advantages of the basic Glock 17 pistol and is structurally very similar to it.[1] One of the differences is the fire mode selector lever at the left rear of the slide housing. In popular culture, samples as Glock 18 are often actually converted (with automatic fire capability) Glock 17s, usually with a 33-round magazine. The Glock 18 can easily be distinguished by the muzzle protruding outside the breech-cover, with an integrated reactive compensator that reduces the muzzle flap when firing. The 18C has the same muzzle protrusion and bore as the 17C. Sighting equipment is detachable and installed in cross-hole dovetail style mounts. Standard iron sights are non-adjustable, and include white or glow (tritium) dots for easy aiming in poor lighting conditions.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer GemTech (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_grach_descr">
		<text>Yarygin pistol "Grach" (GRAU Index - 6P35) is a self-loading pistol of Russian production. Developed by a team of designers led by V. A. Yarygin, mass production was mastered at the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant. In 1990, the USSR Ministry of Defense announced a competition for a new pistol, designed to replace the PM pistol, which is in service but does not fully meet modern requirements (Rook and Rook program "Grach"). In 1993, a pistol designed by Yarygin was presented to this competition. According to the test results, in 2000 the pistol (named MP-443 "Rook") became the winner of the competition. In 2003, under the name "Yarygin's 9-mm pistol" (PY), it was adopted by the Armed Forces of the Russian Federation. The Yarygin pistol is built on the basis of automation using recoil energy with a short rollback of the barrel and its tight locking. The shutter and frame of the gun are made of carbon steel, the barrel is made of stainless steel. In general, the PY is a fairly comfortable weapon, well balanced, has a fairly "pleasant" descent.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_descr">
		<text>This futuristic-looking weapon is a fully mass-produced Belgian assault rifle by FN Herstal. Despite the external bulkiness, it is characterized by high ergonomics, the convenience of firing in all modes and high reliability.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_nimble_descr">
		<text>This futuristic-looking weapon is a fully mass-produced Belgian assault rifle by FN Herstal. Despite the external bulkiness, it is characterized by high ergonomics, the convenience of firing in all modes and high reliability. On this model, the standard optical sight was replaced by an EOTech collimator, which significantly affected accuracy, but the weapon was clearly upgraded with a bias towards close combat due to an increase in the rate of fire.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] EOTech (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort">
		<text>Fort-17</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_worn">
		<text>Fort-17 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_descr">
		<text>Fort-17 - Ukrainian self-loading pistol chambered for 9x18 mm PM. Designed in the spring of 2004, produced by NPO Fort. “Fort-17” is a modification of the “Fort-12” pistol with a polymer frame made of impact-resistant polyamide reinforced with fiberglass, detachable by a grip on the handle (allowing the shooter to fit on the arm) and a picatinny mount under the gun barrel. The use of polymers made it possible to reduce weight, increase manufacturability and reduce the cost of production of the gun.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_rusty">
		<text>Fort-17 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_rusty_descr">
		<text>Fort-17 - Ukrainian self-loading pistol chambered for 9x18 mm PM. Designed in the spring of 2004, produced by NPO Fort. “Fort-17” is a modification of the “Fort-12” pistol with a polymer frame made of impact-resistant polyamide reinforced with fiberglass, detachable by a grip on the handle (allowing the shooter to fit on the arm) and a picatinny mount under the gun barrel. The use of polymers made it possible to reduce weight, increase manufacturability and reduce the cost of production of the gun.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort12">
		<text>Fort-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort12_descr">
		<text>Fort-12 - Ukrainian self-loading pistol chambered for 9x18 mm PM. Designed mainly for arming law enforcement and law enforcement agencies. It has the best combat accuracy compared to the PM, responsiveness and capacity of the store. Mainly falls into the Zone among the rejects widely implemented here. Nevertheless, it is in demand among stalkers because of the fairly high combat characteristics.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1_descr">
		<text>The G3 SG1 sniper rifle was developed by Heckler & Koch in 1973 specifically for the FRG army and is a modification of the G3A3 assault rifle. G3 SG1 were produced by finalizing the standard G3A3 samples which showed high accuracy in factory tests. The main feature of the G3 SG1 rifle, which provides an accurate shot, is a semi-free bolt circuit, the retreat of which is slowed down by the rollers. This circuit does not require a gas regulator and moving the piston back and forth. Previously in service with the armed forces of Germany and Italy. In addition, it was used by special forces of various countries, including the United States.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight G3 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1_modern_descr">
		<text>The G3 SG1 sniper rifle was developed by Heckler & Koch in 1973 specifically for the FRG army and is a modification of the G3A3 assault rifle. G3 SG1 were produced by finalizing the standard G3A3 samples which showed high accuracy in factory tests. The main feature of the G3 SG1 rifle, which provides an accurate shot, is a semi-free bolt circuit, the retreat of which is slowed down by the rollers. This circuit does not require a gas regulator and moving the piston back and forth. Previously in service with the armed forces of Germany and Italy. In addition, it was used by special forces of various countries, including the United States.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight G3 (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36">
		<text>G36</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_camo">
		<text>G36 (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_worn">
		<text>G36 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_descr">
		<text>The embodiment of new trends in Western-made automatic weapons: the mechanism is now based not on a half-free shutter, but on a short stroke of the gas piston. I must say, the changes clearly benefited: this assault rifle is a first-class example of modern weapons - lightweight, reliable and ergonomic.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Grenade launcher AG36</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_nimble">
		<text>G36 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_nimble_descr">
		<text>The embodiment of new trends in Western-made automatic weapons: the mechanism is now based not on a half-free shutter, but on a short stroke of the gas piston. I must say, the changes clearly benefited: this assault rifle is a first-class example of modern weapons - lightweight, reliable and ergonomic. This prototype has improved kill and camouflage.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Grenade launcher AG36</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k">
		<text>G36K</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k_descr">
		<text>HK G36K is a shortened carbine based on the G36 assault rifle, created to replace the obsolete G3, which was in service with the Bundeswehr. Rather reliable and technologically advanced, the G36 family of assault rifles is used by military, police and special forces in more than 30 countries.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight G36 (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k_worn">
		<text>G36K (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36c">
		<text>HK G36C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36c_descr">
		<text>Extremely shortened version of the German rifle G36. The rifle was developed in 1996 by the German arms company Heckler & Koch. Due to its compactness and maneuverability, for a long time it was used by a certain mercenary nicknamed Ara.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_xm8">
		<text>XM8</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_xm8_descr">
		<text>XM8 - a complex of small arms, developed jointly by the American arms company ATK (Alliant Techsystems) and the German company Heckler & Koch based on the HK G36 rifle. XM8 is designed primarily to replace the M16 and M4A1 assault rifles, having less weight and greater reliability. When using new cartridges with a lightweight composite metal-plastic sleeve, the new machine provided 20% mass savings compared to the M16. The start of production of this weapon was scheduled for approximately 2006. In 2004, machine guns passed extensive tests in the US armed forces, earning positive reviews. Despite this, in October 2005, the project was officially closed.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS:\n \n %c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] integrated sight XM8 \n %c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_descr">
		<text>The standard individual weapons of the armed forces of Great Britain. The L85 assault rifle in its original A1 version had many design flaws. The L85A2 version, upgraded by the German company Heckler & Koch, is characterized by increased reliability in a wide range of climatic factors and operating conditions.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] ACOG, Trijicon TARS101, EOTech, C-MORE, AC11090\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_modern">
		<text>L85A2 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_modern_descr">
		<text>Improved assault rifle L85A2, significantly improved the reliability of the design and increased rate of fire. The L85A2 version, upgraded by the German company Heckler & Koch, is characterized by increased reliability in a wide range of climatic factors and operating conditions.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] ACOG, Trijicon TARS101, EOTech, C-MORE, AC11090\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300">
		<text>LR-300 ML</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_camo">
		<text>LR-300 ML (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_custom">
		<text>LR-300 ML (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_worn">
		<text>LR-300 ML (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_descr">
		<text>A light assault rifle with an effective firing range of 300 meters, the LR-300ML is a new step in the development of the famous AR-15 family. In fact, the changes affected only the upper half of the receiver with the barrel, gas outlet unit and bolt group, resulting in increased ergonomics and reliability, and the mass, on the contrary, decreased. This rifle is highly accurate, although its high sensitivity to contamination makes it unsuitable for use in difficult conditions of the Zone.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska ES AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, PN23 "Saracin", ELCAN SpecterDR, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_rusty">
		<text>LR-300 ML (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_rusty_descr">
		<text>A light assault rifle with an effective firing range of 300 meters, the LR-300ML is a new step in the development of the famous AR-15 family. In fact, the changes affected only the upper half of the receiver with the barrel, gas outlet unit and bolt group, resulting in increased ergonomics and reliability, and the mass, on the contrary, decreased. This rifle is highly accurate, although its high sensitivity to contamination makes it unsuitable for use in difficult conditions of the Zone.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska ES AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, PN23 "Saracin", ELCAN SpecterDR, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203 (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk416">
		<text>HK416</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk416_descr">
		<text>HK416 is a German automatic rifle, created by Heckler & Koch on the basis of M4 carbine. Initially, the new weapon was supposed to be a replacement for the M4 or M16 rifle, but later it was replaced by the MK416 rifle. The name HK416 symbolizes the continuity of the M4 and M16 rifles. The receiver is made from aluminum alloy and the magazines are made from steel (standard M16 magazines can also be used). The barrel is hinged in the fore-end of the barrel. The barrel is made from Picatinny or Daniel Defense slats on the upper plane of the receiver, as well as on the four sides of the receiver's forend, so that a wide range of accessories can be used. Multi-position telescopic buttstock is similar in design to the M4. The gun shows high accuracy and pile-up shooting. Due to its high modularity and versatility, the HK416 can be adapted to any type of combat.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska ES AC11090, C-MORE, Coyote JH-406, EOTech, PN23 "Saracin", ELCAN SpecterDR, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	 <string id="st_wpn_hk417">
		<text>HK417</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk417_descr">
		<text>HK417 - 7.62mm automatic rifle, based on HK416 (5.56mm). The rifle features a modular design, similar to that of the M16 rifle, but features gas operated, short-stroke gas piston system, like the HK G36. The barrel is locked by rotary bolt action with 7 locking lugs. The controls and assembly/disassembly procedures are inherited from the M16, but the gas piston system is similar to the HK G36. It can be fired in single shots, or in continuous bursts. The barrel is cold forged and has threads for installing silencer or muzzle brake. The receiver is made from aluminum alloy. The barrel is telescopic and sliding. Polymer clear box magazines were specially designed for HK417, allowing the shooter to control ammunition consumption. Rifle caliber is 7.62x51 NATO. Another feature of the HK417 is the ability to quickly change the barrel by the user, using a minimum number of tools, thus achieving tactical flexibility of the weapon. The HK416/417 rifle has similar capabilities, as well as Belgian FN SCAR rifle. Single shot accuracy is about one corner minute with "sniper" barrel and corresponding cartridges.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech, Coyote JH-406, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ru556">
		<text>Ruger SR-556</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ru556_descr">
		<text>Ruger SR-556 is an American self-loading carbine manufactured by Sturm, Ruger & Company, Inc. The weapon was introduced in 2009 and became the first model of the Ruger AR-10 family. The next variant in this range was the Ruger SR-762 carbine with .308 cartridge[2]. This rifle is one of the few AR-15 rifles, which uses powder gas venting. Production ceased in January 2016 after introduction of the Takedown version with lightweight Keymod stock. The rifle is based on the patented AR-15 direct gas blowback mechanism, which operates in two stages and is opposed to the AR-15 direct gas blowback system. Powder gas venting is controlled by four-stage regulator. Several key parts - short stroke gas piston, gas regulator and bolt group - are chrome plated. Instead of the AR-15 gas piston, there is a built-in tab in the bolt. Flame arrester is similar to the AC-556 and Mini-14GB flame arresters.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: ACOG, AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech, Coyote JH-406, Trijicon TARS101\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tactical grip</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm">
		<text>PM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_custom">
		<text>PM (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_worn">
		<text>PM (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_rusty">
		<text>PM (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_descr">
		<text>The most common pistol in the area, a legacy of the Soviet era, the PM is one of the best representatives of the compact self-defense weapon class. It is small in size, extremely reliable, easy to use and maintain. Among its drawbacks are short range and accuracy of fire, low bullet efficiency, and (compared to modern pistols of the same class) quite large weight with insufficient magazine capacity.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 9mm (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm">
		<text>PMM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_descr">
		<text>The 9mm Makarov pistol is a modernized PMM (GRAU Index - 56-A-125M) - a Russian pistol developed in the early 1990s as part of the research and development theme "Grac". The pistol has a reinforced frame and increased bolt weight. The PMM pistol is equipped with spiral grooves, which allows to use 9x18mm PMM high pulsed cartridges for firing. When the gun is fired, the pressure of the powder gases presses the shell walls into three grooves on the chamber walls, holding the shell in the chamber until the bullet leaves the barrel and the pressure decreases, after which the shell is extracted and ejected. The maximum pressure in the channel of the gun barrel increased by 15% with a new cartridge, which slightly increased the recoil. 70 % of PMM pistol parts are interchangeable with PM pistol.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 9mm</text>
	</string>
	 <string id="st_wpn_pl15">
		<text>PL-15</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_descr">
		<text>Lebedev's pistol (PL-15) - developed by Russian self-loading pistol under the cartridge 9?19 mm Parabellum. The PL-15 is a short-stroke, recoil operated weapon that uses short-stroke inertia of the bolt, linked to the barrel. The bolt is unlocked by lowering the barrel by the curved tide below the barrel. The barrel channel is locked by hitch on the upper edge of the barrel when it is coupled to the ejection port in the bolt. Double action, curved, with concealed trigger and inertial striker. Self-propelled shots are fired in self-loading mode for each shot, with 4 kg of trigger force and 7 mm full stroke. In addition, a manual safety feature is provided, and the trigger is detachable from the trigger with trigger and has two flat levers on both sides of the weapon. Cartridge indicator in the chamber is made in the form of a pin, which protrudes from the rear end of the bolt, when cartridge is in the barrel. The bolt levers are reversible. The PL-15 pistol is fitted with extended threaded barrel for quick-release silencer.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm (after modification)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sight Leupold DeltaPoint</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_descr">
		<text>The smooth-bore revolver shotgun, designed to provide high firepower to paramilitary units. Today, the Protecta shotgun is already outdated in comparison with the domestic Saiga-12 and American AA-12 shotguns, and in 1980s it was a revolutionary weapon. Its main advantages are its large magazine capacity and practical speed of fire, but the price for it is impressive size and weight of the weapon, combined with low reload speed. It is rare in the Zone and is mainly used to clear closed spaces of mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usas12_descr">
		<text>The USAS-12 is an automatic shotgun developed by John Trevor in the late 1980s based on the ideas of another American designer, Maxwell Atchisson, who created the Atchisson Assault Shotgun. USAS-12 uses automation based on the removal of powder gases from the bore with locking the barrel by turning the shutter. As well as in AAS / AA-12, the plastic butt is made hollow so that the bolt group would roll back into it when shooting. This solution reduces the rate of fire and reduces recoil. To ensure "two-sidedness", the windows of the sleeve extractor, as well as cutouts for the cocking handle of the shutter, are available on both sides of the receiver. The three-position fuse-translator of the firing modes is similar to that of the M16 assault rifle. The receiver has an integrated carrying handle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7_descr">
		<text>The simplicity, strength, low cost and effectiveness of the RPG-7 made it the most popular recoilless anti-tank gun in the world. Currently, it is produced in various versions by nine countries and is in service with more than 40 countries of the world.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_descr">
		<text>Designed to arm the Swiss army, the SIG P220 became the basis for a whole family of pistols. These guns are of the highest quality workmanship, without compromising on strength and functionality. SIG P220 adopted by the army and police of Japan, Austria, France, Switzerland and several other countries.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer .45ACP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_rusty_descr">
		<text>Designed to arm the Swiss army, the SIG P220 became the basis for a whole family of pistols. These guns are of the highest quality workmanship, without compromising on strength and functionality. SIG P220 adopted by the army and police of Japan, Austria, France, Switzerland and several other countries.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington870">
		<text>Remington 870 "Trapper"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington870_descr">
		<text>The Remington 870 is an American shotgun, first introduced in 1950 by Remington Arms. Due to its characteristic reloading it is one of the most famous pump-action shotguns in the world. Available in various versions, it is suitable for military and police use, as well as for hunters and athletes, and in self-defense. It is with this gun that Fox went on his last chimera hunt, which proves that even an experienced hunter with a good weapon may not come back after meeting with chimera. The shotgun has high damage due to its chrome plating on the inside of the barrel.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] Sights: Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12">
		<text>SPAS-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_custom">
		<text>SPAS-12 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_worn">
		<text>SPAS-12 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_rusty">
		<text>SPAS-12 (rusty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_descr">
		<text>Smooth automatic special purpose shotgun with switchable firing modes, with open buttstock. Developed back in the second half of XX century, it continues to be used as a universal combat weapon by police and assault units of the army. It is distinguished by high reliability and tactical flexibility. Despite its large mass, sophisticated device and high price, it is quite popular in the Zone as an effective means to combat mutants. Mechanisms on this model are slightly upgraded, parts are tightly fitted to each other, thanks to this it was possible to significantly increase the killing of weapons, but do not forget about the weakened side of the weapon, the gaps in the channels decreased, and therefore the resource of the barrel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_nimble">
		<text>SPAS-12 (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_nimble_descr">
		<text>Smooth automatic special purpose shotgun with switchable firing modes. Developed back in the second half of XX century, it continues to be used as a universal combat weapon by police and assault units of the army. It is distinguished by high reliability and tactical flexibility. Despite its large mass, sophisticated device and high price, it is quite popular in the Zone as an effective means of fighting against mutants. Mechanisms on this model are slightly upgraded, parts are tightly fitted to each other, thanks to this it was possible to significantly increase the killing of weapons, but do not forget about the weakened side of the weapon, the gaps in the channels decreased, and therefore the resource of the barrel. Previously it belonged to the Ant.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val">
		<text>AC «Val»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_descr">
		<text>The special "Val" rifle is based on the silent VSS "Vintorez" sniper rifle. It was developed for arming special purpose units of the Soviet Army and the Ministry of Internal Affairs. The main purpose of the rifle is to effectively defeat the enemy, using modern personal protective equipment, without revealing the position of the shooter. Thanks to the integrated silencer and 9x39 cartridge with heavy sonic bullet, the sound of the shot and muzzle flame are minimized.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer VSS (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern">
		<text>AC «Val» (modernized)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_worn">
		<text>AC «Val» (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern_descr">
		<text>The special rifle "Val" is based on the silent VSS "Vintorez" sniper rifle. It was developed for arming special purpose units of the Soviet Army and the Ministry of Internal Affairs. The main purpose of the rifle is to effectively defeat the enemy, using modern personal protective equipment, without revealing the position of the shooter. Thanks to the integrated silencer and 9x39 cartridge with heavy sonic bullet, the sound of the shot and muzzle flame are minimized.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer VSS (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_grip">
		<text>AC «Val» (tactical)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_grip_descr">
		<text>The special rifle "Val" is based on the silent VSS "Vintorez" sniper rifle. It was developed for arming special purpose units of the Soviet Army and the Ministry of Internal Affairs. The main purpose of the rifle is to effectively defeat the enemy, using modern personal protective equipment, without revealing the position of the shooter. Thanks to the integrated silencer and 9x39 cartridge with heavy sonic bullet, the sound of the shot and muzzle flame are minimized.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer VSS (integrated)\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tactical grip (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vihr_descr">
		<text>SR-3M "Vikhr" is a compact Russian automatic rifle developed in Klimovsk TsNIITOCHMASH by designers A.D. Borisov and V.N. Levchenko in 1994. It was manufactured by designer A. I. Tashlykov and was launched into mass production in 1996. It is based on the silent automatic rifle AS "Val", with which it is unified in basic details, which has a positive impact on the production and operation of weapons. The SR-3 is similar to the AS "Val" in general: gas operated weapon and bolt locking with 6 locking lugs. The SR-3M was developed later, and features a silencer, metal magazines for 30 rounds, telescope and night sights, folding left frame buttstock (borrowed from AS "Val"), flag fuse, made on the type of SVD, and a new forend.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer SR-3M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_9a91_descr">
		<text>Small-size automatic carbine 9A-91 was developed in 1992 as a more technological analogue and competitor of SR-3 "Vortex" in Tula Instrument Design Bureau. Automatic carbine 9A-91 is based on discharge of powder gases from the barrel channel. It is locked by rotating the bolt with 4 locking lugs. The bolt is of the trigger type, and can be fired in single and continuous bursts. The bolt carrier is located at the left side of the receiver, above the trigger guard (in the upgraded version - at the right side of the receiver, as the telescope sights are mounted on the left side of the receiver). Early versions had muzzle brake-compensator, but later it was discarded. The buttstock was folded upward and forward. The receiver was made from steel, as well as all other parts, except plastic pistol grip and chains. When folded, the automatic rifle is suitable for covert carrying. The bolt handle is also made from folded steel for easy concealed carrying. Unlike the Kalashnikov assault rifle, the slit for the bolt handle is always open.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Sights: 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78 "Chestnut", "Kobra" EKP-1C-03, "Kobra" EKP-8-02, OKP-7, PSO-1\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer for 9A-91/VSK-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss">
		<text>Gauss rifle “Product 62”</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_descr">
		<text>The super-precision high-tech weapon, known as "Product No. 62", was developed by designers of secret laboratories within the Zone. Its principle of operation is based on the overclocking of the bullet by a system of electromagnets; the bullet is capable of developing super speed, which provides a colossal punching ability with almost no recoil. Particles of some artifacts are used to ensure sufficient power capacity of batteries.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_descr">
		<text>The Beretta 92F is perhaps the most famous American military pistol that replaced the legendary M1911. Characteristic features of this pistol: short-stroke recoil operated, aluminum alloy frame and chromed barrel channel. The gun is very popular and has been adopted by several countries in the world.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm (after modification)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_rusty_descr">
		<text>The Beretta 92F is perhaps the most famous American military pistol that replaced the legendary M1911. Characteristic features of this pistol: short-stroke recoil operated, aluminum alloy frame and chromed barrel channel. The gun is very popular and has been adopted by several countries in the world.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Unable to attach silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_descr">
		<text>Featuring best-in-class ergonomics, the Walther P99 is built on a short stroke recoil energy pattern. The gun frame is made of light polymer material. Designed for law enforcement agencies and civil arms market, the pistol is adopted by police units of several countries.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer 9mm \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight Leupold DeltaPoint</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-gauss">
		<text>Projectile for Gauss rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-gauss_descr">
		<text>Specially made 12 gauge projectiles for Gauss rifles. They have high penetrating power.\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]V\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]very strong\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] prototype</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-gauss_cardan">
		<text>Crafted Gauss Rifle Shell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-gauss_cardan_bad">
		<text>Crafted Gauss Rifle Shell (worn out)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-gauss_cardan_verybad">
		<text>Crafted Gauss Rifle Shell (very worn out)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-gauss_cardan_descr">
		<text>The projectiles are made of 12 caliber zhekan. Have a high penetration ability.\n \n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Penetrates armor class: %c[0,170,170,170]V\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Tissue damage: %c[0,170,170,170]very strong\n \n%c[0,170,170,170]FEATURE:\n \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] prototype</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_6x4">
		<text>Soviet combat knife-bayonet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_6x4_descr">
		<text>This Soviet steel knife has a 132-mm blade with a large choyal toe, a brown wooden handle and an S-shaped guard. It is a reverse type of garment, as the standard Soviet knife grip is a blade to itself. The handle is reinforced with a coarse overlay for better retention. The knife is relatively small, which does not allow deep wounds to be inflicted, but it is capable of piercing bulletproof vests.\n \n%c[ui_red] - %c[ui_red] Not intended for cutting huge objects.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_combat">
		<text>Hunting knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_combat_descr">
		<text>A big hunting knife with a reliable rubberized grip. Sharp and in good condition. Not suitable for piercing bulletproof vests, but thanks to a serrated blade it cuts flesh well, keeping the wound from closing. This makes it an ideal weapon against animals, especially when piercing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_needle">
		<text>Soviet combat knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_needle_descr">
		<text>The Soviet combat knife used during the Second World War. It has a small popularity among stalkers in the Zone.\n \n%c[ui_red] • %c[ui_red] Not intended for cutting big game.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_swat">
		<text>Special Forces folding knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_swat_descr">
		<text>Folding knife of extremely high quality, ideal for scouts. It is an extremely lethal weapon and the only knife in the Zone that penetrates the vests equally well and inflicts serious wounds to the unprotected flesh. It's an excellent close combat weapon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_hunting">
		<text>Long hunting knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_hunting_descr">
		<text>Very robust hunting knife with large stainless steel blade. Ideal for hunting mutants, cutting meat and thick skins. The knife is able to cause extensive bleeding wounds. Its disadvantage is that it cannot penetrate heavy armor.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_knife_fanat">
		<text>Fanatic's long hunting knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_custom">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_worn">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 (worn)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 in standard configuration with fixed 1.5x optical sights. AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - army universal rifle) is an Austrian 5.56mm bullpup assault rifle, developed by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH &amp; Co KG during 1960s. In 1978 AUG was adopted by Austrian army as standard small arms under the designation of StG 77, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (licensed FN FAL). The rifle and its variants have also been adopted by the armies of Argentina, Australia, Malaysia, New Zealand, Bolivia, Ecuador, Ireland, Luxembourg, Saudi Arabia, Tunisia, Pakistan, as well as by the US border guard.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight 1.5x (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_custom_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 in a modified configuration with fixed 2.0x optical sights and composite materials. AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - army universal rifle) is an Austrian 5.56mm bullpup assault rifle, developed during 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH &amp; Co KG. In 1978 AUG was adopted by Austrian army as standard small arms under the designation of StG 77, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (licensed FN FAL). The rifle and its variants have also been adopted by the armies of Argentina, Australia, Malaysia, New Zealand, Bolivia, Ecuador, Ireland, Luxembourg, Saudi Arabia, Tunisia, Pakistan, as well as by the US border guard. This model has been upgraded to NATO standard 7.62x51 cartridge.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] sight 1.5x (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_descr">
		<text>AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr) - small arms complex, produced in 1977 by Austrian company Steyr-Daimler-Puch. The Steyr AUG A3 differs from the basic model by its four Picatinny bars: the upper barrel is used to attach the sights, the lower barrel can be fitted with underbarrel grenade launcher or vertical front grip, and the lateral barrel can be fitted with a laser designator or other necessary additional equipment.\n \n%c[default]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] Sights: ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, Barska Red Dot AC11090, C-MORE, EOTech\n \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] underbarrel grenade launcher M203\n \n%c[255,1,255,255]•%c[default] Silencer caliber 5.56x45 NATO.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>