<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<!-- Mutant body parts -->
	<string id="mutant_flesh_meat">
		<text>Flesh meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_flesh_meat_description">
		<text>Pretty popular product in the Zone, flesh meat has good taste and great nutritional value. Scientists have already done quite a lot of research on the samples brought by stalkers, so the demand for such pieces of meat itself has dropped. Some animal fat suitable for weapons lubrication can be extracted from a piece of meat by simple manipulation.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal and mutant meat in the Zone in raw form, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +584 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_boar_meat">
		<text>Boar meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_boar_meat_description">
		<text>The most popular meat in the Exclusion Zone. Very nutritious and not highly contaminated. Scientists have already done quite a lot of research on the stalker specimens brought in, so the demand for such pieces of meat has dropped. Some animal fat suitable for weapons lubrication can be extracted from a piece of meat by simple manipulation.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal and mutant meat in the Zone in raw form, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +646 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_meat">
		<text>Blind dog meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_meat_description">
		<text>Many stalkers use the meat of a mutated blind dog as a cheap alternative to the most popular boar meat. Scientists have already done quite a lot of research on the samples brought by the stalkers, so the demand for such pieces of meat itself has dropped. From a piece of meat with simple manipulations, it is possible to get some animal fat suitable for weapons lubrication.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of meat of animals and mutants in the Zone in raw form, as it must be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +202 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_psevdodog_meat">
		<text>Pseudodog meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_psevdodog_meat_description">
		<text>Pseudodog meat - quite tasty, with great nutritional value, stalkers often choose it fried. It may be of interest to scientists. From a piece of meat, with simple manipulations, you can get a little animal fat, suitable for lubricating weapons.\n \n%c[ui_green]NOTE:\n \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this kind of meat of animals and mutants in the Zone in raw form, as it is probably contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +264 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+1%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_krovosos_meat">
		<text>Bloodsucker meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_krovosos_meat_description">
		<text>The bloodsucker's meat is very viscous and viscous, so it is not suitable for eating. Although the bloodsuckers are deadly monsters, the price of their meat is not very high due to limited use. It might interest scientists. From a piece of meat, a little animal fat, suitable for weapons lubrication, can be extracted by simple manipulation. \n \n%c[ui_green]NOTE:\n \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of meat of animals and mutants in the Zone in raw form, as it is probably contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] high origin mutatn part \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +541 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_stronglav_meat">
		<text>Stronglav meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_stronglav_meat_description">
		<text>Stronglav meat is very viscous and viscous, but very nutritious. The price of such meat is much higher than usual. It may be of interest to scientists. From a piece of meat, a little animal fat suitable for weapons lubrication can be obtained by simple manipulation.\n \n%c[ui_green]NOTE:\n \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal and mutant meat in the Zone in raw form, as it is probably contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] high origin mutatn part \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +541 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_snork_hand">
		<text>Snork hand</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_snork_hand_description">
		<text>It is generally believed that snork mutated from people, poet to eat their meat is considered ogres and very immoral. However, some groups, such as bandits and mercenaries, include this type of meat in the diet of their fighters, thus showing a kind of superiority over other groups. Scientists may be interested in finding a better use for this type of meat. \n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of meat of animals and mutants in the Zone raw, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +408 mSv</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_meat">
		<text>Chimera meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_meat_description">
		<text>Heavy piece of chimera meat. Chimera is commonly referred to as one of the most dangerous creatures, so its meat is highly valued by stalkers veterans who are willing to buy it for a very impressive price. The cooks at Skadovsk use this meat as one of the key ingredients of the so-called "Hunter's Food". But few people admit that chimera meat tastes different from boar meat in some way. Could be of interest to scientists. In addition, it can be used to produce the best quality animal fat available in the Zone, which can easily be used to effectively lubricate weapons.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal meat and mutants in the Zone in raw form, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] high origin mutatn part \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +665 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+4%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_medwed_meat">
		<text>Bear's meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_medwed_meat_description">
		<text>Heavy piece of bear meat. Bears are commonly called one of the most dangerous creatures in the area, so their meat is highly valued by veteran stalkers who are willing to buy it for a very impressive price. But few people admit that his meat tastes different from wild boar meat. It may be of interest to scientists. It can also be used to produce the best quality animal fat available in the Zone, which can easily be used to effectively lubricate weapons.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal and mutant meat in the Zone raw, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] high origin mutatn part \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +665 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+4%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_medwed_fat">
		<text>Bear's fat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_medwed_fat_description">
		<text>Heavy piece of bear lard. Hard animal fat, very nutritious food. It is very difficult to extract, so it is highly valued by veteran stalkers and traders who are willing to buy the piece for a very impressive price. It could be of interest to scientists. It can also be used to produce the best quality animal fat available in the Zone, which can easily be used to effectively lubricate weapons.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal meat and mutants in the Zone raw, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] high origin mutatn part \n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +665 mSv\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] gun lubricant (+4%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_tushkano_meat">
		<text>Tushkano meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_tushkano_meat_description">
		<text>A small piece of meat from the body of a mutated rodent. A cheap and common food, which, as stalkers say, strengthens the heart muscle when cooked on fire. Scientists may be interested.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal and mutant meat in the Zone raw, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +139 mSv</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_rat_meat">
		<text>Rat meat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_rat_meat_description">
		<text>A small piece of meat from the body of the mutated rat. A cheap and common food, which, as stalkers say, strengthens the heart muscle when cooked on fire. Scientists may be interested.\n \n%c[ui_green]WARNING: \n%c[default]Stalkers are advised to refrain from eating this type of animal and mutant meat in the Zone raw, as it is likely to be contaminated with trichinosis or brucellosis. These diseases are transmitted by the consumption of contaminated meat. Symptoms include fever, fatigue and loss of appetite, which are very dangerous in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Abscesses, strange tumours on meat make it clear that it is infected and should be discarded.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] can be cooked\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +84 mSv</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_rat_spleen">
		<text>Rat spleen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_rat_spleen_description">
		<text>We still don't know who discovered it first. Probably some inquisitive scientist. But they claim that the spleen of mutated rats, for unknown and incredible reasons, contains and produces stem cells, widely used in genetic engineering. At the same time, these cells are so resistant to external influences that they can be stored in an undamaged organ without additional treatment for up to fourteen days. Such a spleen is not found in all rodents, but stalkers have learned to accurately identify the right individual by its size and color of skin. Engaged in the autopsy of rats - it is not their pleasant, but the high price of this "product" makes the inhabitants of the Zone and this work.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,0,255,30] • %c[default] mutant meat of low origin»\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] poisonous food\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] radiation exposure: %c[0,170,170,170] +84 mSv</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_flesh_eye">
		<text>Flesh eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_flesh_eye_description">
		<text>Mutated, swollen eyes of the flesh have a number of very strange features, the most interesting and useful of which is the ability to restore the damaged parts of the body, even in very serious lesions. The whole specificity of this process is still unknown. But scientists believe that if you manage to unravel this process - it is likely to cause a revolutionary progress in modern medicine and will get a cure for many diseases. You can play your part and accelerate the process of advancing science to the important discovery and save millions of innocent lives by selling flesh eyes to scientists.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_boar_leg">
		<text>Boar's hoof</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_boar_leg_description">
		<text>Boar hooves can be used for the production of many medicinal products, for example, to obtain anti-radiation serum that removes excess radiation from the body.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_boar_tusk">
		<text>Boar's tusk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_boar_tusk_description">
		<text>The tusk of a Chernobyl boar reaches 30 cm in length, making it a dangerous weapon against a weakly protected victim. In terms of composition and strength, it is no different from an ordinary tusk, so it is of little interest to scientists. As a common trophy among stalkers, it is valued by collectors outside the Exclusion Zone.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_tail">
		<text>Blind dog Tail</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_tail_description">
		<text>The resistance of the skin of mutated blind dogs to electricity and chemical reagents caused quite a stir in the scientific community. Since the tails of dogs lack any fatty tissue, they are particularly suitable for laboratory tests.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_psevdodog_tail">
		<text>Pseudodog tail</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_psevdodog_tail_description">
		<text>Recently there have been rumours in the Zone that there is a new trend in fashion that has enslaved the whole world: fur from the tails of pseudosobaks. The fur is so soft that it has no equal. It is also said that this fur is able to keep warm even in the strongest snowstorms and blizzards. For this reason, the tails of pseudosobak are in great demand.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_bloodsucker_jaw">
		<text>Bloodsucker tentacles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_bloodsucker_jaw_description">
		<text>The tentacles of a bloodsucker contain special glands that secrete an enzyme that can break down skin cells and at the same time prevent blood clotting. Disclosing the composition of this enzyme can make a big breakthrough in a whole chain of medical discoveries. Some stalkers snatch teeth from defeated bloodsuckers to make necklaces for themselves. In general, the bloodsucker tentacles are one of the most popular jewelry in the Zone.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_stronglav_jaw">
		<text>Stronglav tentacles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_stronglav_jaw_description">
		<text>The largest tentacles of this rare species. Stronglava tentacles contain special glands that release an enzyme that can break down skin cells and at the same time prevent blood clotting. Discovering the composition of this enzyme can make a big breakthrough in the chain of medical discoveries. Some stalkers rip the teeth out of defeated bloodsuckers to make necklaces for themselves. In general, the bloodsucker tentacles are one of the most popular jewelry in the Zone.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_snork_leg">
		<text>Snork leg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_snork_leg_description">
		<text>The leg of the snork contains a large number of super elastic tendons. This explains the mutant's ability to make such high and long jumps. Scientists are still trying to find a way to use these tendons and will be very grateful for every sample they bring.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_snork_mask">
		<text>Snork mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_snork_mask_description">
		<text>The masks on the snork muzzles seem to be an old Soviet-made version of the GP-5 gas mask, which was often used by soldiers and researchers in the Exclusion Zone before the second Chernobyl disaster. Some of these people worked in numerous underground laboratories, completely isolated from the outside world, which were exposed to huge amounts of radiation, which caused a mutagenic form of a man known to us as a snork. The mask, even if it is broken (the lenses are cracked, the hose from the filter is punctured in many places), is still in great demand by scientists. Of course, it can be used to repair your clothes, but this will make it unsuitable for further sale.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological subject\n%c[ui_green] • %c[default] broken, not repairable\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] is used at:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+4%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_claw">
		<text>Chimera claw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_claw_description">
		<text>Chimera claw. Its exact molecular composition has not been studied, but everyone knows that it is as strong and sharp as a diamond. That explains why a monster can easily tear apart any armor.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_heart">
		<text>Chimera heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_heart_description">
		<text>The heart of chimera is a duplicate organ with a high level of regeneration, which is already of great interest to scientists. If one organ fails, the second one takes over the entire load, so that the mutant remains capable of fighting even with severe wounds. The heart is also of special interest to medicine, as its study can help solve the problem of high mortality among Siamese twins.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_tooth">
		<text>Chimera tooth</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_chimera_tooth_description">
		<text>The front tooth of a chimera. Its exact molecular composition has not been studied, but it is known to be as strong and sharp as a diamond. That explains why a monster can bite any armor with ease. This tooth is highly prized among stalkers, and is direct proof that its master is a true hunter. Several poachers even came to the Zone to obtain chimera teeth and resell them on the black market. Unfortunately, the chimeras were not as obedient and predictable as many thought. So none of them came back. All that's left of them are memories and some of their personal belongings, which helped to recognize where they were torn to pieces by these terrible mutants.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_medwed_claw">
		<text>Bear claw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_medwed_claw_description">
		<text>Bear claw. Its exact molecular composition has not been studied, but everyone knows that it is as strong and sharp as a diamond. That explains why a monster can easily tear apart any armor.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_tushkano_head">
		<text>Tushkano head</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_tushkano_head_description">
		<text>Head of a tushkano. The eyes, ears, mouth and nose of a tushkano in a small, tiny package. Scientists are interested in studying these parts of monsters in order to determine the origin of tushkano.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_part_controller_brain_tissue">
		<text>Controller brain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_part_controller_brain_tissue_description">
		<text>Controllers have powerful mental abilities and it is safe to say that these forces originate in their brains. What's interesting is that every mutant with this kind of psi-wave related ability has a similar brain structure. Scientists will pay generously for samples of these tissues. The brain has the smell of sour pumpkin.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_controller_hand">
		<text>Controller's hand</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_controller_hand_description">
		<text>The controllers seem to use their hands in mental contact with their victim. Scientists are happy to study them, trying to find any mutations responsible for their connection to the Controller's psi brain radiation. Smells like old socks mixed with sour vegetables.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_cat_tail">
		<text>Cat tail</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_cat_tail_description">
		<text>Cats in the Zone are incredibly large compared to pets and pose an impressive danger. They are able to move around without the slightest sound, regardless of the type of soil under their feet. The tail of these cats symbolises the awareness of their presence alongside you.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_zombi_hand">
		<text>Zombie hand</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_zombi_hand_description">
		<text>The mutated hand of the mutant, called "old zombie" stalkers, are former people who lived and worked in the Alienation Zone, exposed to huge amounts of radiation every day and, after the second Chernobyl incident, also to constant exposure to psi radiation. After many years in this condition, the bones in their bodies became brittle and half-rotted pieces of flesh were visible. For this reason, from afar, these creatures look like animated corpses. But this view is deceptive - creatures are quite alive and constantly hungry, so they are a threat, especially when their whole crowd. Zombie hand is a valuable material for scientific research, it can also identify the person to whom it belonged.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_fracture_hand">
		<text>Fracture arm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_fracture_hand_description">
		<text>The severed arm of the Breakaway is an awfully deformed part of the body of a humanoid mutant. Clearly, these creatures used to be human, and all that happened to them was the aftermath of the second Chernobyl accident. From the remnants of clothing on their bodies, we can conclude that the Fractures are indigenous people who lived and worked directly within the perimeter of the Exclusion Zone. Since the deformation of the bodies in all the fractures is identical, it is assumed that at the time of the mutation all the bodies were in the same position: either they were transported somewhere or someone deliberately placed them like this. All samples of this type of mutants encountered by stalkers were male. Therefore, it is safe to say that the fruit of the fractures can not exactly be and their number in the Zone is gradually decreasing. For this reason, they are now very rare, and a fairly deformed right arm of the Fault is a valuable object for study.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_pseudogiant_hand">
		<text>Pseudogiant hand</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_pseudogiant_hand_description">
		<text>The paw of a pseudo giant can be a very valuable find for scientists who would be happy to study it. It smells like old socks mixed with sour vegetables.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_pseudogiant_eye">
		<text>Pseudogiant's eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_pseudogiant_eye_description">
		<text>The eye of a pseudo giant resembles an enlarged human eye, but with slight differences. It has more developed tear glands and a more textured iris. Pseudo giants seem to cry quite often, but it is not known whether this is some kind of physiological process or a side effect of the psychology of the creature. In any case, scientists will probably want to clean it up, so they'll be willing to pay a substantial amount for this kind of samples.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_burer_hand">
		<text>Burer's hand</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_burer_hand_description">
		<text>Burer's hands play a vital role in using his telekinetic abilities. Scientists have taken great interest in studying this kind of specimens to detect mutations in them. It smells like old socks mixed with sour vegetables.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_burer_brain">
		<text>Burer's Brain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_burer_brain_description">
		<text>Burer is fluent in telepathic abilities, completely unexplored by science, so some of his organs are a welcome trophy of scientists and mercenaries. The brain, being the source of telepathic abilities, plays the main role in this list. It weighs one and a half or two times the mass of the human brain. Externally, it's indistinguishable. Due to its size and structure, the brain can be easily damaged during prey: a damaged organ is not suitable for laboratory studies.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mutant_part_crow_beak">
		<text>Raven beak</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mutant_part_crow_beak_description">
		<text>The mutated beak of the Chernobyl Raven, which apparently has lived in the Alienation Zone for over 15 years. Very strong and hard to the touch. Most stalkers consider the raven to be pests that should be destroyed. Others find them very useful when navigating the wastelands. Sometimes the beak is used as decoration, but apart from its aesthetic appearance, it is of no use. Rumor has it, however, that the very first stalkers to arrive in the Zone invented some kind of ritual called "Beak".\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_liver">
		<text>Blind dog liver</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_liver_description">
		<text>In the Alienation Zone conditions, the blind dog's body has undergone major changes. One of them is a mutated liver, which was heavily loaded due to a toxic diet and lack of clean drinking water. Scientists are interested in it, because studying its structure can help to create drugs for people suffering from severe liver disease.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_heart">
		<text>Blind dog heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_dog_heart_description">
		<text>Blind dogs have many features that make them very different from their healthy brothers. One of these differences is an extremely hardy heart that allows a mutant to chase his victim for a long time until he is exhausted. Heart rate during chase reaches 250 beats per minute, which is unthinkable for healthy mutated individuals of the same weight class. This endurance makes the heart of the blind dog an interesting subject to study, but because of its prevalence, the prices for the organ among scientists are very low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_cat_thyroid">
		<text>Cat thyroid gland</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_cat_thyroid_description">
		<text>Prolonged residence in areas contaminated with radiation resulted in the thyroid glands of cats increasing many times in size. At present, hyperthyroidism has become a hereditary disease rather than an acquired one after many generations. Symptoms of the disease: increased food intake, increased activity, changes in behavior, nervousness, hair loss. These acquired skills did not destroy the species, but rather allowed mutated animals to quickly displace their healthy congeners and take high positions in the food chain. This is of little interest to scientists due to the study of the mechanisms and consequences of the disease. \n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_cat_claw">
		<text>Cat claw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_cat_claw_description">
		<text>The cat's claws have an unknown structure that allows them to easily cut the overalls. Scientists and the military believe that in-depth study of them will help to create new particularly durable materials and vests based on them.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_bloodsucker_heart">
		<text>Bloodsucker heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_bloodsucker_heart_description">
		<text>The bloodsucker's heart has an unexplored property - it releases an enzyme into the victim's bloodstream that does not clot due to incompatibility of groups. Studying the principle of this mechanism and the composition of the enzyme will allow scientists to solve the problem of blood donation for patients with rare groups, and is likely to open new boundaries for medicine.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_stronglav_heart">
		<text>Stronglav heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_stronglav_heart_description">
		<text>Stronglav's heart is so strong that it seems to pulsate even after death. Heavier than a normal bloodsucker's heart, it has the property of regeneration - it releases an enzyme into the victim's bloodstream that prevents it from clotting due to incompatibility of groups. Studying the principle of this mechanism and the composition of the enzyme will allow scientists to solve the problem of blood donation for patients with rare groups, and is likely to open new boundaries for medicine.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_psevdodog_fang">
		<text>Pseudodog fang</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_psevdodog_fang_description">
		<text>The tusks of a pseudops serve to tear and hold the victim. Due to the huge jaw pressure, the mutant bites most of the protective equipment used in the Zone, while the teeth themselves are not strong and are regularly replaced with new ones throughout life. Scientists are not of particular interest, as opposed to collectors from a large land.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common scientific specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_karlik_ear">
		<text>Karlik ear</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_karlik_ear_description">
		<text>The karlik's pointed ear. Part of the body, interesting only from a scientific point of view, as the brain and the other cells are destroyed by chemicals after death. Very valuable because of the huge stock of luck and the skills that are needed to get this trophy.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific specimen\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mutant_poltergeist_hand">
 		<text>Poltergeist's hand</text>
 	</string>
   <string id="mutant_poltergeist_hand_description">
 		<text>The chopped off arm of a poltergeist, oddly enough, but these crawling mutants are quite tangible, which really puzzled the scientists. It has a horrible smell. It is of medium scientific value, as the origin of these creatures is not known to science.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] mutated body part\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] common specimen of science\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] average value</text>
 	</string>
</string_table>