<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="af_drops">
		<text>«Droplets»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af-drops_descr">
		<text>Formed in the Burner anomaly, at high temperatures. From the exterior, it looks like a tear-like shade compound with a glossy surface, covered in cracks.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="af_ameba_slime">
		<text>«Slime»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ameba_slime_descr">
		<text>It is certain that this artefact is created by the anomaly called "Fruit punch". When carried on the belt the wounds bleed less, although the body of its owner becomes more vulnerable to various burns.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="af_ameba_slug">
		<text>«Slug»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ameba_slug_descr">
		<text>Formed by the "Fruit punch" anomaly. The negative qualities of this artefact are compensated by the fact that it heightens the coagulation quality of blood. It's not often that one runs into such an artefact, and they pay well for it too.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="af_ameba_mica">
		<text>«Mica»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ameba_mica_descr">
		<text>Anomaly "Fruit punch" is able to create such an artefact at the rarest, most extreme collection of physical conditions. The result is a semi-transparent, hard object. A rare and expensive artefact.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="af_rusty_thorn">
		<text>«Thorn»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_descr">
		<text>The result of the interaction between the anomaly Burnt Fuzz and the body of a careless stalker. The Thorn artefact pokes the body of its owner, no matter what. But it also helps clean the body of radionuclide. Quite widespread and cheap.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="af_rusty_kristall">
		<text>«Crystal Thorn»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_kristall_descr">
		<text>Crystallizes in the anomaly Burnt Fuzz. Naturally takes out the radiation from the organism. That is, through the ears along with some amount of blood. Blood loss is possible also through over openings. Widespread and quite effective, which is the cause for the stable price in the artefact market.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="af_rusty_sea_urchin">
		<text>«Urchin»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_sea_urchin_descr">
		<text>The anomaly Burnt Fuzz very rarely gives rise to this artefact. Raise the blood pressure and so, the body gets rid of a large amount of red blood cells. But along with them the stored radiation leaves the body as well. In his fundamental work titled "Ionization and polarization of the components of rare artefacts", Sakharov noted that the content of this formation has a critical stability, and it's not realistic to create such an artefact in lab conditions in the next ten years.n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_name">
		<text>«Bubble»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_descr">
		<text>The artifact is a few hollow formations of organic nature that are connected to each other. It emits a gaseous substance capable of neutralizing chemical or toxic particles in the human body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand but also has numerous negative properties. For example, it significantly enhances the effect of psi waves, as well as the fields created by mutants and anomalies. Many stalkers told us that when they had a "Bubble", the effect of psi radiation was so powerful that the only thing they could do was to scream as hard as they could. This also applies to the Electro - the artifact conducts electricity and increases the current by many times. The only positive aspect of this artifact is that it speeds up wound healing. This property makes it very expensive on the artifact market, it is in demand. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Scale of Radiation" is average. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact can be easily ignited, like other organic formations, it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of thermal and acid anomalies.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_name">
		<text>«Stone Blood»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_descr">
		<text>It is a reddish formation of pressed and fossilized plant remains, soil and animal remains. It has the ability to partially neutralize chemical substances harmful to humans, absorbing them and reducing the overall level of toxicity in the owner's blood. Quite widespread and not particularly effective, as after its use chemical burns fester. It can catch fire from an open flame or even spontaneously ignite. Increases the negative impact of psi waves and is a powerful electrical conductor. It also absorbs energy when worn on the belt. "Blood Stone, however, speeds up wound healing well because of its organic nature. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_name">
		<text>«Crystal»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_descr">
		<text>The artifact occurs in anomalous zones under the influence of high temperatures. It actively absorbs excess heat from the space around it, while remaining cool to the touch. On the other hand, the presence of such an environment increases the impact of acid on corrosion of mechanisms. All pros and cons of artifacts in toxic areas should be considered. It acts as a good conductor of electricity. Accelerates blood coagulation if applied close to the body (Note: it is not recommended to leave the artifact on the body for a long time, as the resulting blood clots may be dangerous to health). This artifact is also in demand by jewelers outside the Zone, as its inner core is not radioactive and is very beautiful if it is skillfully worked on. The outside is covered with a very hard layer of 10 mm, which emits most of the radiation. It's relatively heavy because of its high density. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_name">
		<text>«Stone Flower»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_descr">
		<text>This artifact is like cheese mixed with sapphire rocks. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so skillfully processed it is possible to extract non-radioactive blue embeddings used by jewelers to make jewelry. The utility of the artifact is not limited to its industrial application. There is scientific evidence that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Because of its high density, it weighs heavily even when compared to other anomalous formations in the Zone. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_name">
		<text>«Battery»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_descr">
		<text>This artifact provides a little more protection from psi fields than his younger brother Moonlight. The artifact includes electrostatic elements, but scientists are still unable to determine the nature of its formation. It is quite popular in the Zone, valued for its active properties, although it has side effects on the owner's body when used for a long time. It should be noted that this artifact prevents blood clotting and increases bleeding from existing wounds. On the other hand, being a powerful insulator, it provides good protection against high energy discharges. This artifact is also very light and compact. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_name">
		<text>«Shell»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_descr">
		<text>"Shell" consists of two discs of bluish color, bound together by a translucent material of unknown nature. This strange artifact has been considered devoid of any useful properties for a long time. Only recently has it been discovered that it provides all the high level of protection against psi-effects, partially absorbing them. It also absorbs electromagnetic interference and acts like an earthing switch.  When the artifact reacts with the body, the body's endurance increases and the wearer begins to feel younger. For some stalkers, it can be hyperactive. One drawback to this artifact is that it reduces the number of platelets in the blood and thus increases the rate of bleeding. It's very light and compact. Radioactive radiation on the artifact's radiation scale is high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_spring">
		<text>«Spring»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_spring_descr">
		<text>According to some theoretical researchers, this artifact is a hybrid of "Batteries" and "Pacifiers". The "spring" is a very rare artifact. It is one of the few artifacts that are well increasing the protection against shocks. That is, it reduces both physical damage and gravitational anomalies, which seriously helps if the stalker needs to "climb" into the anomaly to get the artifact.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_pellicle">
		<text>«Pellicle»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_pellicle_descr">
		<text>This artifact is so rare that many researchers do not even realize that such a substance can exist in natural conditions. It rejects caustic chemical components. One of the few artifacts that has no negative effects.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_name">
		<text>«Mama's Beads»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_descr">
		<text>It takes the form of a DNA spiral, "Mom's beads" are formed in fire anomalies. A characteristic feature is a constant pulsation and the radiation of waves that are beneficial to the body: increase metabolism, accelerate wound healing. The consequences of using this artifact are not yet known. "Mom's beads also have powerful protective properties: they can protect the body from high temperatures and acid.   However, care should be taken when using this artifact in acidic and toxic environments, it should be taken into account that its use increases the corrosive wear of equipment and mechanisms in such conditions. It also increases conductivity, which increases the risk of electric shock when worn on the belt during a storm or from an electrical anomaly. Sufficiently high weight due to high density of the artifact. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_name">
		<text>«Flash»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_descr">
		<text>This artifact is very similar to "Moonlight" and resembles a ball filled with plasma. As you know, when used, it extinguishes the harmful effects of psi-anomalies or psi waves of some mutants. The "Flash" acts as a capacitor and will absorb even lethal blows of electricity. However, it is important to note that a "Flash" can cause a slight shock when it comes into contact with electricity. It has weak regenerative properties, so it even prevents wound healing. It should be used with care when wounds and bleeding. Very lightweight and compact. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_name">
		<text>«Moonlight»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_descr">
		<text>This artifact of electrostatic nature demonstrates the ability to resonate under the influence of psi waves. Over time, stalkers have learned to adjust Moonlight to resonate in phase with the main source of radiation, thus completely or significantly neutralizing the psy-wave effect. This artifact ball also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high voltages. It also increases energy and endurance, allowing the wearer to feel full of energy. A side effect is that the rate of healing of wounds decreases. The artifact is very light and compact. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_name">
		<text>«Sparkler»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_descr">
		<text>It looks like a semitransparent spider web. It is also sticky, like the protein spider web, and has glue properties. Most often it can be found in the vicinity of electrical anomalies, which certainly affects their characteristics: it can smooth out voltage differences in the electric field, which protects the owner from the electric field. Also slightly protects against psi-radiated anomalies of psi waves of mutants. Due to its electrical nature, it is a weak source of energy. It has no healing properties, but the liquid formed by the artifact damages the skin and prevents blood clotting. It is lightweight. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_name">
		<text>«Eye»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_descr">
		<text>This artifact really looks like an organ of vision. In injuries, it speeds up metabolic processes, which promotes rapid healing of wounds. In addition, among experienced stalkers there is a belief that the "Eye" is able to bring good luck. True or not, its positive effects are really quite powerful. Firstly, it reduces body temperature, secondly, it provides protection against any kind of acids, thirdly, it reduces pain and is extremely useful in the treatment of wounds. Many stalkers say that even hopeless wounds from mutants heal in front of their eyes, many managed to survive without bandages only using this artifact. However, the artifact is dangerous to use in chemical anomalies, it is better to keep it in a backpack. People sometimes call it "Copper Eye" because it conducts electricity well and increases its impact. Radioactive radiation from the "Artifact Scale of Radiation" is high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_name">
		<text>«Flame»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_descr">
		<text>It is formed in areas of high thermal activity. It is characterized by intense infrared radiation, which accelerates the process of blood clotting in open wounds. Due to the great rarity of this artifact, its cost is extremely high. When used, it reduces the body temperature of the owner, which is very useful in areas of high temperatures. It also acts as a powerful insulator and suppresses some of the effects of acids. The effect of healing wounds is very strong, some stalkers said that they managed to survive even after biting chimera. Many stalkers and veteran hunters managed to survive this artifact. Has side effects: it is suicide to enter into toxic or acid anomalies with the artifact on your body. It increases the corrosiveness of toxic particles and the negative impact of chemicals on the owner's blood. It can be used instead of a first aid kit, as wound healing is very fast. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Scale" is high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_name">
		<text>«Fireball»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_descr">
		<text>Spherical artifact formed in thermal anomalies from reddish crystals. It has a constant temperature of 24 degrees Celsius, regardless of the surrounding conditions. This allows it to absorb heat in close proximity to itself and create, as if a small thermal barrier around the owner, which protects against contact with flames and high temperatures. Constant temperature is also a consequence of another positive effect: it speeds up the healing rate of wounds and stops bleeding. The artifact will also protect the wearer from acid burns, but it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies with the activated artifact, as this will increase the negative impact of acids and toxins on the wearer's blood. It also makes the possessor vulnerable to electricity. It's very heavy because of the high density of the crystal structure. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Scale of Radiation" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_name">
		<text>«Kolobok»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_descr">
		<text>Quite a rare artifact formed in areas of high chemical contamination. It is highly valued for its ability to "spur" the body so that it can recover from injuries of any degree of severity within minutes. Scientists are spreading information about the effects of an artifact on the owner's genetic material; however, this is not yet confirmed and should be seen as an attempt to monopolize the supply of the artifact by the scientific community. But one should not assume that the artifact is absolutely harmless. One disadvantage is that it increases electrical conductivity, so it is better to avoid electrical anomalies. Also reduces energy recovery, but it is unlikely to flow from its properties, but rather affects the strong injections from its needles when used. Needles contribute to the rapid healing of wounds, but cause constant pain and itching, thus reducing endurance. It has a negative impact on the protection against psyche waves coming from anomalies or mutants, as well as protection from heat and acids because of its rapid flammability. Given its chemical origin, it is well known that an artifact can enhance the owner's protection against toxicity. It is light and does not take up much space. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_name">
		<text>«Firefly»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_descr">
		<text>"Firefly" works with fields inaccessible to science, accelerating the regeneration of tissues and organs of living creatures, as well as normalizing metabolic processes. It is able to literally put on the feet of a man with serious wounds. Unfortunately, this artifact is extremely rare. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact is much more likely to ignite spontaneously than any other organic artifact, so it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of fire and acid anomalies. The artifact also significantly increases the harmful effects of psi radiation and several times increases the effect of electric current on the host body. Many have also noticed that it reduces endurance and fatigue somewhat. But in spite of all this, the artifact will suck all lethal doses of chemical poisoning from the host body, in addition, excellent protection against toxicity. It is in demand in military circles, because it allows to conduct attacks with biological and chemical weapons with the least casualties. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_name">
		<text>«Goldfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_descr">
		<text>All its properties were discovered by Sakharov on Amber after a massive ejection. After his careful research, it was found that this artifact is formed after the merger of the three "Gravi" at the level of interaction of singular fields. This phenomenon is very rare and therefore the artifact is very valuable. The Russian government is very interested in obtaining and using this artifact. There are rumors in Ukrainian special forces circles that there are agents of the Russian Ministry of Defence in the Zone, whose only task is to search for and transport the "Golden Fish" to a special laboratory outside the Alienation Zone. The artifact creates a gravitational field of singularity, which affects all objects around it. It also creates a kind of protective film around the owner, which has good qualities of fire resistance, and also protects against acid by decomposing acid-containing elements into simpler compounds. The artifact is very heavy and should not be taken for long walks. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_name">
		<text>«Gravi»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_descr">
		<text>The artifact is formed under prolonged gravitational action on metal-containing substances. It is able to maintain a small gravitational field around itself, in particular reduces the weight of all objects in the immediate vicinity. For a long time, the nature of the artifact was unclear until the scientist Sakharov on Amber found that "Gravi" produces fields of gravity component at intervals of 30 minutes. Due to this property, the artifact reduces the weight of objects and also emits small doses of radiation. But on the other hand protects the owner from shocks and physical damage due to its own micro gravity field. Some have expressed concern that this artifact could be used as a basis for the creation of weapons of mass destruction. There are rumours that the Russian Federation is conducting research on the possibility of using Gravity as a weapon. The artifact is very heavy, so it is not recommended to take it on long walks. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_name">
		<text>«Snowflake»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_descr">
		<text>Also known as "Radioactive Snowflake." The artifact looks like a "Snowflake"; there is a perception that it is a kind of "Snowflake" as it significantly increases its resistance to electric current by creating its own field that absorbs electricity. Thanks to its unique properties, the artifact is able to dramatically increase the muscle tone of the carrier, thereby increasing endurance. Increased radioactivity (the source of which is still unknown to science) also affects the carrier, so stalkers jokingly call it "Radioactive Snowflake". When used, it is worth weighing all the pros and cons: get high endurance and protection from electricity at the cost of high radiation. Use in combat also remains a controversial issue, as its use increases bleeding from wounds and prevents healing of wounds due to the burning outer shell, irritating the skin. It is very light and does not take up much space. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" - high.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_name">
		<text>«Jellyfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_descr">
		<text>An artifact of gravitational nature, with the ability to actively attract and absorb radioactive and chemical particles, thereby reducing the body's irradiation. Widely distributed in the Zone; outside the Zone, it is widely, though covertly, used in the treatment of acute radiation sickness and deadly chemical poisoning. This artifact is very heavy. It slightly protects the carrier from elevated temperatures and abnormal acids. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is absent.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_name">
		<text>«Meat Chunk»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_descr">
		<text>This artifact has a soft, porous structure and is said to shrink like a sponge. When exposed to certain external conditions, it reveals its special characteristics. First, it emits the smell of burning flesh when it is near a heat source. Prolonged heating can ignite it. Although objects near an artifact are more likely to ignite, it remains intact. In this way it can be said that the "Meat Scrap" absorbs heat and transmits it to the surrounding objects. Secondly, the pores on the surface of the artifact absorb toxicity from the environment. Thirdly, when in contact with psi-anomalies or psi waves of different nature, it absorbs part of the field energy, but at the same time emits strong radiation. Fourth, it conducts electricity in the same way as any flesh of living creatures. Many stalkers reported that they felt exhausted, even with short-term use of the artifact. However, its most useful property is to slowly close wounds and repair damaged tissue. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_name">
		<text>«Night Star»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_descr">
		<text>A luminous artifact capable of generating a gravitational field around itself, which increases its mass. For this reason, it's very heavy, but provides protection against acids and heat. Due to its beautiful inner core is very appreciated by jewelers all over the world, but care should be taken when processing it, as improper polishing of the artifact can cause an explosion that can destroy a small building. The Night Star will also absorb toxic and chemical substances from the environment, making it valuable among artefact hunters, although the absorption of toxins is negligible. It's quite cheap, so even stalkers with a limited budget can afford to buy this artifact. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_name">
		<text>«Soul»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_descr">
		<text>A unique organic artifact with unique properties - secrets mucus, which is unknown so far, increases the overall rate of recovery of the body after injuries of any nature. Due to its pleasant appearance and reasonable price, it is of particular interest for collectors. Because of its organic nature, the "Soul" is easily inflammable and should not be kept near a fire or sources of intense heat. It is known that it ignites at temperatures above 60 degrees Celsius. The artifact provides good chemical and toxic protection by absorbing the chemicals it uses to form mucus. It also increases the effects of psi waves on the host organism and increases electrical damage. The density of the structure is low, so it's not very heavy. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_name">
		<text>«Wrenched»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_descr">
		<text>An artifact of bizarre shape that occurs in areas of high gravitational activity. It is a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements. Equally successfully protects its carrier from the external effects of toxic substances, as well as from chemical particles already in the body. It looks like coral, thanks to the inorganic nature of non-combustible, which provides adequate protection against heat and acids. No one is particularly interested in this artifact, so it is mainly bought up by scientists who are experimentally trying to find use of its properties. It has a high density, so it is very heavy. Radioactive radiation on the "Artifact Radiation Scale" is low.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_compass">
		<text>«Compass»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_compass_descr">
		<text>A rare artifact - last found many months ago. It has the ability to show ruptures in abnormal fields. They say it can be used to pass by the most difficult anomalies without the slightest risk, but very few people know how to handle it.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_oasis_heart">
		<text>«Heart of the Oasis»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_oasis_heart_descr">
		<text>An artifact from the center of the legendary Oasis. Apparently, it is a crystallized plant, which has adopted the characteristic property of the Oasis beneficial to the body as a whole. It's exceptionally radioactive, unlike the Oasis itself.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b1_half_artifact">
		<text>Altered Insulator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b1_half_artifact_descr">
		<text>This used to be an insulator. It has now almost turned into an unstable artifact. It is probably the source of intermittent psy-emissions.\n \n%c[default]PROPERTIES:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] half-artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] valuable\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_surge_name">
		<text>Surge</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_surge_descr">
		<text>Increases the efficiency of a small but advanced device that absorbs electrical energy around it. It serves as an overvoltage protection, limiting the amount of electricity that comes into contact with the body by shorting it to the ground. It is a rather complex circuit, consisting of a limiting resistor and a varistor, which greatly increases the electrical resistance of the body. As a result, the body falls under a lower voltage and is able to withstand discharges of electricity, which previously led to fatal consequences. It is therefore very important to have a current limiter on your belt when you need to get close to electrical anomalies or other sources of electricity in the Zone. As with any metal object, it can be used as a repair material if appropriate tools and skills are available. \n \n%c[ui_red]WARNING:\n%c[default]Please note that such a module will not be able to function properly and will not provide sufficient protection if your suit does not meet the minimum protection requirements for the anomaly fields.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] does not require recharging\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+8%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_frames_name">
		<text>Frames</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_frames_descr">
		<text>Instead of simply using the backpack straps behind your back, you can attach the backpack to your body using aluminum frames that make it easier to carry. The frames are made of aluminium, which is chosen as the base because of its low weight, while the small external elements are made of plastic. This is necessary to achieve the necessary flexibility for long stretches and sprints. The whole construction is equipped with a system of belts and straps, which allows you to easily adjust the position of the backpack on the back and, therefore, increase the comfort and convenience of its use. A single set of aluminum frames replaces only the basic frame of your backpack. However, several sets can be used to fine-tune and further improve the transport of goods. Although the system is made of lightweight aluminum, some of the material can be useful for minor repairs.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] widespread application\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases maximum weight\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+6%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grid_name">
		<text>Titanium frame</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grid_descr">
		<text>Instead of simply using the backpack straps behind your back, you can attach it to your body with a titanium frame that makes it easier to carry. The frame is made of titanium, which is chosen as the base because of its light weight and strength, while the small external elements are made of plastic. This is necessary to achieve the necessary flexibility for long runs and sprints. The whole construction is equipped with a system of belts and straps, which allows you to easily adjust the position of the backpack on the back and, therefore, increase the convenience and comfort of its use. The frame is made of high quality titanium and therefore the disassembled frame can be used as a supplement when repairing armour or helmets for better protection.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] widespread application\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+10%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_freon_name">
		<text>Freon cooler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_freon_descr">
		<text>Freon cooling module is designed to maintain a constant temperature around the body at 20 degrees Celsius. Consequently, it is extremely useful for minimizing the harmful effects of high temperatures in places where additional protection is required. The entire system is in a vacuum and absorbs excess heat, lowering the temperature of the carrier by creating a freon cloud that cools the air molecules. Another property of the freon cloud is that it is to some extent a dielectric, i.e. it has the property of reducing the effects of electricity.\n \n%c[ui_red]WARNING: \n \n%c[default]It should be noted that such a module will not be able to work properly and provide sufficient protection if your suit does not meet the requirements of minimum protection in an abnormal field.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] does not require recharging</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cooler_name">
		<text>Cooling module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cooler_descr">
		<text>Body Cooler is an electrical module designed to maintain a constant temperature around the body at 15 degrees Celsius. Therefore, it is extremely useful for minimizing the harmful effects of high temperatures in places where additional protection is required. It generates fast electrical pulses that discharge air, creating a vacuum that absorbs excess heat and slightly lowers the temperature around the medium. The system does not require water to function. Another ability of the chiller is to reduce the impact of electricity on the body slightly. If disassembled using a special set of tools, the metal case can be reused as armour repair material.\n \n%c[ui_red]WARNING:\n \n%c[default]Please note that such a module will not be able to work properly and will not provide sufficient protection if your suit does not meet the minimum protection requirements in abnormal fields.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] does not require recharging\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+8%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_name">
		<text>Kevlar plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective properties and are therefore highly valued. They can perform a wide variety of functions, but the most important of them is to absorb the energy of firearms bullets, mainly at the front and back of the torso. They are a lightweight alternative to heavy steel plates. In addition, they allow the armour to remain in good condition for longer periods of time by significantly reducing the wear and tear of the armour when in contact with adversaries. Used by military units around the world.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n %c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+12%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_plates_name">
		<text>Steel plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_plates_descr">
		<text>Specially designed plates are made by long and complex heat treatment of steel. They are made taking into account the ballistic properties of armor and the installation of various modifications and upgrades. Used to absorb shock on the front and back of the body. Such protection comes at a price, since thick steel plates are very heavy, and they also significantly limit movement speed and maneuverability. They allow you to maintain armor in good condition longer due to a significant reduction in wear when in contact with bullets or bumps. It is widely used by special forces. \n \n %c[ui_red] ATTENTION: \n \n %c[default] Steel is a good conductor and, being so close to the body, makes the carrier more vulnerable to electricity. Caution should be exercised near electrical anomalies and other sources of electrical energy.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] single layer steel sheet\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+20%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_name">
		<text>Camel hump</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_descr">
		<text>It takes its name from the myth that camels store water in their humps. The "camel hump" allows you to transfer water on your back or on your belt, is a hydration system: a dense soft reservoir, in the form of a heating pad, filled with water. A flexible hose with a dosing system makes it easy to use even in the most demanding situations. The system integrates protection against external damage, whether it is a blow or an anomaly. Since the tank is made of high-quality textiles, experienced stalkers reuse it as a material for repairing equipment. \ N \ n% c [ui_red] ATTENTION: \ n \ n% c [default] Although water has lower conductivity, than metals, its proximity to the body can make the wearer more vulnerable to electricity. You should pay attention to the environment when you have a “Camel Hump” with you.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+6%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_iam_name">
		<text>Improvised Application Module (empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_iam_descr">
		<text>The home-made application module, short for IAM, filters a small amount of radioactive particles emitted by artifacts. This mechanical metallized bag is the cheapest device that can use the properties of weak artefacts. The filter consists of many layers made mainly of lead, which is a weak shield against radiation. It represents an alternative to more reliable AAC and AAM. In case of breakage or if it is unnecessary, the metal of the module can be used to repair armour or helmets. It is not currently used. It is necessary to fix an artifact in it, and then attach the module to the belt. The artifact retains its characteristics with the exception of radiation exposure.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] empty\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+6%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_aac_name">
		<text>Artifact Application Container (empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_aac_descr">
		<text>Artifact Application Container (AAC) filters a moderate amount of radiation particles emitted from artifacts. This mechanical aluminum container is the most cost-efficient and thus the most popular way of handling artifacts as it allows the user to harness the power of more potent artifacts. Artifact filter is composed of multiple layers made primarily of lead, with one layer of thorium which has strong radiation shielding properties. This device has been manufactured by scientists residing in military bunkers around the Zone. In case of emergency or if no longer needed, the module can be utilized as a source of quality metal for use in outfit or helmet repairs. Currently unusable. To attach it to the belt, you have to put an artifact inside. The artifact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] empty\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+10%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_aam_name">
		<text>Artifact Application Module (empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_aam_descr">
		<text>Artifact Application Module (AAM) filters a significant amount of radiation particles emitted from artifacts. This advanced mechanical module is the most effective way of harnessing the power of most potent artifacts. Artifact filter is composed of numerous layers made of nano-carbon. It is hence lightweight and has strongest radiation shielding properties of all devices. Regarded as a symbol of affluence in the Zone. Most commonly used by the scientists to minimize the harmful effects of artifacts. Designed and manufactured in Ukraine by a government institute which provides equipment for the scientists residing in the Zone of Alienation. In case of emergency or if no longer needed, the module can be utilized as a source of quality metal for use in outfit or helmet repairs. Currently unusable. To attach it to the belt, you have to put an artifact inside. The artifact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] empty\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+14%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_flesh_name">
		<text>Flesh hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_flesh_descr">
		<text>Hide removed from a breed of mutated pigs commonly referred to as fleshes. Its heavy weight (its main drawback) results from a thick layer of fat underneath the relatively soft and shallow skin. It offers low physical protection, but on the other hand considerably reduces the harmful effects of chemical, thermal and electrical anomalies. Can be used only for minor repairs as the layer of fat is useless for the purposes of armor maintenance and must be cut off, leaving only a small patch of shallow skin tissue.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] light mutant pelt\n%c[0,93,0,116] • %c[default] very low rupture protection increase\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+2%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_boar_name">
		<text>Boar hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_boar_descr">
		<text>The skin of wild boars located in the Zone is almost completely covered with a thick layer of fur. These mutants are quite resistant to damage and can take significant damage for one simple reason: large muscle mass and virtually indestructible bones. At the same time, their skin is quite thin (most likely for heat transfer efficiency), which makes it a rather weak subject to improve the quality of equipment protection. The fur, in turn, makes the skin a relatively good heat insulator. Leather can also be used for minor repairs. Unfortunately, the use of the skin makes the wearer less protected against the effects of radiation and toxic damage, since heavy particles of this nature settle on the fur and accumulate in it.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] light mutant pelt\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_bloodsucker_name">
		<text>Bloodsucker hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_bloodsucker_descr">
		<text>Bloodsuckers are a type of mutated people, which is immediately noticeable in a detailed examination of the skin. Most importantly, their skin is soft and pleasant to the touch like that of a child. Beneath the skin is a developed musculature, which clearly will not play into your hands when close combat with him. Using the skin of a bloodsucker in his armor is a symbol of an experienced hunter. Its most unique feature, at the same time a disadvantage, is an intense reaction to temperature changes - although the skin does not burn at high temperatures, but it heats up badly causing damage to the wearer and can spoil his equipment.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] strong mutant skin\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+6%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_burer_name">
		<text>Burer skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_burer_descr">
		<text>The skin of a burer is a lot like the skin of a twisted dwarf. Add to that the unbearable smell of rotten eggs, and you get a complete picture of why stalkers consider skinning a real feat. Practice shows that the skin provides relatively little protection from physical influences, but can also absorb and disperse significant amounts of psi waves when worn on the head. In addition, given that Burers are rare in the Zone, skin is of particular value to scientists. The skin of a burer has low electrical resistance, and lowers the resistance of the host body, making it more susceptible to electric shock.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] light mutant pelt\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_chimera_name">
		<text>Chimera skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_chimera_descr">
		<text>Chimera is one of the most dangerous mutants in the Zone, so it should be considered not only a deadly threat, but also a source of enrichment. All the body parts that can be cut from the defeated chimera can be sold for an impressive amount of money. Skin is the most valuable thing for science, and is also the best object to increase armor efficiency within the Alien Zone. It offers very good protection properties, is very light and does not hinder movement. The most unique feature of chimera skin is that its organic fibres are very good conductors. This fact is confirmed by many scouts who have observed the behavior of chimera, claiming that chimeras sometimes look like electrical anomalies in contact with any hostile organism. But there is no concrete evidence of this fact, as few people came back alive after such sorties.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very strong mutant skin\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+8%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_medwed_name">
		<text>Bear skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_medwed_descr">
		<text>The bear is one of the most dangerous mutants in the Zone, so it should be considered not only a deadly threat, but also a source of enrichment. All body parts that can be cut from a defeated bear can be sold for an impressive amount of money. Skin is the most valuable thing for science, and is also the best object to increase armour efficiency within the Alien Zone. It offers very good protection properties, is very light and does not hinder movement. The most unique feature of the bear's skin is that its organic fibres are something like a ring. Some experienced stalkers tell us that they have observed the behavior of mutated bears, claiming that their skin can withstand even a few shots from a couple of meters, reinforced with bullets. But there is no concrete proof of this fact, as few people came back alive after such meetings with these dangerous animals.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very strong mutant skin\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+8%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_vodianoy_name">
		<text>Vodyanoy skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_vodianoy_descr">
		<text>Vodyanoy is a rare creature that lives near reservoirs, their origin remains a mystery, so it is worth considering it not only as a mortal threat, but also as a source of enrichment. The value of a skin of water is of great interest to hunters and scientists, and is also the best item to increase the effectiveness of armor within the Exclusion Zone. Firstly, this biological waterproof fabric has good protection properties and is very lightweight and does not constrain movement. The most unique feature of the skin of an aquatic animal is that its organic fibers represent something like chain mail. Some experienced stalkers say that they watched the behavior of these creatures, claiming that their skin can withstand even a few shots from a couple of meters, reinforced with cartridges. But there is no concrete evidence of this fact, since few people managed to survive after meeting with this dangerous mutant.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very strong mutant skin\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+8%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_pseudogiant_name">
		<text>Pseudogiant hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_pseudogiant_descr">
		<text>The skin of a pseudogiant resembles the skin of an elephant. Thick and hard to the touch, the texture is loose and filled with folds that serve as a “radiator”, cooling the body of the creature. On average, the thickness of the pseudo-giant skin is 2 cm, which makes it very strong and able to withstand significant damage. But, due to this, it has significant weight. Pseudo-giants are known to live in areas with high toxicity and radioactivity, therefore, their skins are adapted to these conditions, which makes them even more useful. It can be used to upgrade even the heaviest armor, but this process requires the most durable and expensive tools. The skin of a pseudo-giant is appreciated not only for its physical qualities, it can also serve as an excellent trophy and a rare instance for scientists in the Zone.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very strong mutant skin\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+9%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_controller_name">
		<text>Controller's scalp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_controller_descr">
		<text>As with other humanoid mutants, taking the scalp from the controller is quite an emotional challenge, as the face of the controller preserves human features. Confidential sources in the armed forces reported that the fingerprints of the person who turned into a controller can be found in the databases. A recent analysis showed that not only the controller's hands are capable of emitting psi waves, but his whole body is a source of radiation. Thus, properly prepared skin from his head, has the ability to absorb psi energy, it is enough to throw a scalp on your head. Leather is also a good electrical conductor. The structure is very thin and can be used for minor repairs of clothes.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] light mutant pelt\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+3%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_pseudodog_name">
		<text>Pseudodog hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_pseudodog_descr">
		<text>Densely coated with short and hard fur, the pseudodog hide is one of the most useful, widely used and widely used skins available in the Zone. It can be easily attached to the armour even with light and simple tools, but remains quite strong, which makes it suitable for middle-class armour repair. When used, it provides good protection from physical influences and heat. The fur also provides good insulation against electricity, but like all hides, it accumulates radioactive and toxic particles in the pile. It is recommended to remove it in radioactive and toxic areas.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] strong mutant skin\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+5%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_psy_dog_name">
		<text>Pseudodog fur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_psy_dog_descr">
		<text>Pseudodog fur is undoubtedly one of the most beautiful and rare materials for clothes manufacturing in the world. Usually pure white or gray, it is in great demand and can be sold for huge money. In the fashion industry, fur has leaked through smugglers who have joined the ranks of mutant hunters. It can serve as a blanket for stalkers, especially during cold nights. It also protects against psi influences when fur is used as a mask or hood. Like all skins, it accumulates radiation and toxins, so it is recommended that you take it off in contaminated areas. Hunters wear it proudly if they killed the mutant themselves.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] strong mutant skin\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] increases protection efficiency\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] equipment repair (+7%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poltergeist_powder">
		<text>Diamond powder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poltergeist_powder_descr">
		<text>"Diamond Powder" is a generic name for a crystalline substance that can be found in the bellies of psycho mutants. Nobody knows exactly what metabolic processes led to its formation, so scientists are willing to pay large sums of money to get it. Its practical use is limited, but some stalkers sprinkle hunting knives with it, which makes it easier to sharpen them. It also gives a shine to the blade, which looks pretty groomed.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] a product of the metabolism of a psy-mutant\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] very rare scientific sample\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used in:%c[0,170,170,170] knives sharpening (+28%)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Jellyfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_iam_descr">
		<text>"Jellyfish" in a improvised application module. Gravity artifact of nature, which has the ability to actively attract and absorb radioactive and chemical particles, thereby reducing the irradiation of the body and reducing toxic poisoning on the body. Widely distributed in the Zone; outside the Zone, it is widely, though covertly, used in the treatment of acute radiation sickness and deadly chemical poisoning. This artifact is very heavy. It protects the carrier a little from elevated temperatures and abnormal acids. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Jellyfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Stone Flower»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_iam_descr">
		<text>"Stone flower" in a improvised application module. This artifact is like cheese mixed with sapphire stones. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so skillfully processed it is possible to extract non-radioactive blue embeddings used by jewelers to make precious objects. The utility of the artifact is not limited to its industrial application. There is scientific evidence that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Because of its high density, it weighs heavily even when compared to other anomalous formations in the Zone. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone flower»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Night star»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_iam_descr">
		<text>"Night Star" in a improvised application module. A luminous artifact capable of generating a gravitational field around itself, which increases its mass. For this reason, it's very heavy, but provides protection against acids and heat. Due to its beautiful inner core, it is highly valued by jewelers all over the world, but care should be taken when processing it, as improper polishing of the artifact can cause an explosion that can destroy a small building. The Night Star will also absorb toxic and chemical substances from the environment, making it valuable among artefact hunters, although the absorption of toxins is negligible. It's quite cheap, so even stalkers with a limited budget can afford to buy this artifact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Night star»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Wrenched»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_iam_descr">
		<text>"Wrenched" in a improvised application module. An artifact of a bizarre shape that occurs in areas of high gravitational activity. It is a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements. It equally successfully protects its carrier from both the external effects of toxic substances and chemical particles that have already entered the body. It looks like coral, thanks to the inorganic nature of non-combustible, which provides adequate protection against heat and acids. No one is particularly interested in this artifact, so it is mainly bought up by scientists who are experimentally trying to find use of its properties. It has a high density, so it is very heavy. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Wrenched»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Gravi»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_iam_descr">
		<text>"Gravi" in a improvised application module. An artifact is formed under prolonged gravitational action on metal-containing substances. It is able to maintain a small gravitational field around itself, in particular increases the weight of all objects in the immediate vicinity. For a long time, the nature of the artifact was not clear until the scientist Sakharov on Amber found that "Gravi" produces fields of gravity component at intervals of 30 minutes. Due to this property, the artifact increases the weight of objects and also emits lethal doses of radiation. But on the other hand, it protects the possessor from fire anomalies and acids from chemical and toxic anomalies. But it does not absorb chemical toxins, and enters into compounds with them, dividing them into more simple substances due to the peculiarities of its field. Some have expressed concern that this artifact could be used as a basis for weapons of mass destruction. There are rumours that the Russian Federation is conducting studies on the possibility of using Gravi as a weapon. The artifact is very heavy, so it is not recommended to take it on long walks. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Gravi»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Goldfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_iam_descr">
		<text>"Goldfish" in the improvised application module. All its properties were discovered by the Sakharov scientist on Amber after a massive ejection. After his careful research, it was found that this artifact is formed after the merger of three "Gravies" at the level of interaction of singular fields. This phenomenon is very rare and therefore the artifact is very valuable. The Russian government is very interested in obtaining and using this artifact. There are rumors in Ukrainian special forces circles that there are agents of the Russian Ministry of Defence in the Zone, whose only task is to search for and transport the "Golden Fish" to a special laboratory outside the Alienation Zone. The artifact creates a gravitational field of singularity, which affects all objects around it. It also creates a kind of protective film around the owner, which has good qualities of fire resistance, and also protects against acid by decomposing acid-containing elements into simpler compounds. The artifact is very heavy and should not be taken for long walks. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Goldfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Thorn»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_iam_descr">
		<text>"Thorn" in the improvised application module. "Thorn" is the result of interaction between Burnt Fuzz anomaly and the body of a careless stalker. The Thorn artefact pokes the body of its owner, no matter what. But it also helps clean the body of radionuclide. Quite widespread and cheap.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Thorn»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Crystal»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_iam_descr">
		<text>"Crystal" in a improvised application module. The artifact arises in anomalous zones under the influence of high temperatures. It actively absorbs excess heat from the space around it, while remaining cool to the touch. It will also protect the owner in toxic and acid anomalies. On the other hand, the presence of such an environment increases the impact of acid on corrosion of mechanisms. All pros and cons of artifacts in toxic areas should be considered. Acts as a good electrical conductor. Accelerates blood coagulation if applied close to the body (Note: it is not recommended to leave the artifact on the body for a long time, as the resulting blood clots may be dangerous to health). This artifact is also in demand by jewelers outside the Zone, as its inner core is not radioactive and is very beautiful if it is skillfully worked on. The outside is covered with a very hard layer of 10 mm, which emits most of the radiation. It's relatively heavy because of its high density. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Crystal»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Fireball»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_iam_descr">
		<text>"Fireball" in a improvised application module. Spherical artifact formed in thermal anomalies from reddish crystals. It has a constant temperature of 24 degrees Celsius, regardless of the surrounding conditions. This allows it to absorb heat in close proximity to itself and create, as if a small thermal barrier around the owner, which protects against contact with flames and high temperatures. Constant temperature is also a consequence of another positive effect: it speeds up the healing rate of wounds and stops bleeding. The artifact will also protect the wearer from acid burns, but it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies with the activated artifact, as this will increase the negative impact of acids and toxins on the wearer's blood. It also makes the possessor vulnerable to electricity. It's very heavy because of the high density of the crystal structure. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Fireball»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Mama's Beads»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_iam_descr">
		<text>"Mama's beads" in the improvised application module. Has the form of a spiral of DNA, "Mom's beads" are formed in fire anomalies. A characteristic feature is the constant pulsation and radiation of waves that are beneficial to the body: increase metabolism, accelerate wound healing. The consequences of using this artifact are not yet known. "Mom's beads also have powerful protective properties: they can protect the body from high temperatures and acid.   However, care should be taken when using this artifact in acidic and toxic environments, it should be considered that its use increases the corrosive wear of equipment and mechanisms in such conditions. It also increases conductivity, which increases the risk of electric shock when worn on the belt during a storm or from an electrical anomaly. Sufficiently high weight due to high density of the artifact. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Mama's Beads»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Eye»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_iam_descr">
		<text>"Eye" in the improvised application module. This artifact really looks like an eye. In injuries, it accelerates metabolic processes, which promotes rapid healing of wounds. In addition, among the experienced stalkers there is a belief that the "Eye" is able to bring good luck. True or not, its positive effects are really quite powerful. Firstly, it reduces body temperature, secondly, it provides protection against any kind of acids, thirdly, it reduces pain and is extremely useful in the treatment of wounds. Many stalkers say that even hopeless wounds from mutants heal in front of their eyes, many managed to survive without bandages only using this artifact. However, the artifact is dangerous to use in chemical anomalies, it is better to keep it in a backpack. People sometimes call it "Copper Eye" because it conducts electricity well and increases its impact. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Eye»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Flame»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_iam_descr">
		<text>"Flame" in the improvised application module. Appears in areas of high thermal activity. It is characterized by intensive infrared radiation, which accelerates the process of blood clotting in open wounds. Due to the great rarity of this artifact, its cost is extremely high. When used, it reduces the body temperature of the owner, which is very useful in areas of high temperatures. It also acts as a powerful insulator and suppresses some of the effects of acids. The effect of healing wounds is very strong, some stalkers said that they managed to survive even after biting chimera. Many stalkers and veteran hunters managed to survive this artifact. Has side effects: it is suicide to enter into toxic or acid anomalies with the artifact on your body. It increases the corrosiveness of toxic particles and the negative impact of chemicals on the owner's blood. It can be used instead of a first aid kit, as wound healing is very fast. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flame»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Stone Blood»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_iam_descr">
		<text>"Stone Blood" in a improvised application module. It is a reddish formation of compressed and fossilized plant remains, soil and animal remains. It has the ability to partially neutralize chemical substances harmful to humans, absorbing them and reducing the overall level of toxicity in the owner's blood. Quite widespread and not particularly effective, as after its use chemical burns fester. It can catch fire from an open flame or even spontaneously ignite. Increases the negative impact of psi waves and is a powerful electrical conductor. It also absorbs energy when worn on the belt. "Blood Stone, however, speeds up wound healing well because of its organic nature. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Blood»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Meat Chunk»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_iam_descr">
		<text>"Meat Chunk" in a improvised application module. This artifact has a soft, porous structure and is said to shrink like a sponge. When exposed to certain external conditions, it reveals its special characteristics. First, it emits the smell of burning flesh when it is near a heat source. Prolonged heating can ignite it. Although objects near an artifact are more likely to ignite, it remains intact. In this way it can be said that the "Meat Scrap" absorbs heat and transmits it to the surrounding objects. Secondly, the pores on the surface of the artifact absorb toxicity from the environment. Thirdly, when in contact with psi-anomalies or psi waves of different nature, it absorbs part of the field energy, but at the same time emits strong radiation. Fourthly, it conducts electricity in the same way as any flesh of living creatures. Many stalkers reported that they felt exhausted even with the short-term use of the artifact. However, its most useful property is to slowly close wounds and repair damaged tissue. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Meat Chunk»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Soul»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_iam_descr">
		<text>"Soul" in a improvised application module. A unique organic artifact with unique properties - secrets slime, which is unknown yet, increases the overall rate of recovery of the body after injuries of any nature. Due to its pleasant appearance and reasonable price, it is of particular interest for collectors. Because of its organic nature, the "Soul" is easily inflammable and should not be kept near a fire or sources of intense heat. It is known that it ignites at temperatures above 60 degrees Celsius. The artifact provides good chemical and toxic protection by absorbing the chemicals it uses to form mucus. It also increases the effects of psi waves on the host body and increases damage from electricity. The density of the structure is low, so it's not very heavy. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Soul»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Kolobok»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_iam_descr">
		<text>"Kolobok" in the improvised application module. Quite a rare artifact formed in areas of high chemical contamination. It is highly valued for its ability to "spur" the body so that it can recover from injuries of any degree of severity within minutes. Scientists are spreading information about the effects of an artifact on the owner's genetic material; however, this is not yet confirmed and should be seen as an attempt to monopolize the supply of the artifact by the scientific community. But one should not assume that the artifact is absolutely harmless. One disadvantage is that it increases electrical conductivity, so it is better to avoid electrical anomalies. Also reduces energy recovery, but it is unlikely to flow from its properties, but rather affects the strong injections from its needles when used. Needles contribute to the rapid healing of wounds, but cause constant pain and itching, thus reducing endurance. It has a negative impact on the protection against psyche waves coming from anomalies or mutants, as well as protection from heat and acids because of its rapid flammability. Given its chemical origin, it is well known that an artifact can enhance the owner's protection against toxicity. It is light and does not take up much space. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Kolobok»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Bubble»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_iam_descr">
		<text>"Bubble" in the improvised application module. The artifact is a few hollow formations of organic nature that are connected to each other. It emits a gaseous substance capable of neutralizing chemical or toxic particles in the human body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand but also has numerous negative properties. For example, it significantly enhances the effect of psi waves, as well as the fields created by mutants and anomalies. Many stalkers told us that when they had a "Bubble", the effect of psi radiation was so powerful that the only thing they could do was to scream as hard as they could. This also applies to the Electro - the artifact conducts electricity and increases the current by many times. Another positive aspect of this artifact is that it speeds up wound healing. This property makes it very expensive on the artifact market, it is in demand. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact can be easily ignited, like other organic formations, it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of thermal and acid anomalies. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Bubble»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Firefly»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_iam_descr">
		<text>"Firefly" in a improvised application module. This artifact works with fields inaccessible to science, accelerating the regeneration of tissues and organs of living creatures, and normalizing metabolic processes. It is able to literally put on the feet of a man with serious wounds in front of his eyes. Unfortunately, this artifact is extremely rare. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact is much more likely to ignite spontaneously than any other organic artifact, so it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of fire and acid anomalies. The artifact also significantly increases the harmful effects of psi radiation and several times increases the effect of electric current on the host body. Many have also noticed that it reduces endurance and fatigue somewhat. But in spite of all this, the artifact will suck all lethal doses of chemical poisoning from the host body, in addition, excellent protection against toxicity. It is in demand in military circles, because it allows to conduct attacks with biological and chemical weapons with the least casualties. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Firefly»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Sparkler»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_iam_descr">
		<text>"Sparkler" in a improvised application module. It looks like a semitransparent spider web. It is as sticky as a protein spider web and has glue properties. Most often it can be found in the vicinity of electrical anomalies, which certainly affects their characteristics: it can smooth out voltage differences in the electric field, which protects the owner from the electric field. Also slightly protects against psi-radiated anomalies of psi waves of mutants. Due to its electrical nature, it is a weak source of energy. It has no healing properties, but the liquid formed by the artifact damages the skin and prevents blood clotting. It is lightweight. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Sparkler»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Flash»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_iam_descr">
		<text>"Flash" in a improvised application module. This artifact is very similar to "Moonlight" and resembles a ball filled with plasma. As you know, when used, it extinguishes harmful effects from psi-anomalies or psi waves of some mutants. The "Flash" acts as a capacitor and will absorb even lethal blows of electricity. However, it is important to note that a "Flash" can cause a slight shock when it comes into contact with electricity. It has weak regenerative properties, so it even prevents wound healing. It should be used with care when wounds and bleeding. Very lightweight and compact. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flash»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Moonlight»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_iam_descr">
		<text>"Moonlight" in a improvised application module. This artifact of electrostatic nature demonstrates the ability to resonate under the influence of psi waves. Over time, stalkers have learned to adjust Moonlight so that it resonates in phase with the main source of radiation, thus completely or significantly neutralizing the psy-wave effect. This artifact ball also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high voltages. It also increases energy and endurance, allowing the wearer to feel full of energy. A side effect is that the rate of healing of wounds decreases. The artifact is very light and compact. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Moonlight»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Battery»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_iam_descr">
		<text>"Battery" in a improvised application module. This artifact provides slightly more protection against psi fields than his younger brother Moonlight. The artifact includes electrostatic elements, but scientists are still unable to determine the nature of its formation. It is quite popular in the Zone, valued for its active properties, although it has side effects on the owner's body when used for a long time. It should be noted that this artifact prevents blood clotting and increases bleeding from existing wounds. On the other hand, being a powerful insulator, it provides good protection against high energy discharges. This artifact is also very light and compact. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Battery»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Shell»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_iam_descr">
		<text>"Shell" in the improvised application module. This artifact consists of two bluish discs linked together by a translucent material of unknown nature. This strange artifact has been considered devoid of any useful properties for a long time. Only recently has it been discovered that it provides all the high levels of protection against psi-effects, partially absorbing them. It also absorbs electromagnetic interference and acts like an earthing switch.  When the artifact reacts with the body, the body's endurance increases and the wearer begins to feel younger. For some stalkers, it can be hyperactive. One drawback to this artifact is that it reduces the number of platelets in the blood and thus increases the rate of bleeding. It's very light and compact. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Shell»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Snowflake»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_iam_descr">
		<text>"Snowflake" in a improvised application module. Also known as "Radioactive Snowflake." The artifact looks like a "Snowflake"; there is a perception that it is a kind of "Snowflake" as it significantly increases its resistance to electric current by creating its own field that absorbs electricity. Thanks to its unique properties, the artifact is able to dramatically increase the muscle tone of the carrier, thereby increasing endurance. Increased radioactivity (the source of which is still unknown to science) also affects the carrier, so stalkers jokingly call it "Radioactive Snowflake". When used, it is worth weighing all the pros and cons: get high endurance and protection from electricity at the cost of high radiation. Use in combat also remains a controversial issue, as its use increases bleeding from wounds and prevents healing of wounds due to the burning outer shell, irritating the skin. It is very light and does not take up much space. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Snowflake»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Compass»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_iam_descr">
		<text>"Compass" in the improvised application module. A rare artifact - the last time it was found many months ago. It has the ability to show ruptures in anomalous fields. They say it can be used to pass by the most difficult anomalies without the slightest risk, but very few people know how to handle it. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Compass»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Heart of the Oasis»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_iam_descr">
		<text>"Heart of Oasis" in a improvised application module. An artifact from the center of the legendary Oasis. Apparently, it is a crystallized plant that has adopted the characteristic property of the Oasis beneficial to the body as a whole. It's exceptionally radioactive, unlike the Oasis itself. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Heart of the Oasis»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Altered Insulator»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_iam_descr">
		<text>"Modified isolator" in the home-made application module. This thing is something remotely reminiscent of an ordinary electrical insulator. Now, under the influence of abnormal fields, the Alienation Zone is an artifact of unstable nature. Judging by its effects on the body, it's the source of intermittent psy waves. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Insulator»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] extremely radioactive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_iam_name">
		<text>IAM with «Altered Wheel»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_iam_descr">
		<text>"Modified hand wheel" in the improvised application module. That's what's left of the normal ship's helm. It is now an artifact of strange nature. There are no outstanding properties, except a small glow and a lot of radioactivity. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Wheel»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] extremely radioactive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Jellyfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_aac_descr">
		<text>"Jellyfish" in an artifact application container. Gravity artifact of nature, which has the ability to actively attract and absorb radioactive and chemical particles, thereby reducing the irradiation of the body and reducing toxic poisoning on the body. Widely distributed in the Zone; outside the Zone, it is widely, though covertly, used in the treatment of acute radiation sickness and deadly chemical poisoning. This artifact is very heavy. It protects the carrier a little from elevated temperatures and abnormal acids. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Jellyfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Stone Flower»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_aac_descr">
		<text>"Stone Flower" in an artifact application container. This artifact is like cheese mixed with sapphire stones. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so skillfully processed it is possible to extract non-radioactive blue inclusions used by jewelers to make precious objects. The usefulness of the artifact is not limited to its industrial application. There is scientific evidence that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Because of its high density, it weighs heavily even when compared to other anomalous formations in the Zone. Emitted particles do not penetrate the walls of the container..\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Flower»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Night star»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_aac_descr">
		<text>"Night Star" in an artifact application container. A luminous artifact capable of generating a gravity field around itself, which increases its mass. For this reason, it's very heavy, but provides protection against acids and heat. Due to its beautiful inner core is very appreciated by jewelers all over the world, but care should be taken when processing it, as improper polishing of the artifact can cause an explosion that can destroy a small building. The Night Star will also absorb toxic and chemical substances from the environment, making it valuable among artefact hunters, although the absorption of toxins is negligible. It's quite cheap, so even stalkers with a limited budget can afford to buy this artifact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Night star»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Wrenched»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_aac_descr">
		<text>"Whipped" in an artifact application container. An artifact of a bizarre shape that occurs in areas of high gravitational activity. It is a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements. Equally successfully protects its carrier from the external effects of toxic substances, as well as from chemical particles that have already entered the body. It looks like coral, thanks to the inorganic nature of non-combustible, which provides adequate protection against heat and acids. No one is particularly interested in this artifact, so it is mainly bought up by scientists who are experimentally trying to find use of its properties. It has a high density, so it is very heavy. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Wrenched»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Gravi»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_aac_descr">
		<text>"Gravi" in an artifact application container. An artifact is formed under prolonged gravitational action on metal-containing substances. It is able to maintain a small gravitational field around itself, in particular, increases the weight of all objects in the immediate vicinity. For a long time, the nature of the artifact was not clear until the scientist Sakharov on Amber found that "Gravi" produces fields of gravity component at intervals of 30 minutes. Due to this property, the artifact increases the weight of objects and also emits lethal doses of radiation. But on the other hand, it protects the possessor from fire anomalies and acids from chemical and toxic anomalies. But it does not absorb chemical toxins, and enters into compounds with them, dividing them into more simple substances due to the peculiarities of its field. Some have expressed concern that this artifact could be used as a basis for weapons of mass destruction. There are rumours that the Russian Federation is conducting studies on the possibility of using Gravi as a weapon. The artifact is very heavy, so it is not recommended to take it on long walks. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Gravi»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Goldfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_aac_descr">
		<text>"Goldfish" in an artifact application container. All its properties were discovered by Sakharov's scientist on Amber after a massive ejection. After his careful research, it was found that this artifact is formed after the merger of three "Gravies" at the level of interaction of singular fields. This phenomenon is very rare and therefore the artifact is very valuable. The Russian government is very interested in obtaining and using this artifact. There are rumors in Ukrainian special forces circles that there are agents of the Russian Ministry of Defence in the Zone, whose only task is to search for and transport the "Golden Fish" to a special laboratory outside the Alienation Zone. The artifact creates a gravitational field of singularity, which affects all objects around it. It also creates a kind of protective film around the owner, which has good qualities of fire resistance, and also protects against acid by decomposing acid-containing elements into simpler compounds. The artifact is very heavy and should not be taken for long walks. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Goldfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Thorn»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_aac_descr">
		<text>"Thorn" in an artifact application container. "Thorn" is the result of interaction between Burnt Fuzz anomaly and the body of a careless stalker. The Thorn artefact pokes the body of its owner, no matter what. But it also helps clean the body of radionuclide. Quite widespread and cheap.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Thorn»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Crystal»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_aac_descr">
		<text>"Crystal" in an aartifact application container. This artifact is like cheese mixed with sapphire stones. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so skillfully processed you can extract non-radioactive blue inclusions used by jewelers to make precious objects. The usefulness of the artifact is not limited to its industrial application. There is scientific evidence that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Because of its high density, it weighs heavily even when compared to other anomalous formations in the Zone. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Crystal»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Fireball»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_aac_descr">
		<text>"Fireball" in an artifact application container. Spherical artifact formed in thermal anomalies from reddish crystals. It has a constant temperature of 24 degrees Celsius, regardless of the surrounding conditions. This allows it to absorb heat in close proximity to itself and create, as if a small thermal barrier around the owner, which protects against contact with flames and high temperatures. Constant temperature is also a consequence of another positive effect: it speeds up the healing rate of wounds and stops bleeding. The artifact will also protect the wearer from acid burns, but it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies with the activated artifact, as this will increase the negative impact of acids and toxins on the wearer's blood. It also makes the possessor vulnerable to electricity. It's very heavy because of the high density of the crystal structure. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Fireball»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Mama's Beads»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_aac_descr">
		<text>"Mama's beads" in an artifact application container. Has the form of a spiral of DNA, "Mom's beads" are formed in fire anomalies. A characteristic feature is the constant pulsation and radiation of waves that are beneficial to the body: increase metabolism, accelerate wound healing. The consequences of using this artifact are not yet known. "Mama's beads also have powerful protective properties: they can protect the body from high temperatures and acid.   However, care should be taken when using this artifact in acidic and toxic environments, it should be considered that its use increases the corrosive wear of equipment and mechanisms in such conditions. It also increases conductivity, which increases the risk of electric shock when worn on the belt during a storm or from an electrical anomaly. Sufficiently high weight due to high density of the artifact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Mama's Beads»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Eye»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_aac_descr">
		<text>"Eye" in an artifact application container. This artifact really does look like an eye. In injuries, it speeds up metabolic processes, which promotes rapid healing of wounds. In addition, among the experienced stalkers there is a belief that the "Eye" is able to bring good luck. True or not, its positive effects are really quite powerful. Firstly, it reduces body temperature, secondly, it provides protection against any kind of acids, thirdly, it reduces pain and is extremely useful in the treatment of wounds. Many stalkers say that even hopeless wounds from mutants heal in front of their eyes, many managed to survive without bandages only using this artifact. However, the artifact is dangerous to use in chemical anomalies, it is better to keep it in a backpack. People sometimes call it "Copper Eye" because it conducts electricity well and increases its impact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Eye»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Flame»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_aac_descr">
		<text>"Flame" in an artifact application container. It is formed in areas of high thermal activity. It is characterized by intense infrared radiation, which accelerates the process of blood clotting in open wounds. Due to the great rarity of this artifact, its cost is extremely high. When used, it reduces the body temperature of the owner, which is very useful in areas of high temperatures. It also acts as a powerful insulator and suppresses some of the effects of acids. The effect of healing wounds is very strong, some stalkers said that they managed to survive even after biting chimera. Many stalkers and veteran hunters managed to survive this artifact. Has side effects: it is suicide to enter into toxic or acid anomalies with the artifact on your body. It increases the corrosiveness of toxic particles and the negative impact of chemicals on the owner's blood. It can be used instead of a first aid kit, as wound healing is very fast. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flame»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Stone Blood»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_aac_descr">
		<text>"Stone Blood" in an applied artifact container. It is a reddish formation of compressed and fossilized plant remains, soil and animal remains. It has the ability to partially neutralize chemical substances harmful to humans, absorbing them and reducing the overall level of toxicity in the owner's blood. Quite widespread and not particularly effective, as after its use chemical burns fester. It can catch fire from an open flame or even spontaneously ignite. Increases the negative impact of psi waves and is a powerful electrical conductor. It also absorbs energy when worn on the belt. "Blood Stone, however, speeds up wound healing well because of its organic nature. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Blood»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Meat Chunk»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_aac_descr">
		<text>"Meat Chunk" in an applied artifact container. This artifact has a soft, porous structure and is said to shrink like a sponge. When exposed to certain external conditions, it reveals its special characteristics. First, it emits the smell of burning flesh when it is near a heat source. Prolonged heating can ignite it. Although objects near an artifact are more likely to ignite, it remains intact. In this way it can be said that the "Meat Scrap" absorbs heat and transmits it to the surrounding objects. Secondly, the pores on the surface of the artifact absorb toxicity from the environment. Thirdly, when in contact with psi-anomalies or psi waves of different nature, it absorbs part of the field energy, but at the same time emits strong radiation. Fourthly, it conducts electricity in the same way as any flesh of living creatures. Many stalkers reported that they felt exhausted even with the short-term use of the artifact. However, its most useful property is to slowly close wounds and repair damaged tissue. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Meat Chunk»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Soul»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_aac_descr">
		<text>"Soul" in an artifact application container. A unique organic artifact with unique properties - secrets slime, which is unknown yet, increases the overall rate of recovery of the body after injuries of any nature. Due to its pleasant appearance and reasonable price, it is of particular interest for collectors. Because of its organic nature, the "Soul" is easily inflammable and should not be kept near a fire or sources of intense heat. It is known that it ignites at temperatures above 60 degrees Celsius. The artifact provides good chemical and toxic protection by absorbing the chemicals it uses to form mucus. It also increases the effects of psi waves on the host body and increases damage from electricity. The density of the structure is low, so it's not very heavy. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Soul»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Kolobok»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_aac_descr">
		<text>The "Kolobok" is in an artifact application container. Quite a rare artifact formed in areas of high chemical contamination. It is highly valued for its ability to "spur" the body so that it can recover from injuries of any degree of severity within minutes. Scientists are spreading information about the effects of an artifact on the owner's genetic material; however, this is not yet confirmed and should be seen as an attempt to monopolize the supply of the artifact by the scientific community. But one should not assume that the artifact is absolutely harmless. One disadvantage is that it increases electrical conductivity, so it is better to avoid electrical anomalies. Also reduces energy recovery, but it is unlikely to flow from its properties, but rather affects the strong injections from its needles when used. Needles contribute to the rapid healing of wounds, but cause constant pain and itching, thus reducing endurance. It has a negative impact on the protection against psyche waves coming from anomalies or mutants, as well as protection from heat and acids because of its rapid flammability. Given its chemical origin, it is well known that an artifact can enhance the owner's protection against toxicity. It is light and does not take up much space. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Kolobok»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Bubble»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_aac_descr">
		<text>"Bubble" in an artifact application container. The artifact is a few hollow formations of organic nature connected to each other. It emits a gaseous substance capable of neutralizing chemical or toxic particles in the human body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand but also has numerous negative properties. For example, it significantly enhances the effect of psi waves, as well as the fields created by mutants and anomalies. Many stalkers told us that when they had a "Bubble", the effect of psi radiation was so powerful that the only thing they could do was to scream as hard as they could. This also applies to the Electro - the artifact conducts electricity and increases the current by many times. The only positive aspect of this artifact is that it speeds up wound healing. This property makes it very expensive on the artifact market, it is in demand. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact can be easily ignited, like other organic formations, it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of thermal and acid anomalies. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Bubble»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Firefly»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_aac_descr">
		<text>"Firefly" in an artifact application container. This artifact works with fields inaccessible to science, accelerating the regeneration of tissues and organs of living creatures, and normalizing metabolic processes. It can literally put a man with serious wounds on his feet before his eyes. Unfortunately, this artifact is extremely rare. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact is much more likely to ignite spontaneously than any other organic artifact, so it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of fire and acid anomalies. The artifact also significantly increases the harmful effects of psi radiation and several times increases the effect of electric current on the host body. Many have also noticed that it reduces endurance and fatigue somewhat. But in spite of all this, the artifact will suck all lethal doses of chemical poisoning from the host body, in addition, excellent protection against toxicity. It is in demand in military circles, because it allows to conduct attacks with biological and chemical weapons with the least casualties. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Firefly»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Sparkler»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_aac_descr">
		<text>"Sparkler" in an artifact application container. It looks like a semitransparent spider web. It is as sticky as the protein spider web and has glue properties. Most often it can be found in the vicinity of electrical anomalies, which certainly affects their characteristics: it can smooth out voltage differences in the electric field, which protects the owner from the electric field. Also slightly protects against psi-radiated anomalies of psi waves of mutants. Due to its electrical nature, it is a weak source of energy. It has no healing properties, but the liquid formed by the artifact damages the skin and prevents blood clotting. It is lightweight. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Sparkler»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Flash»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_aac_descr">
		<text>"Flash" in an artifact application container. This artifact is very similar to "Moonlight" and resembles a ball filled with plasma. As you know, when used, it extinguishes the harmful effects of psi-anomalies or psi waves of some mutants. The "Flash" acts as a capacitor and will absorb even lethal blows of electricity. However, it is important to note that a "Flash" can cause a small shock when it comes into contact with electricity. It has weak regenerative properties, so it even prevents wound healing. It should be used with care when wounds and bleeding. Very lightweight and compact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flash»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Moonlight»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_aac_descr">
		<text>"Moonlight" in an artifact application container. This artifact of electrostatic nature demonstrates the ability to resonate under the influence of psi waves. Over time, stalkers have learned to adjust Moonlight to resonate in the phase with the main source of radiation, thus completely or significantly neutralizing the psy-wave effect. This artifact ball also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high voltages. It also increases energy and endurance, allowing the wearer to feel full of energy. A side effect is that the rate of healing of wounds decreases. The artifact is very light and compact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Moonlight»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Battery»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_aac_descr">
		<text>"Battery" in an artifact application container. This artifact provides a little more protection from psi fields than his younger brother Moonlight. The artifact includes electrostatic elements, but scientists are still unable to determine the nature of its formation. It is quite popular in the Zone, valued for its active properties, although it has side effects on the owner's body when used for a long time. It should be noted that this artifact prevents blood clotting and increases bleeding from existing wounds. On the other hand, being a powerful insulator, it provides good protection against high energy discharges. This artifact is also very light and compact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Battery»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Shell»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_aac_descr">
		<text>"Shell" in an artifact application container. This artifact consists of two discs in a bluish color, bound together by a translucent material of unknown nature. This strange artifact has been considered devoid of any useful properties for a long time. Only recently has it been discovered that it provides all the high levels of protection against psi-effects, partially absorbing them. It also absorbs electromagnetic interference and acts like an earthing switch.  When the artifact reacts with the body, the body's endurance increases and the wearer begins to feel younger. For some stalkers, it can be hyperactive. One drawback to this artifact is that it reduces the number of platelets in the blood and thus increases the rate of bleeding. It's very light and compact. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Shell»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Snowflake»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_aac_descr">
		<text>"Snowflake" in an artifact application container. Also known as the Radioactive Snowflake. The artifact looks like a "Snowflake"; there is a perception that it is a kind of "Snowflake" as it significantly increases its resistance to electric current by creating its own field that absorbs electricity. Thanks to its unique properties, the artifact is able to dramatically increase the muscle tone of the carrier, thereby increasing endurance. Increased radioactivity (the source of which is still unknown to science) also affects the carrier, so stalkers jokingly call it "Radioactive Snowflake". When used, it is worth weighing all the pros and cons: get high endurance and protection from electricity at the cost of high radiation. Use in combat also remains a controversial issue, as its use increases bleeding from wounds and prevents healing of wounds due to the burning outer shell, irritating the skin. It is very light and does not take up much space. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Snowflake»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Compass»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_aac_descr">
		<text>"Compass" in an artifact application container. A rare artifact - last found many months ago. It has the ability to show ruptures in abnormal fields. It is said to be able to pass by the most difficult anomalies without the slightest risk, but very few people know how to handle it. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Compass»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Heart of the Oasis»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_aac_descr">
		<text>"Heart of the Oasis" in an artifact application container. An artifact from the heart of the legendary Oasis. Apparently, it is a crystallized plant, which has adopted the characteristic property of the Oasis beneficial to the body as a whole. It's exceptionally radioactive, unlike the Oasis itself. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Heart of the Oasis»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Altered Insulator»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_aac_descr">
		<text>"Altered insulator" in the artifact application container. This thing is something remotely reminiscent of an ordinary electrical insulator. Now, under the influence of abnormal fields, the Alienation Zone is an artifact of unstable nature. Judging by its effects on the body, it's the source of intermittent psy waves. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Insulator»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] extremely radioactive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_aac_name">
		<text>AAC with «Altered Wheel»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_aac_descr">
		<text>"Altered helm" in the artifact application container. This is what's left of the usual ship's helm. Now it's an artifact of a strange nature. There are no outstanding properties, except a little glow and a lot of radioactivity. The emitted particles barely penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Wheel»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] extremely radioactive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Jellyfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_aam_descr">
		<text>"Jellyfish" in the artifact application module. Gravity artifact of nature, which has the ability to actively attract and absorb radioactive and chemical particles, thereby reducing the irradiation of the body and reducing toxic poisoning on the body. Widely distributed in the Zone; outside the Zone, it is widely, though covertly, used in the treatment of acute radiation sickness and deadly chemical poisoning. This artifact is very heavy. It protects the carrier a little from elevated temperatures and abnormal acids. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Jellyfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Stone Flower»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_aam_descr">
		<text>"Stone flower" in the artifact application module. This artifact is like cheese mixed with sapphire stones. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so skillfully processed it is possible to extract non-radioactive blue impregnations used by jewelers to make precious objects. The usefulness of the artifact is not limited to its industrial application. There is scientific evidence that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Because of its high density, it weighs heavily even when compared to other anomalous formations in the Zone. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Flower»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Night star»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_aam_descr">
		<text>"Night Star" in the artifact application module. A luminous artifact capable of generating a gravity field around itself, which increases its mass. For this reason, it's very heavy, but provides protection against acids and heat. Due to its beautiful inner core is very appreciated by jewelers all over the world, but care should be taken when processing it, as improper polishing of the artifact can lead to an explosion that can destroy a small building. The Night Star will also absorb toxic and chemical substances from the environment, making it valuable among artefact hunters, although the absorption of toxins is negligible. It's quite cheap, so even stalkers with a limited budget can afford to buy this artifact. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Night star»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Wrenched»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_aam_descr">
		<text>"Wrenched" in the artifact application module. An artifact with a bizarre shape that occurs in areas of high gravitational activity. It is a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements. Equally successfully protects its carrier from the external effects of toxic substances, as well as from chemical particles that have already entered the body. It looks like coral, thanks to the inorganic nature of non-combustible, which provides adequate protection against heat and acids. No one is particularly interested in this artifact, so it is mainly bought up by scientists who are experimentally trying to find use of its properties. It has a high density, so it is very heavy. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Wrenched»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Gravi»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_aam_descr">
		<text>"Gravi" in the artifact application module. An artifact is formed under prolonged gravitational action on metal-containing substances. It is able to maintain a small gravitational field around itself, in particular increases the weight of all objects in the immediate vicinity. For a long time the nature of the artifact was not clear until the scientist Sakharov on Amber found that "Gravi" produces fields of gravity component at intervals of 30 minutes. Due to this property, the artifact increases the weight of objects and also emits lethal doses of radiation. But on the other hand, it protects the possessor from fire anomalies and acids from chemical and toxic anomalies. But it does not absorb chemical toxins, and enters into compounds with them, dividing them into more simple substances due to the peculiarities of its field. Some have expressed concern that this artifact could be used as a basis for weapons of mass destruction. There are rumours that the Russian Federation is conducting studies on the possibility of using Gravi as a weapon. The artifact is very heavy, so it is not recommended to take it on long walks. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Gravi»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Goldfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_aam_descr">
		<text>"Goldfish" in the artifact application module. All its properties were discovered by the scientist Sakharov at Yantar after a massive discharge. After his careful research, it was found that this artifact is formed after the merger of the three "Graves" at the level of interaction of singular fields. This phenomenon is extremely rare, as a result of which the artifact is very valuable. The Russian government is very interested in receiving and using this artifact. There are rumors in Ukrainian Special Forces circles that there are agents of the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation in the Zone whose sole task is to search for and transport the Golden Fish to the Special. laboratories outside the Exclusion Zone. The artifact creates a gravitational field of singularity that affects all objects around it. It also creates a kind of protective film around the owner, which has good fire resistance properties, and also protects against acid due to the decomposition of acid-containing elements into simpler compounds. The artifact is very heavy, it is not recommended to take with you on long walks. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Goldfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Thorn»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_aam_descr">
		<text>"Thorn" in the artifact application module. "Thorn" is the result of interaction between Burnt Fuzz anomaly and the body of a careless stalker. The Thorn artefact pokes the body of its owner, no matter what. But it also helps clean the body of radionuclide. Quite widespread and cheap.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Thorn»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Crystal»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_aam_descr">
		<text>"Crystal" in the artifact application module. This artifact resembles cheese mixed with sapphire stones. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so with skillful processing you can extract non-radioactive blue blotches used by jewelers for the manufacture of precious products. The usefulness of an artifact is not limited to its industrial use. There are scientifically proven facts that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Due to its high density, it is significant in weight even in comparison with other abnormal formations of the Zone. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Crystal»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Fireball»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_aam_descr">
		<text>"Fireball" in the artifact application module. A spherical artifact formed in thermal anomalies from reddish crystals. It has a constant temperature of 24 degrees Celsius, regardless of the surrounding conditions. This allows him to absorb heat in close proximity to himself and create, as it were, a small thermal barrier around the holder, which protects against contact with the flame and high temperatures. Constant temperature is also the result of another positive effect: it accelerates the rate of wound healing and stops bleeding. Also, the artifact will protect the owner from acid burns, but it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies with the activated artifact, because this will increase the negative effects of acids and toxins on the wearer's blood. Also makes the wearer vulnerable to electricity. Very heavy due to the high density of the crystalline structure. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Fireball»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Mama's Beads»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_aam_descr">
		<text>"Mama’s beads" in the artifact application module. It has the shape of a DNA helix, "Mother's beads" are formed in fiery anomalies. A characteristic feature is the constant pulsation and emission of waves that have a beneficial effect on the body: increase metabolism, accelerate wound healing. The consequences of using this artifact are still unknown. "Mother's beads" also have powerful protective properties: they are able to protect the body from exposure to high temperatures and acid. However, caution should be exercised when used in acidic and toxic environments, it is worth considering that its use of an artifact increases the corrosive wear of equipment and mechanisms in such conditions. It also increases electrical conductivity, which increases the risk of electric shock when worn on the belt during a storm or from an electrical anomaly. Fairly high weight due to the high density of the artifact. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Mama's Beads»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Eye»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_aam_descr">
		<text>"Eye" in the artifact application module. This artifact externally really resembles an organ of vision. With injuries, it accelerates the metabolism, which contributes to the rapid healing of wounds. In addition, among experienced stalkers there is a belief that the "Eye" is able to bring good luck. True or not, but its positive effects are really quite powerful. Firstly, it lowers body temperature, secondly it provides protection against any kind of acid, thirdly it reduces pain and is extremely useful in the treatment of wounds. Many stalkers say that even the hopeless wounds received from mutants heal in front of our eyes, many managed to survive without bandages only using this artifact. However, it is dangerous to use an artifact in chemical anomalies; it is better to keep it in a backpack. The people sometimes call the "Copper Eye", because conducts electricity well and enhances its effect. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Eye»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Flame»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_aam_descr">
		<text>"Flame" in the artifact application module. Formed in areas of increased thermal activity. It is characterized by intense infrared radiation, under the influence of which the process of blood coagulation in open wounds is accelerated. Due to the rarity of this artifact, its cost is extremely high. When used, it reduces the body temperature of the wearer, which is very useful in areas of elevated temperatures. It also acts as a powerful insulator and suppresses some effects from acids. The wound healing effect is very strong, some stalkers said that they managed to survive even after being bitten by a chimera. Many stalkers and veteran hunters managed to survive thanks to this artifact. It has side effects: entering into toxic or acid abnormalities with an artifact on the body is suicide. It increases the corrosiveness of toxic particles and the negative effects of chemicals on the blood of the owner. It can be used instead of a first aid kit, as wound healing is very fast. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flame»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Stone Blood»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_aam_descr">
		<text>"Stone Blood" in the artifact application module. It is a reddish formation from compressed and petrified remains of plants, soil and animal remains. It has the ability to partially neutralize chemicals harmful to humans, absorbing them and reducing the overall level of toxicity in the blood of the owner. Quite common and not very effective, because after using it, chemical burns fester. May catch fire from exposure to an open flame or even spontaneously ignite. Increases the negative effects of psi waves and is a powerful conductor of electricity. Also absorbs energy when worn on a belt. Blood of Stone, however, accelerates wound healing well due to its organic nature. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Blood»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Meat Chunk»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_aam_descr">
		<text>"Meat Chunk" in the artifact application module. This artifact has a soft, porous structure and, as they say, can shrink, resembling a sponge. Under the influence of certain external conditions, he reveals his special characteristics. Firstly, being near a heat source emits the smell of burning flesh. Prolonged heating may ignite it. Although objects near an artifact are more often ignited, it remains intact. Thus, it can be argued that the "Chunk of Meat" absorbs heat and transfers it to surrounding objects. Secondly, pores on the surface of an artifact absorb environmental toxicity. Thirdly, in contact with psi anomalies or psi waves of various nature, it absorbs part of the field energy, but at the same time emits strong radiation. Fourth, it conducts electricity just like any flesh of living things. Many stalkers reported feeling exhausted even with short-term use of the artifact. However, its most useful property is that it slowly closes wounds and restores damaged tissue. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Meat Chunk»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Soul»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_aam_descr">
		<text>"Soul" in the artifact application module. A unique organic artifact with unique properties - secretes mucus, which until now in an unknown way increases the overall speed of the body's recovery after injuries of any nature. Due to its pleasant appearance and reasonable price, it is of particular interest to collectors. Due to its organic nature, the “Soul” is highly flammable; it should not be kept near a fire or sources of strong heat. It is known to ignite at temperatures above 60 degrees Celsius. The artifact provides good chemical and toxic protection by absorbing the chemicals that it uses to form mucus. Also increases the effect of psi waves on the body of the carrier and increases the damage from electricity. The density of the structure is low, therefore, not very heavy. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Soul»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Kolobok»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_aam_descr">
		<text>"Kolobok" in the application module of artifacts. A fairly rare artifact that forms in areas of severe chemical pollution. It is highly appreciated for the ability to “boost” the body so that it recovers in a matter of minutes after injuries of any severity. Scientists disseminate information about the effects of the artifact on the owner’s genetic material; however, there is no confirmation of this yet and it should be considered as an attempt to monopolize the supply of the artifact by the scientific community. But you should not assume that the artifact is absolutely harmless. One of the drawbacks is that it increases electrical conductivity, so it is better to avoid electrical anomalies. It also lowers energy recovery, but it hardly arises from its properties, but rather affects the strong injections from its needles when used. Needles contribute to the rapid healing of wounds, but cause constant pain and itching, thereby reducing stamina. Negatively affects the protection against psi waves emanating from anomalies or mutants, as well as the protection against exposure to heat and acids due to its rapid inflammability. Given its chemical origin, the ability of an artifact to increase the wearer's protection against toxicity is well known. Lightweight and does not take up much space. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Kolobok»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Bubble»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_aam_descr">
		<text>"Bubble" in the artifact application module. The artifact is a few hollow formations of organic nature, interconnected. It releases a gaseous substance capable of neutralizing chemical or toxic particles in the human body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand, but it also has numerous negative properties. For example, significantly enhances the effect of psi waves, as well as from the fields created by mutants and anomalies. Many stalkers said that when the Bubble was on them, the influence of psi radiation was so powerful that the only thing they could do was shout at as much as they could. This also applies to "Electr" - the artifact conducts electricity and increases the current strength at times. The only positive aspect of this artifact is that it accelerates wound healing. This property makes it very expensive in the artifact market, it is in demand. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container. ATTENTION: Due to its organic nature and instability, this artifact can easily ignite, like other organic formations, it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of thermal and acid anomalies. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Bubble»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Firefly»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_aam_descr">
		<text>"Firefly" in the artifact application module. This artifact works with fields inaccessible to science, accelerating the regeneration of tissues and organs of living creatures, as well as normalizing metabolic processes. Able to literally put a seriously wounded person on his feet. Unfortunately, this artifact is extremely rare. ATTENTION: Due to its organic nature and instability, this artifact is much more often spontaneously ignited than any other organic artifacts, therefore it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of fire and acid anomalies. Also, the artifact significantly enhances the harmful effects of psi radiation and several times enhances the effect of electric current on the body of the carrier. Many also noticed that when used, endurance and fatigue are somewhat reduced. But despite all this, the artifact will suck out all lethal doses of chemical poisoning from the body of the carrier, in addition, it will perfectly protect against toxicity. It is in demand in military circles, because it allows terrorist attacks using biological and chemical weapons with the least losses. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Firefly»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_aam_name">
		<text>AAAM with «Sparkler»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_aam_descr">
		<text>"Sparkler" in the artifact application module. It looks like a semitransparent web. It is as sticky as the protein spider web and has glue properties. Most often it can be found in the vicinity of electrical anomalies, which certainly affects their characteristics: it can smooth out voltage differences in the electric field, which protects the owner from the electric field. Also slightly protects against psi-radiated anomalies of psi waves of mutants. Due to its electrical nature, it is a weak source of energy. It has no healing properties, but the liquid formed by the artifact damages the skin and prevents blood clotting. It is lightweight. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Sparkler»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Flash»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_aam_descr">
		<text>"Flash" in the artifact application module. This artifact is very similar to "Moonlight" and resembles a ball filled with plasma. As you know, when used, it extinguishes the harmful effects of psi-anomalies or psi waves of some mutants. The "Flash" acts as a capacitor and will absorb even lethal blows of electricity. However, it is important to note that a "Flash" can cause a slight shock when it comes into contact with electricity. It has weak regenerative properties, so it even prevents wound healing. It should be used with care when wounds and bleeding. Very lightweight and compact. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flash»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Moonlight»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_aam_descr">
		<text>"Moonlight" in the artifact application module. This artifact of electrostatic nature demonstrates the ability to resonate under the influence of psi waves. Over time, stalkers have learned to adjust Moonlight to resonate in the phase with the main source of radiation, thus completely or significantly neutralizing the psy-wave effect. This artifact ball also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high voltages. It also increases energy and endurance, allowing the wearer to feel full of energy. A side effect is that the rate of healing of wounds decreases. The artifact is very light and compact. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Moonlight»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Battery»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_aam_descr">
		<text>"Battery" in the artifact application module. This artifact provides a little more protection against psi fields than his younger brother Moonlight. The artifact includes electrostatic elements, but scientists are still unable to determine the nature of its formation. It is quite popular in the Zone, valued for its active properties, although it has side effects on the owner's body when used for a long time. It should be noted that this artifact prevents blood clotting and increases bleeding from existing wounds. On the other hand, being a powerful insulator, it provides good protection against high energy discharges. This artifact is also very light and compact. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Battery»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Shell»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_aam_descr">
		<text>"Shell" in the artifact application module. This artifact consists of two discs in a bluish color, bound together by a translucent material of unknown nature. This strange artifact has been considered devoid of any useful properties for a long time. Only recently has it been discovered that it provides all the high levels of protection against psi-effects, partially absorbing them. It also absorbs electromagnetic interference and acts like an earthing switch.  When the artifact reacts with the body, the body's endurance increases and the wearer begins to feel younger. For some stalkers, it can be hyperactive. One drawback to this artifact is that it reduces the number of platelets in the blood and thus increases the rate of bleeding. It's very light and compact. The emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Shell»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Snowflake»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_aam_descr">
		<text>"Snowflake" in the artifact application module. Also known as the Radioactive Snowflake. The artifact looks like a "Snowflake"; there is a perception that it is a kind of "Snowflake" as it significantly increases its resistance to electric current by creating its own field that absorbs electricity. Thanks to its unique properties, the artifact is able to dramatically increase the muscle tone of the carrier, thereby increasing endurance. Increased radioactivity (the source of which is still unknown to science) also affects the carrier, so stalkers jokingly call it "Radioactive Snowflake". When used, it is worth weighing all the pros and cons: get high endurance and protection from electricity at the cost of high radiation. Use in combat also remains a controversial issue, as its use increases bleeding from wounds and prevents healing of wounds due to the burning outer shell, irritating the skin. It is very light and does not take up much space. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Snowflake»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Compass»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_aam_descr">
		<text>"Compass" in the artifact application module. A rare artifact - last found many months ago. It has the ability to show ruptures in anomalous fields. They say it can be used to pass by the most difficult anomalies without the slightest risk, but very few people know how to handle it. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Compass»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Heart of the Oasis»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_aam_descr">
		<text>"Heart of the Oasis" in the artifact application module. An artifact from the heart of the legendary Oasis. Apparently, it is a crystallized plant, which has adopted the inherent property of the Oasis beneficial to the body as a whole. It's exceptionally radioactive, unlike the Oasis itself. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Heart of the Oasis»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Altered Insulator»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_aam_descr">
		<text>"Altered isolator" in the artifact application module. This thing is something remotely reminiscent of an ordinary electrical insulator. Now, under the influence of abnormal fields, the Alienation Zone is an artifact of unstable nature. Judging by its effects on the body, it's the source of intermittent psy waves. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Insulator»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] extremely radioactive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_aam_name">
		<text>AAM with «Altered Wheel»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_aam_descr">
		<text>"Altered Wheel" in the artifact application module. That's what's left of the normal ship's helm. Now it's an artifact of a strange nature. There are no outstanding properties, except a little glow and a lot of radioactivity. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] high-quality product\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Wheel»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] possible to attach to suit\n%c[ui_red] • %c[default] extremely radioactive</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Jellyfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Jellyfish" in a lead-insulated metal container. Gravity artifact of nature, which has the ability to actively attract and absorb radioactive and chemical particles, thereby reducing the irradiation of the body and reducing toxic poisoning on the body. Widely distributed in the Zone; outside the Zone, it is widely, though covertly, used in the treatment of acute radiation sickness and deadly chemical poisoning. This artifact is very heavy. It protects the carrier a little from elevated temperatures and abnormal acids. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Jellyfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Stone Flower»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Stone flower" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact is like cheese mixed with sapphire stones. Only the outer shell of the artifact emits radiation, so skillfully processed it is possible to extract non-radioactive blue inclusions used by jewelers to make precious objects. The usefulness of the artifact is not limited to its industrial application. There is scientific evidence that sapphire stones protect against toxicity, while the outer shell of the artifact increases resistance to high temperatures. Because of its high density, it weighs heavily even when compared to other anomalous formations in the Zone. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Flower»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Night star»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Night Star" in a lead-insulated metal container. A luminous artifact capable of generating a gravitational field around itself, which increases its mass. For this reason, it's very heavy, but provides protection against acids and heat. Thanks to its beautiful inner core, it is very appreciated by jewelers all over the world, but care should be taken when processing it, as improper polishing of the artifact can cause an explosion that can destroy a small building. The Night Star will also absorb toxic and chemical substances from the environment, making it valuable among artefact hunters, although the absorption of toxins is negligible. It's quite cheap, so even stalkers with a limited budget can afford to buy this artifact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Night star»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Wrenched»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Wrenched" in a lead-insulated metal container. An artifact of bizarre shape arising in places of high gravitational activity. It is a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements. Equally successfully protects its carrier from the external effects of toxic substances, as well as from chemical particles that have already entered the body. It looks like coral, thanks to the inorganic nature of non-combustible, which provides adequate protection against heat and acids. No one is particularly interested in this artifact, so it is mainly bought up by scientists who are experimentally trying to find use of its properties. It has a high density, so it is very heavy. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Wrenched»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Gravi»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Gravi" in a lead-insulated metal container. The artifact is formed under prolonged gravitational action on metal-containing substances. It is able to maintain a small gravitational field around itself, in particular increases the weight of all objects in its immediate vicinity. For a long time, the nature of the artifact was not clear until the scientist Sakharov on Amber found that "Gravi" produces fields of gravity component at intervals of 30 minutes. Due to this property, the artifact increases the weight of objects and also emits lethal doses of radiation. But on the other hand, it protects the possessor from fire anomalies and acids from chemical and toxic anomalies. But it does not absorb chemical toxins, and enters into compounds with them, dividing them into more simple substances due to the peculiarities of its field. Some have expressed concern that this artifact could be used as a basis for weapons of mass destruction. There are rumours that the Russian Federation is conducting studies on the possibility of using Gravi as a weapon. The artifact is very heavy, so it is not recommended to take it on long walks. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Gravi»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Goldfish»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Goldfish" in a lead-insulated metal container. All its properties were discovered by Sakharov on Amber after a massive ejection. After his careful research, it was found that this artifact is formed after the merger of the three "Gravi" at the level of interaction of singular fields. This phenomenon is very rare and therefore the artifact is very valuable. The Russian government is very interested in obtaining and using this artifact. There are rumors in Ukrainian special forces circles that there are agents of the Russian Ministry of Defence in the Zone, whose only task is to search for and transport the "Golden Fish" to a special laboratory outside the Alienation Zone. The artifact creates a gravitational field of singularity, which affects all objects around it. It also creates a kind of protective film around the owner, which has good qualities of fire resistance, and also protects against acid by decomposing acid-containing elements into simpler compounds. The artifact is very heavy and should not be taken for long walks. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Goldfish»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Thorn»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_rusty_thorn_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Thorn" in a lead-insulated metal container. "Thorn" is the result of interaction between Burnt Fuzz anomaly and the body of a careless stalker. The Thorn artefact pokes the body of its owner, no matter what. But it also helps clean the body of radionuclide. Quite widespread and cheap.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Thorn»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Crystal»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Crystal" in a lead-insulated metal container. The artifact occurs in abnormal areas under the influence of high temperatures. It actively absorbs excess heat from the space around it, while remaining cool to the touch. It will also protect the owner in toxic and acid anomalies. On the other hand, the presence of such an environment increases the impact of acid on corrosion of mechanisms. All pros and cons of artifacts in toxic areas should be considered. Acts as a good electrical conductor. Accelerates blood coagulation if applied close to the body (Note: it is not recommended to leave the artifact on the body for a long time, as the resulting blood clots may be dangerous to health). This artifact is also in demand by jewelers outside the Zone, as its inner core is not radioactive and is very beautiful if it is skillfully worked on. The outside is covered with a very hard layer of 10 mm, which emits most of the radiation. It's relatively heavy because of its high density. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Crystal»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Fireball»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Fireball" in a lead-insulated metal container. Spherical artifact formed in thermal anomalies from reddish crystals. It has a constant temperature of 24 degrees Celsius, regardless of the surrounding conditions. This allows it to absorb heat in close proximity to itself and create, as if a small thermal barrier around the owner, which protects against contact with flames and high temperatures. Constant temperature is also a consequence of another positive effect: it speeds up the healing rate of wounds and stops bleeding. The artifact will also protect the wearer from acid burns, but it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies with the activated artifact, as this will increase the negative impact of acids and toxins on the wearer's blood. It also makes the possessor vulnerable to electricity. It's very heavy because of the high density of the crystal structure. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Fireball»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Mama's Beads»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Mama's beads" in a lead-insulated metal container. Has the form of a spiral of DNA, "Mom's beads" are formed in fire anomalies. A characteristic feature is the constant pulsation and radiation of waves, useful for the body: increase metabolism, accelerate wound healing. The consequences of using this artifact are not yet known. "Mama's beads also have powerful protective properties: they can protect the body from high temperatures and acid.   However, care should be taken when using this artifact in acidic and toxic environments, it should be considered that its use increases the corrosive wear of equipment and mechanisms in such conditions. It also increases conductivity, which increases the risk of electric shock when worn on the belt during a storm or from an electrical anomaly. Sufficiently high weight due to high density of the artifact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Mama's Beads»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Eye»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Eye" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact really looks like the eye. In injuries, it accelerates metabolic processes, which promotes rapid healing of wounds. In addition, among the experienced stalkers there is a belief that the "Eye" is able to bring good luck. True or not, its positive effects are really quite powerful. Firstly, it reduces body temperature, secondly, it provides protection against any kind of acids, thirdly, it reduces pain and is extremely useful in the treatment of wounds. Many stalkers say that even hopeless wounds from mutants heal in front of their eyes, many managed to survive without bandages only using this artifact. However, the artifact is dangerous to use in chemical anomalies, it is better to keep it in a backpack. People sometimes call it "Copper Eye" because it conducts electricity well and increases its impact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Eye»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Flame»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Flame" in a lead-insulated metal container. It is formed in areas of high thermal activity. It is characterized by intense infrared radiation, which accelerates the process of blood clotting in open wounds. Due to the great rarity of this artifact, its cost is extremely high. When used, it reduces the body temperature of the owner, which is very useful in areas of high temperatures. It also acts as a powerful insulator and suppresses some of the effects of acids. The effect of healing wounds is very strong, some stalkers said that they managed to survive even after biting chimera. Many stalkers and veteran hunters managed to survive this artifact. Has side effects: it is suicide to enter into toxic or acid anomalies with the artifact on your body. It increases the corrosiveness of toxic particles and the negative impact of chemicals on the owner's blood. It can be used instead of a first aid kit, as wound healing is very fast. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flame»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Stone Blood»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Stone Blood" in a lead-insulated metal container. It is a reddish formation of compressed and fossilized plant remains, soil and animal remains. It has the ability to partially neutralize chemicals harmful to humans, absorbing them and reducing the overall level of toxicity in the owner's blood. Quite widespread and not particularly effective, as after its use chemical burns fester. It can catch fire from an open flame or even spontaneously ignite. Increases the negative impact of psi waves and is a powerful electrical conductor. It also absorbs energy when worn on the belt. "Blood Stone, however, speeds up wound healing well because of its organic nature. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Stone Blood»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Meat Chunk»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Meat Chunk" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact has a soft, porous structure and is said to shrink like a sponge. When exposed to certain external conditions, it reveals its special characteristics. First, it emits the smell of burning flesh when it is near a heat source. Prolonged heating can ignite it. Although objects near an artifact are more likely to ignite, it remains intact. In this way it can be said that the "Meat Scrap" absorbs heat and transmits it to the surrounding objects. Secondly, the pores on the surface of the artifact absorb toxicity from the environment. Thirdly, when in contact with psi-anomalies or psi waves of different nature, it absorbs part of the field energy, but at the same time emits strong radiation. Fourthly, it conducts electricity in the same way as any flesh of living creatures. Many stalkers reported that they felt exhausted even with the short-term use of the artifact. However, its most useful property is to slowly close wounds and repair damaged tissue. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Meat Chunk»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Soul»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Soul" in a lead-insulated metal container. A unique organic artifact with unique properties - secrets slime, which is unknown yet, increases the overall rate of recovery of the body after injuries of any nature. Due to its pleasant appearance and reasonable price, it is of particular interest for collectors. Because of its organic nature, the "Soul" is easily inflammable and should not be kept near a fire or sources of intense heat. It is known that it ignites at temperatures above 60 degrees Celsius. The artifact provides good chemical and toxic protection by absorbing the chemicals it uses to form mucus. It also increases the effects of psi waves on the host body and increases damage from electricity. The density of the structure is low, so it's not very heavy. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Soul»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Kolobok»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Kolobok" in a lead-insulated metal container. Quite a rare artifact formed in areas of high chemical contamination. It is highly valued for its ability to "spur" the body so that it can recover from injuries of any degree of severity within minutes. Scientists are spreading information about the effects of an artifact on the owner's genetic material; however, this is not yet confirmed and should be seen as an attempt to monopolize the supply of the artifact by the scientific community. But one should not assume that the artifact is absolutely harmless. One disadvantage is that it increases electrical conductivity, so it is better to avoid electrical anomalies. Also reduces energy recovery, but it is unlikely to flow from its properties, but rather affects the strong injections from its needles when used. Needles contribute to the rapid healing of wounds, but cause constant pain and itching, thus reducing endurance. It has a negative impact on the protection against psyche waves coming from anomalies or mutants, as well as protection from heat and acids because of its rapid flammability. Given its chemical origin, it is well known that an artifact can enhance the owner's protection against toxicity. It is light and does not take up much space. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Kolobok»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Bubble»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Bubble" in a lead-insulated metal container. The artifact is a few hollow formations of organic nature connected to each other. It emits a gaseous substance capable of neutralizing chemical or toxic particles in the human body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand but also has numerous negative properties. For example, it significantly enhances the effect of psi waves, as well as the fields created by mutants and anomalies. Many stalkers told us that when they had a "Bubble", the effects of psi radiation were so powerful that the only thing they could do was to scream as hard as they could. This also applies to the Electro - the artifact conducts electricity and increases the current by many times. The only positive aspect of this artifact is that it speeds up wound healing. This property makes it very expensive on the artifact market, it is in demand. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact can be easily ignited, like other organic formations, it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of thermal and acid anomalies. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Bubble»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Firefly»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Firefly" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact works with fields inaccessible to science, accelerating the regeneration of tissues and organs of living creatures, and normalizing metabolic processes. It can literally put a man with serious wounds on his feet in front of his eyes. Unfortunately, this artifact is extremely rare. WARNING: Because of its organic nature and instability, this artifact is much more likely to ignite spontaneously than any other organic artifact, so it is recommended to refrain from using it in the immediate vicinity of fire and acid anomalies. The artifact also significantly increases the harmful effects of psi radiation and several times increases the effect of electric current on the host body. Many have also noticed that it reduces endurance and fatigue somewhat. But in spite of all this, the artifact will suck all lethal doses of chemical poisoning from the host body, in addition, excellent protection against toxicity. It is in demand in military circles, because it allows to conduct attacks with biological and chemical weapons with the least casualties. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Firefly»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Sparkler»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Sparkler" in a lead-insulated metal container. It looks like a semitransparent spider web. It is as sticky as a protein spider web and has glue properties. Most often it can be found in the vicinity of electrical anomalies, which certainly affects their characteristics: it can smooth out voltage differences in the electric field, which protects the owner from the electric field. Also slightly protects against psi-radiated anomalies of psi waves of mutants. Due to its electrical nature, it is a weak source of energy. It has no healing properties, but the liquid formed by the artifact damages the skin and prevents blood clotting. It is lightweight. Emitted particles practically do not penetrate through the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Sparkler»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Flash»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Flash" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact is very similar to "Moonlight" and resembles a ball filled with plasma. As you know, when used, it extinguishes harmful effects from psi-anomalies or psi waves of some mutants. The "Flash" acts as a capacitor and will absorb even lethal blows of electricity. However, it is important to note that a "Flash" can cause a small shock when it comes into contact with electricity. It has weak regenerative properties, so it even prevents wound healing. It should be used with care when wounds and bleeding. Very lightweight and compact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Flash»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Moonlight»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Moonlight" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact of electrostatic nature demonstrates the ability to resonate under the influence of psi waves. Over time, stalkers have learned to adjust Moonlight to resonate in the phase with the main source of radiation, thus completely or significantly neutralizing the psy-wave effect. This artifact ball also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high voltages. It also increases energy and endurance, allowing the wearer to feel full of energy. A side effect is that the rate of healing of wounds decreases. The artifact is very light and compact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Moonlight»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Battery»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Battery" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact provides a little more protection from psi fields than his younger brother Moonlight. The artifact includes electrostatic elements, but scientists are still unable to determine the nature of its formation. It is quite popular in the Zone, valued for its active properties, although it has side effects on the owner's body when used for a long time. It should be noted that this artifact prevents blood clotting and increases bleeding from existing wounds. On the other hand, being a powerful insulator, it provides good protection against high energy discharges. This artifact is also very light and compact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Battery»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Shell»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Shell" in a lead-insulated metal container. This artifact consists of two bluish discs bound together by a translucent material of unknown nature. This strange artifact has been considered devoid of any useful properties for a long time. Only recently has it been discovered that it provides all the high levels of protection against psi-effects, partially absorbing them. It also absorbs electromagnetic interference and acts like an earthing switch.  When the artifact reacts with the body, the body's endurance increases and the wearer begins to feel younger. For some stalkers, it can be hyperactive. One drawback to this artifact is that it reduces the number of platelets in the blood and thus increases the rate of bleeding. It's very light and compact. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Shell»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Snowflake»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Snowflake" in a lead-insulated metal container. Also known as "Radioactive Snowflake." The artifact looks like a "Snowflake"; there is a perception that it is a kind of "Snowflake" as it greatly increases its resistance to electric current by creating its own field that absorbs electricity. Thanks to its unique properties, the artifact is able to dramatically increase the muscle tone of the carrier, thereby increasing endurance. Increased radioactivity (the source of which is still unknown to science) also affects the carrier, so stalkers jokingly call it "Radioactive Snowflake". When used, it is worth weighing all the pros and cons: get high endurance and protection from electricity at the cost of high radiation. Use in combat also remains a controversial issue, as its use increases bleeding from wounds and prevents healing of wounds due to the burning outer shell, irritating the skin. It is very light and does not take up much space. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Snowflake»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Compass»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Compass" in a lead-insulated metal container. A rare artifact - last found many months ago. It has the ability to show ruptures in abnormal fields. It is said to be able to pass the most difficult anomalies without the slightest risk, but very few people know how to handle it. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Compass»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Heart of the Oasis»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Heart of the Oasis" in a lead-insulated metal container. An artifact from the center of the legendary Oasis. Apparently, it is a crystallized plant, which has adopted the Oasis inherent property beneficial to the body as a whole. It's exceptionally radioactive, unlike the Oasis itself. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Heart of the Oasis»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Altered Insulator»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b1_half_artifact_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Modified insulator" in a lead-insulated metal container. This thing is something remotely reminiscent of an ordinary electrical insulator. Now, under the influence of abnormal fields, the Alienation Zone is an artifact of unstable nature. Judging by its effects on the body, it's the source of intermittent psych waves. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Insulator»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_lead_box_name">
		<text>Lead Box with «Altered Wheel»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_lead_box_descr">
		<text>"Altered wheel" in a lead-insulated metal container. That's what's left of the usual ship's helm. It is now an artifact of a strange nature. There are no outstanding properties, except a small glow and a lot of radioactivity. The emitted particles hardly penetrate the walls of the container.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] technological device\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] high value\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] low power consumption\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] can store a single artifact\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] maximal capacity:%c[0,170,170,170] 1\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] state:%c[0,170,170,170] filled in (contains an artifact «Altered Wheel»)\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[ui_red] impossible to attach to suit</text>
	</string>

	<!-- New Artefacts -->
	<string id="st_af_cocoon_name">
		<text>«Cocoon»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cocoon_descr">
		<text>Formation of gravitational nature. Useless knickknack, highly valued by collectors and jewelers. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cell_name">
		<text>«Cell»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cell_descr">
		<text>Gravitational rock artifact. It has no useful properties, is not radioactive. It is valued only by collectors and jewelers.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fountain_name">
		<text>«Fountain»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fountain_descr">
		<text>Gravitational abnormal formation. It does not have any useful properties, but because of its bizarre form is highly appreciated by collectors. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_spaika_name">
		<text>«Spike»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_spaika_descr">
		<text>It looks like a fossilized formation. It is a gravitational anomaly. It has no useful properties, is not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_signet_name">
		<text>«Signed Ring»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_signet_descr">
		<text>Stalkers also call this artifact the "Amulet". No useful properties have been found, but stalkers believe that this artifact is a guardian. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_repei_name">
		<text>«Burdock»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_repei_descr">
		<text>Quite often, it is caused by gravitational type anomalies. This is not to say that it has valuable properties, but the absence of any harmful effects on the body makes it attractive to many stalkers. Lightweight, much appreciated by jewelers and collectors. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bat_name">
		<text>«Bat»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bat_descr">
		<text>Very beautiful abnormal formation. It has no useful properties, is not radioactive and is very heavy. Very much appreciated by collectors.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sun_name">
		<text>«Sun»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sun_descr">
		<text>Fairly rare sample, which is very much appreciated by collectors. It does not have useful properties, but it is an inexhaustible source of light, very heavy. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ear_name">
		<text>«Heart»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ear_descr">
		<text>A bizarre artifact whose core resembles a human organ. It does not have useful properties, not radioactive. Valued by collectors outside the Zone.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_chelust_name">
		<text>«Chain»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_chelust_descr">
		<text>A very strange artifact. Starts generating a strong gravitational field if nothing touches it. Has no useful properties, very heavy. Very valuable by jewelers and collectors outside the Zone.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_atom_name">
		<text>«Atom»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_atom_descr">
		<text>An abnormal formation of rare beauty. Outwardly resembles an atom. It is a weak source of heat. It has no useful properties, is not radioactive. Very much appreciated by collectors.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_name">
		<text>«Lighthouse»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_descr">
		<text>Superdense clot of substance. It contains valuable materials that are used in production, so there is a great demand on the Great Earth. Not radioactive, has no useful properties.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_name">
		<text>«Fire Loop»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_descr">
		<text>A necessary condition for the generation of this artifact is the effect and close proximity of the thermal anomaly. It has a fancy look and is therefore appreciated by collectors. Not radioactive, has no useful properties.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_zhelch_name">
		<text>«Scar»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_zhelch_descr">
		<text>The artifact has a calming effect on the human nervous system. Also very appreciated by jewelers. It has no useful properties. Generates a very weak gravitational field. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sandstone_name">
		<text>«Sandstone»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sandstone_descr">
		<text>An artifact that forms in thermally unsafe zones does not have useful properties and is not radioactive. It does not attract either collectors or jewelers, however, it contains a small amount of gold, so it has some value.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kislushka_name">
		<text>«Sourpuss»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kislushka_descr">
		<text>A hollow spherical formation resembling transparent parchment. Covered with a layer of film, pleasant to the touch. It has no useful properties, is not radioactive. Appreciated by collectors.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_angel_name">
		<text>«Black Angel»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_angel_descr">
		<text>The artifact is the root. When it does not come into contact with something, it begins to soar above the surface. Very much appreciated by collectors. It has no useful properties. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grapes_name">
		<text>«Grapes»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grapes_descr">
		<text>Melted piece of wood resin of greenish tint. As a result of powerful anomalies, it became incredibly heavy. Very appreciated by collectors. It has no useful properties. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_name">
		<text>«Miser's Skull»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_descr">
		<text>It's a very light and fragile artifact. Does not have any useful properties. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_name">
		<text>«Phantom Star»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_descr">
		<text>Anomalous formation, is a plasma substance in a transparent pulsating shell. It generates a weak gravitational field. It has no useful properties. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medallion_name">
		<text>«Medallion»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medallion_descr">
		<text>It is a hoop with a small diameter and four triangular shaped parts. Which have two pairs of opposite charges randomly changing their location within the structure. It is valued by collectors. It has no useful properties. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_peas_name">
		<text>«Moon»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_peas_descr">
		<text>Artifact shaped like a crescent moon. Generates a faint and dim light. Has no useful properties. Not radioactive. Has some value with collectors and jewellers.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_generator_name">
		<text>«Generator»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_generator_descr">
		<text>The artifact generates weak electric currents and an electromagnetic field. It is a source of energy and therefore is very much appreciated beyond the perimeter. It has no useful properties. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_ball_name">
		<text>«Ball»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ball_descr">
		<text>There is no exact data under what conditions this spherical artifact is formed, due to which it acquired its name, but practice shows that most often it can be found in places of increased electrical activity. Very mobile and jumping artifact. It does not have useful properties. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fonar_name">
		<text>«Lamp»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fonar_descr">
		<text>Artifact of electric rock. It emits a weak stream of energy and glows. It has no useful properties. Not radioactive. Interesting for collectors.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_name">
		<text>«Tapeworm»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_descr">
		<text>In fact, it's pure silicon dioxide, if you take into account exclusively the atomic mass of the substance. It's got a strange behavior. It has no useful properties. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_moh_name">
		<text>«Moss»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_moh_descr">
		<text>Artifact of electric rock. It has no useful properties. Not radioactive. It has no value.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_serofim_name">
		<text>«Seraphim»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_serofim_descr">
		<text>Artifact of electrical rock. It generates a short-term pulsation with low intensity. As a result of scientific research, it was discovered that the composition of this artifact contains a huge amount of calcium. It was noticed that if you attach this artifact to the place of a fracture or injury, the injury heals much faster. Not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] rare artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_elektron_name">
		<text>«Electron»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_elektron_descr">
		<text>An artifact is a product of electrical anomalies. Super heavy. It has no useful properties. Not radioactive. Very appreciated beyond the perimeter.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_kogot_name">
		<text>«Claw»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kogot_descr">
		<text>Beautiful glass is a similar formation of electrostatic anomalies. It has no useful properties. Not radioactive. It has no special value around the perimeter.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_name">
		<text>«Basilisk»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_descr">
		<text>One of the few artifacts in the Zone that copes well with all kinds of physical influences on its owner.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_geliy_name">
		<text>«Helium»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_geliy_descr">
		<text>Bright (literally) representative of the family of electrostatic artifacts. It releases a gaseous substance that has a beneficial effect on the body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gimlet_name">
		<text>«Gimlet»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gimlet_descr">
		<text>The cup-shaped petals of the artifact are sources of the release of a powerful gaseous stimulator. The result of which is a positive change in the hormonal background.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_name">
		<text>«Dragon's eye»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_descr">
		<text>The artifact is more often formed in fire anomalies and looks like a reptile eye. It has no useful properties. It's not radioactive.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_monolith_name">
		<text>«Monolith»</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_monolith_descr">
		<text>The artifact multiplies the overall rate of regeneration of body tissues after injuries of any nature. It generates a powerful gravitational field around itself, which locally reduces the impact of gravity. Extremely radioactive. The origin of the artifact is shrouded in mystery.\n \n%c[default]CHARACTERISTICS:\n%c[0,225,225,225] • %c[default] inactive artefact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[default] cannot be stored in a modules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_name">
		<text>Altered wheel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_descr">
		<text>It used to be the steering wheel of a dredger, but now it's about half a formed artifact. And the artifact is quite unusual: intensely glowing, weakly radiating - that's all.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-energy_art">
		<text>Fragments of an electrical artifact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-energy_art_descr">
		<text>Fragments of an electrical artifact that can be used as power for some devices.\n \n%c[default]ÕÀÐÀÊÒÅÐÈÑÒÈÊÈ: \n%c[255,238,153,26] • %c[default] used for:%c[0,170,170,170] battery production</text>
	</string>
</string_table>