<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- 	STORYLINE TEXT STRINGS FOR TASKS ON ESCAPE (CORDON) MAP
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_name">
		<text>Get Next Task</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_text">
		<text>Receive your next task.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_about">
		<text>I don't have anything for you, but I know someone who might. I've marked his location on your map.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_finish">
		<text>Good luck stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Mutant Safari Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Mutant Safari</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>You have been tasked to lead a group of tourists on a mutant hunt.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>I have a group of tourists coming through and they want to see what it's like to kill a mutant. Take them out on a hunt, give them a thrill. Just make sure they don't get themselves killed. It's bad for business.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_finish">
		<text>Back from the hunt? Good. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Rookie Initiation Storyline Task- -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_name">
		<text>Rookie Initiation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_text">
		<text>Take a group of rookies into the Zone and show them how to survive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_about">
		<text>The new rookies in the camp are very green. I'm concerned they won't last a day in the Zone. It's bad for business if they die, you see? That many less customers for me. I want you to take them on an expedition into the Zone. Tell them what to watch out for, show them an anomoly, teach them how to stay alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_finish">
		<text>Ah, my customers are still alive. And they need to buy more ammo from me, hehe. Thank you stalker. Take this for your trouble.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Package Task- -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_3_name">
		<text>Goods of Sidorovich</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_3_text">
		<text>I have to deliver the shipment in one day.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_3_about">
		<text>Stalker, you don't look very experienced, but I can give you the job you need. Yeah, don't count on a big fee. I'm a merchant, and like any merchant, there's a need for delivery. Cars in the zone, you know, they can't do that. You'll have exactly one day, take the payment from me, don't demand anything from the recipient. If I find out what I demanded or that something happened to the cargo, you will answer with your head, okay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_3_finish">
		<text>Oh, you're back after all. Well done, there you go, as promised:</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Package Task- -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_4_name">
		<text>Sidor Collectors Ltd.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_4_text">
		<text>We need to get the stalker out of debt within 24 hours and pay Sidorovich back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_4_about">
		<text>Here's one thing you shouldn't have trusted him, though. I'm the only one around here with the money. Accordingly, I am also part of the bank's function. But some dull people think there's no need to pay back debts in the Zone, saying there's no control over them. So, we have to prove to a stalker that we have our own laws here and beat the money out of him. You know what I mean? You're gonna have a day to run around looking for that freak.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_4_finish">
		<text>All right, give them here... Now, I'll do the math... I think it's okay. Take third part and a military map as a gift, I got it from an idiot, I think you can use it:</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Klin (Loner Mechanic) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_name">
		<text>Get Next Task</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_text">
		<text>Receive your next task.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_about">
		<text>A friend of mine could use your services. I've marked his location on your map.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_finish">
		<text>Good luck stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Klin (Loner Mechanic) Rescue Missing Stalker Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Rescue Missing Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>There's a stalker missing from camp, we need to find him. We've got two days to do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>I need help. A stalker from my camp went on a mission and never came back. I'm afraid something bad has happened to him, we need to find him as soon as possible, so don't take more than two days. I'll mark his last known location on the map. Come back if you can find him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_finish">
		<text>You saved him! Well done, stalker. Take it as a thank you:</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Klin (Loner Mechanic) Track Wounded Attacker Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Track Wounded Attacker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>A military detachment attacked the camp, Tech and the guys killed them. One of the attackers managed to escape. We need to track him down in 4 hours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>Where have you been? You always disappear on time. A military unit has attacked the camp. Then there was the damn helicopter... A lot of people died. We managed to kill most of them, but one of them got away. You know what happens if you don't catch up with him, right? I'll show you the direction. You go now. Maximum you've got is 4 hours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thank you stalker. Take this as a gift for your actions.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->
	
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Technical documentation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>Klin asked to return the technical documentation to him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>I was supposed to get some technical documents, but it turns out they're in a stash somewhere, where a courier dropped them off. Bring them to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>Thank you, stalker! Here you go:</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Payoff Change Factions Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_name">
		<text>Pay Sidorovich To Become a Loner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_text">
		<text>Sidorovich will get you out of your current faction commitments for a fee of 10,000 UAH.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_about">
		<text>Well, it's good you've come to me then. I have a lot of connections here in the Zone. I can get you out of your commitment to your faction, but it won't be cheap. I will need to grease some palms, you know. If you can get me, say... 10,000 UAH I'll see what I can do for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Ah, this should do well. I'll make the necessary arrangements, enjoy your new life as a Loner.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Eliminate Car Park Bandits Task -->

	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Eliminate Car Park Bandits</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>Stage an assault on the car park and eliminate the bandits that occupy the location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>Bandits have taken up base in the old car park. These assholes mug or kill anyone who use the roads leading in and out of the camp. It is disrupting local activities for my clients and the stalkers who take refuge in camp. It's hurting business! I need you to "take care" of them. If you want, talk to Fanatic, he may be able to offer you assistance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_finish">
		<text>Great work, stalker! You and I will be best of friends if you keep this up! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_name">
		<text>Contract Killer for Sidorovich</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_text">
		<text>Sidorovich asked to remove one stalker. The execution time is 24 hours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_about">
		<text>I've got a list of stalkers to deal with. It's usually made up of all kinds of bastards and complete assholes... For all sorts of reasons. In a word, trash. Trash that needs to be cleared out of the Zone from time to time, you know? This particular asshole needs to be cleaned up fast before he escapes, so you don't have more than 24 hours. So, do you want to do it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_finish">
		<text>Good, you got rid of that asshole! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>

	<!--     esc_2_12_stalker_wolf	 -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_name">
		<text>Eliminate Mutant Threat from Cordon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_text">
		<text>Wolf asked you to purge an area of all mutant threats in order to ensure the safety of rookie village; as well as the stalkers who pass through Cordon. Reach the location and eliminate all mutants around the area. Return to Wolf for payment after your job is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_about">
		<text>Stalker, I need someone to who is a bit more experienced than the rookies for a task. Cordon is becoming a very dangerous place with all this rampant mutant breeding going on. I need you to hunt around an area that I will mark on your PDA. The job is to kill any mutants you see. If you do this for me, it will earn you some cash. So will you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Thank you, the rookies will be much safer now because of you. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) Stalker Search and Rescue Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_name">
		<text>Stalker Search and Rescue</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_text">
		<text>Search for the missing stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_about">
		<text>A stalker is missing from the camp. I need you to go find out what sort of trouble he's gotten himself into.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thank you. It's stalkers like you that keep this place one of the only safe areas in the Zone.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) Stalker Guide Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_name">
		<text>Stalker Guide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_text">
		<text>Lead a group of rookies into the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_about">
		<text>A group of rookies is heading out into the Zone for the first time. I need a competent stalker to guide them and keep them safe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_finish">
		<text>Thank you for keeping the rookies safe, stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Nimble (Loner Trader) Find Weapon Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_name">
		<text>Find a %s for Nimble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_text">
		<text>Nimble has asked you to find a specific firearm. It needs to be in mint condition. Return to him when you find what he is looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_about">
		<text>I have a client looking for a specific firearm and I need someone to help me find it. If you are interested I will give you more details. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>{item_name}... That is what I need, but it must be in mint condition. The client is paying top dollar and he doesn't want a rusty piece of shit that will jam up in a life or death situation. I'll give you most of the profit since you are doing all the work. Come back when you find it, man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>This is a fine weapon. I think my client will be pleased when I deliver this to him. Here is what I owe you.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Nimble (Loner Trader) Retrieve PDA Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_name">
		<text>Retrieve PDA for Nimble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_text">
		<text>Nimble has a PDA he needs retrieved.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_about">
		<text>I need you to pick up a PDA for me. It's hidden in a spot a little while away from here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thank you stalker!</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Klin (Loner Mechanic) Find Level 1 Toolkit Task -->

	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Klin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>%s are required by Klin to install basic equipment upgrades, you should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>I need a favour, man. A lot of stalkers come by here asking if I can tune their weapons a certain way but I can't. I just don't have the right tools. I would be able to perform upgrades on a greater variety of equipment if I can just get my hands on the right tools. Please, man, will you help me out?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I need a set of basic tools. It should contain what I need. If you can bring some back for me I will be grateful, I will even offer you a discount from here on out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Okay, yeah, this is exactly what I need. Here, I promised you payment; take it.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- FIND LEVEL 2 TOOLS FOR Klin TASK -->
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Find %s for Klin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>%s are required by Klin to install advanced equipment upgrades, you should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>My business is booming now, more and more stalkers come to me when they need their weapon fine-tuned. But I could really use more tools. You brought me a quality toolkit last time but I need an even higher quality set. If you are interested, I will tell you what I need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>I need an {item_name}. If you can bring one back for me I will be grateful, I will even pay you for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Yes, yes! Here is some cash, you deserve it.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- FIND LEVEL 3 TOOLS FOR Klin TASK -->
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Find %s for Klin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>%s are required by Klin to install expert equipment upgrades, you should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>My business is booming now, more and more stalkers come to me when they need their weapon fine-tuned. But I could really use more tools. You brought me a quality toolkit last time but I need an even higher quality set. If you are interested, I will tell you what I need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>I need an {item_name}. If you can bring one back for me I will be grateful, I will even pay you for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Yes, yes! Here is some cash, you deserve it.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>