<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements">
		<text>Achievements</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_bookworm_food">
		<text>Bookworm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_bookworm_food_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Bookworm»%c[default] requires to open all the information in your personal PDA.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nInformation can be opened by talking to important characters, downloading data from storage devices or copying information from personal diaries.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]%c[default]\n
			\nAll founded flash drives will be replaced by a rare PDA with information.\n
			\nWhen adding new articles (When updating the mod), this achievement will be reset and flash drives can be retrieved again.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_completionist">
		<text>Perfectionist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_completionist_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Perfectionist»%c[default] requires to unlock all the achievements in the Zone.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nDoubles the number of rank points.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_down_to_earth">
		<text>Black Hawk Down</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_down_to_earth_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Black Hawk Down»%c[default] requires to destroy 3 helicopters with small arms, or only one with a grenade launcher (RPG-7 or RG-6).\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nMi-24 «Lan» helicopters will be replaced later by weaker helicopters, Mi-2 «Hoplit».
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_duga_free">
		<text>Pioneer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_duga_free_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Pioneer»%c[default] is only available in story mode and requires that you turn off both the «Miracle Machine» and the «Brain Burner».\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nTravel through "Yantar" and "Radar" became much easier now, when their psi-fields were turned off.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_geologist">
		<text>Geologist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_geologist_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Geologist»%c[default] requires detection of at least 50 artifacts.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nTo detect an artifact, a detector is required, which is sold by most traders. You can detect artifacts using the detector near an anomaly.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nThe spawn rate of artifacts in anomalies will be slightly increased.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_heavy_pockets">
		<text>A wealthy client</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_heavy_pockets_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«A wealthy client»%c[default] requires that you have 1,000,000 RUs at any time.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nMost traders will start offering you special products.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_infopreneur">
		<text>Informant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_infopreneur_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Informant»%c[default] requires that you provide a minimum of 50 PDAs to information merchants.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nPDA can be found on the bodies of dead stalkers, and they can be exchanged from the information merchants, just inform them that you have information to sell.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nTraders will offer you a slightly higher reward for any PDA that you brought to them.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_mechanized_warfare">
		<text>Technical Excellence</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_mechanized_warfare_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Technical Excellence»%c[default] requires that you deliver all 3 tool sets to one technician.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\Ordinary tools for fine and rough work can be found mostly in stashes, but they can also be found by compliting some stalkers tasks.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nTechniques and sewing kits will repair weapons and equipment slightly more than before.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_patriarch">
		<text>Legendary stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_patriarch_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Legendary stalker»%c[default] requires that you reach the highest possible rank.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nThe rank can be obtained through almost all the actions that you can take in the Zone.\nAn article describing the rank and how it works can be found in the category of functions.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nYou will be able to hire 2 additional stalkers as companions above your current limit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_radiotherapy">
		<text>Marked One</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_radiotherapy_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Marked One»%c[default] requires to survive 25 psi-storms and 25 blowouts.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nBlowouts and psi storms occur at random intervals that can be changed through the weather parameters section in the main menu.\n
			\nBoth of these functions can be switched at any time during the trek, but should be included so you can get this Achievement.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nThere is a small chance of surviving during a emission or psi storm, outside the shelter.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_rag_and_bone">
		<text>Detective</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_rag_and_bone_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Detective»%c[default] requires to found at least 100 stashes.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nStashes can be found almost anywhere in the Zone at any time, but getting their coordinates after performing tasks will mark them on your map.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nThe maximum number of items that can be found in future stashes will be slightly increased.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_silver_or_lead">
		<text>Any last word?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_silver_or_lead_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Any last word?»%c[default] requires to kill 500 stalkers or to make surrender 50 stalkers.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nThe requirements for this achievement are likely to be met while traveling through the Zone, but if you intentionally try to unlock it, be careful not to kill neutral or friendly stalkers if you value your reputation.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nCaptive stalkers can sometimes give you the coordinates of an additional stash.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_tourist">
		<text>Seeker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_tourist_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Seeker»%c[default] requires that you visit all locations in the Zone.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nYou will receive the coordinates of three unique stashes.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_explorer">
		<text>Explorer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_explorer_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Explorer»%c[default] requires that you explore all areas on Zone locations.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nYou will receive the coordinates of five unique stashes.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_well_dressed">
		<text>Mutant slayer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_well_dressed_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Mutant slayer»%c[default] requires killing 500 mutants, or collecting 250 parts of mutants.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nSometimes you can get additional parts of the mutant.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_wishful_thinking">
		<text>Destroyer of the Legends</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_achievements_wishful_thinking_text">
		<text>
			Achievement  %c[guide_blue]«Destroyer of the Legends»%c[default] available only in story mode and requires that you defeat the Wish-Granter.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Reward%c[default]\n
			\nYou will receive a significant increase in both your rank and reputation.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>