<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants">
		<text>Mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bear">
		<text>Chernobyl Bear</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bear_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Mutated animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] The harmful effects of radiation and abnormal fields.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Fast movements, speed and terrifying bloodlust.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Great similarity with the ordinary bear, huge fangs and slightly deformed limbs.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]High.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Woodlands.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Hulking speed, strength and aggression.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n A huge mutated bear, a huge muscle of muscle. Has no special abilities, except for enormous strength, endurance and speed. Is able to pursue the victim through any obstacles, carrying light and moving through the heavy. The bear itself dwells in dense forests. And if you fall into his eyes at night, then run faster.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n All animals of the Zone have changed under the influence of radioactive and abnormal fields and bears have not become an exception. And without that the impressive sizes of the bear increased thanks to the Zone, clawed paws and huge teeth are capable of breaking any careless stalker.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and Behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Like an ordinary bear, prefers to dwell in places with a dense forest planting, hiding among trees. Stalkers say that by behavior he reminds Chimera, rapid movements, the desire to quickly rip and devour the victim and preferably a nocturnal lifestyle. However, a huge body prevents the bear from making long jumps to shorten the distance with victum.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_blind_dog">
		<text>Blind dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_blind_dog_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Blind dog . 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] 1-2 individuals do not represent danger. Flock attack, attack with bites. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Ugly, Blind dog .
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Low. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Many terrestrial locations. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Good sense of smell.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Mutations and evolutionary adaptation have led to the strengthening of previously weakly expressed canine abilities, often at the expense of the habitual, and the emergence of new ones. As a result, animals are well aware of and bypass the anomalies, radiation and other invisible hazards that the Zone is teeming with. Well jumping.\n
			Vision and in many cases hearing completely lost, but there was an immunity to radiation and developed until a completely studied new "feeling", a kind of telepathic vision that allows dogs to feel the prey or danger literally through the walls. Scientists can not even really determine what internal body is responsible for this, although they have plenty of materials to study. Many dogs, especially those living in the depth of the Zone, use psi-abilities also for hunting, they bring down psi-attacks on the victim. \n
			There is reliable information that in the ancestors of blind dogs there were genetically altered thoroughbred dogs, grown in the laboratories of the Zone. However, any creature of the Zone rumors about the results of "experiments¿. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Laboratory research in the field of breeding included experiments with the genetic material of thoroughbred dogs. It was assumed that a new kind of dog could be more effectively used to guard the perimeter of the Zone. It is known that artificially bred breeds are not as adapted to confront external factors as their wild relatives. The task of the experimenters was to show the degree of influence of "wild" genes on fitness for external natural and anthropogenic factors. It was decided to replace some areas of chromosomes of modern breeds of dogs with highly homologous areas of wild species. As a result of such manipulations, the transgenic dogs of the zone acquired several altered properties from wild dogs. In other words, they were artificially brought closer to the wild state. After the disaster, some laboratory samples left the laboratory and began to mate with mutant feral relatives in the Zone. Accordingly, their descendants have acquired new properties. As a result, there was a "genetic cocktail". The influence of the zone has been increasingly observed, and with each succeeding generation more and more. Due to the huge variety of the original genetic material of the dog of the Zone are superfit, since they have in their genome a lot of "sleeping genes" and just neutral mutations that can appear as positive when the conditions change. Not surprisingly, only qualified individuals have gone through natural selection, so in the Zone, to date, it is possible to find very predatory representatives of canine. As a result, for more than ten years, ordinary dogs soon degenerated here completely, giving way to a new species - blind dogs.\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_blind_dog_text2">
		<text>%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n They are at war with many mutants in the Zone: with zombies, Boar's, Bloodsuckers, flesh, Pseudogiantes, possibly also with burer and dwarfs. For some unknown reason they are afraid of Snork, immediately run away from them, not trying to defend themselves or attack. Dogs hunt rats who are natural enemies of the dog-mole rats, and tushkanoss. They never conflict with pseudo dogs, very often they live and hunt together, showing an optional symbiosis.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n One or two dogs are not dangerous. Loners generally try to bypass armed men. Because dogs are blind, their flock can sometimes be quietly circumvented. When attacking them, they escape, attack themselves only if they are locked in a corner. But meeting with the pack should already be avoided. Well-fed dogs may not pay attention to the stalker. However, like all the creatures of the Zone, dogs have an accelerated metabolism and are full for a very short time. A poorly armed stalker should go around the flocks in a wide arc, move around the hills, high ruins - in time to notice the congestion of dogs. In the melee, however, the dog does not pose a particular problem. Two or three bullets or charge of a large fraction (or even better - a short burst) - deadly for a blind dog. The main thing is to dodge him and his fellow-workers.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High Speed and maneuverability.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Acute Scent.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Rapid Attacks.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Very dangerous when hunted pack. Together, they can knock down even Pseudogiant. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] A small amount of health (lower only in tushkanos).
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] A small damage for bite.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] One or two individuals do not pose a danger to stalkers, as they in most cases retreat.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Rapidly detected by loud barking.\n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Dogs-albinos (distinguished by the absence of pigments).	
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Dogs rat-catchers (with a white neck and earthy body). Albinos and rat-catchers are rarer compared to wild dogs. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Several generations of the dog species have lived and died since the catastrophe. Each was more affected by the Zone than the previous one. Rapid mutation lead to a vast improvement in previously peripheral abilities, frequently at the expense of primary ones. The most notable biological change was the loss of sight, paired with an uncanny development of smell. As it turned out, blind cubs survived in the Zone as well as normal ones, if not better. As a result, the common dog quickly became extinct in the Zone, giving way to a new breed - that of blind dogs. The animals instinctively identify and avoid anomalies, radiation and other invisible dangers that plague the Zone. Like their wild ancestors - the wolves - blind dogs hunt in packs. An encounter with a large group of these animals can be dangerous even to an experiences and well-armed stalker.  ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n 
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Not as dangerous alone, as in a dense pack. They are attacked only if they are hungry, but they are almost always hungry. If you are hunting a pack, try to beat from the hill, otherwise you will simply be overwhelmed by pressure, especially if there are a few hardened dogs in the pack".%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.\n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bloodsucker">
		<text>Bloodsucker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bloodsucker_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] The result of experiments on people.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Fast runs, quickly attack. Becomes invisible and swirling around the victim, trying to disorient her.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] The two-meter-long humanoid has a color of dark red, or dark blue, instead of the lower jaw - 4-5 long tentacles.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] High, the vulnerable part of the body is the head. Invulnerable in invisibility.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Wet and damp dungeons, abandoned houses. Rarely - in open areas.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] It can become almost invisible for a short time.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\It hunts constantly in different places, but it prefers not to change its lair and desperately defends its dwelling in case of an attack by anyone, be it a human or a mutant. Because the bloodsucker's thermoregulatory system is close to that of the cold-blooded, its metabolism is slowed and depends on the temperature of the surrounding air, such as that of frogs. Because of this, the monster is invisible in the infrared spectrum. The bloodsucker, satiated with its victim's blood, digests it for a long time, sitting in its lair. The best living conditions for the bloodsucker are high humidity, darkness and temperature about 17-18 degrees Celsius, due to which it can be found in different kinds of dungeons and cellars, in the swamp or in abandoned buildings in the lowlands.\n  
			\n\n 
			A bloodsucker is a nocturnal creature. The retina of his eye has a large number of "sticks," which allows him to see in the dark and dusk better than during the day. In darkness, its pupils are dilated, so you can see its retinas in the light of a flashlight - a "red-eye" effect. But some individuals are able to hunt during the day, although it is possible that they are pushed to do this only by intense hunger. It will be more convenient to fight off a bloodsucker by standing against a wall or in a corner and attacking with a knife (if desired). The easiest way to fight a mutant is from an elevated position, because the bloodsucker can't get to you that way. \n 
			\n\n 
			Most striking is the ability of the bloodsucker to become invisible; this action is performed automatically and regulated by the eye retina. The mechanism of such a phenomenon is defined as the telephotography of the image appearing on the retina to the surface of the body, a diffuse transfer from the retina to the skin. The light stimulus is transmitted to pigment cells with diverging fibers - chromatophores, which are able to contract and expand, creating numerous color combinations. This makes the bloodsucker similar to a chameleon or cuttlefish, but it spends a lot of energy on this, and the more the mutant loses it, the better it becomes visible. It is impossible to wear a bloodsucker out with running and various athletic exercises, only the physical damage to his health will let him manifest himself literally. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n Bloodsucker is the result of the Chernobyl Scientific Research Institute of Parapsychology (CSRIP) experiments. The purpose of the experiments was to grow humanoid creatures, perhaps in order to obtain a new biological species - the DNA of the human embryos had an extrasensory effect. In the end, Bloodsucker was defined as a dead-end branch of evolution and "genetic rubbish"¿. \n
			After leaving the laboratories, the bloodsuckers continued to mutate throughout the years of the Zone's existence. \n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bloodsucker_text2">
		<text>\n Bloodsucker is a very aggressive mutant that has enough enemies among other creatures. The strongest of them are the Buhrer and Pseudogiant. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude towards people.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n He attacks Anyone without thinking. Unlike battles with other mutants, people use a slightly different tactic - the Bloodsucker tries to get around the rear and try to suck blood. The beginning of the battle with people is also different: they either immediately become invisible and sneak to their victim, or first rush forward and at close range "dissolve in the air," and then begin to "round off" the stalker, inflicting damage with sharp claws. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Pretty High Vitality and the ability to regenerate.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] By sucking the blood out of the victim restores Health. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Effective disguise.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Pretty strong attack.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Particularly dangerous in dark and enclosed spaces, where mostly lives
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] The mobility can confuse the player, knocking down the sight.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High Speed and maneuverability
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Absolutely invisible when disguised.\n%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] At approach loudly wheezes, owing to what it is possible to assume an approximate location of the monster. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] When moving, the outline of the body of the Bloodsucker is visible.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] During the impact, it becomes visible for three or four seconds, which is associated with the expenditure of great forces and energy on the attack. The advantage is that you can see in which direction the Bloodsucker escaped.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Not very resistant to knife impacts.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Can not become invisible if he runs all the time behind his back.%c[default] \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Swamp creature is a special subspecies of Bloodsucker. Dwells only in swamps, attacking a jump from reeds and other vegetation.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Stronglav - a three-meter Bloodsucker - a giant, much more experienced and stronger than his brothers, playing with his victims. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Experienced stalkers describe this semi-legendary beast as a tall, hunched humanoid with a mess of tentacles where its mouth should be. According to those who saw it and lived to tell the tale, the creature uses its tentacles to cling to the victim's throat, paralyze it, and suck it dry of blood. A dry, mummified shell is all that is left of what used to be a living human being. The most astounding feature of the bloodsucker, however, is its ability to become invisible. Countless dead or missing stalkers are said to have perished in the merciless grip of a bloodsucker. The lucky few who have survived an encounter tell spine-chilling tales of marshes and subterranean areas haunted by the Zone's version of Count Dracula  ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Oh, these are hunters who hunt hunters! Their Camouflage is a dream! When disguised, they are almost invisible. If you go to the Bloodsucker, try to scare him away: only in his movement and you can notice. Also remember that this creature strives to go to the victim from the back and crunch his neck with his tentacles... damn, an abomination! ... In general, if not lucky and ran into the family BloodsuckerS, always control the situation behind your back".%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.%c[default] \n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_boar">
		<text>Boar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_boar_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Mutated Boar . 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Rapidly rushes to the victim, trying to hit with fangs. In close combat, it beats with hoofs.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] An increased in size wild boar with four ears.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Low; vulnerable parts - head and sides of the trunk. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Throughout the open fields. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Low aim, In case of a miss, he  reveals  his weaknesses.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n A massive, mutated animal, reaching 1,5 meters at the shoulder. The Zone boar's aggressiveness and ability to survive surpass by far those of its relatives outside the contaminated area. Radiation and anomalies left their mark on the physical appearance of the animal as well: its fur is entirely gone in some places, and long and bristly in others. The hooves have evolved into sturdy, sharp claws, the pupils have became colorless, and the boar's bald head is marred by pigmentation disorders and deep wrinkles. Zone boars are quite resistant to radiation and can stay in heavily contaminated areas for longer periods of time. They usually charge at their victims, trying to knock them over and then rip them to shreds.  \n
			Mutated Boars of The Zone tolerate to radiation well, which allows them to stay in heavily polluted areas for a long time, but are still vulnerable to abnormal impacts. Usually these animals attack from the take-off, developing a large Speed and trying to tear the fangs or legs of the victim with their fangs or knock them down. With such an attack, any obstacles are taken down. In case of a strong skid, after a takeoff run, a jump in place takes place. In close combat, they attack with their hoofs quickly and sharply. \n
			They have good resistance to bullet wounds, but are vulnerable to shot shots. Badly climb the dais. Wild boars are aggressive because they run into rabies, but it is not known whether they are doing this consciously or at the level of instincts, although the behavior of leaders indicates the involvement of instincts. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Boar - one of the most numerous animals of the Zone, exposed to anomalous energy, after the Second Chernobyl catastrophe. In contrast to the flesh, not so much mutated, but greatly increased in size. Depending on the territory, the appearance of Boar may vary, but the habits remain the same. Large herds of these mutants can pose a serious danger even for experienced and well-armed stalkers, so some stalkers issue a task to destroy Boars.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Boar - herd Mutants, behave aggressively towards all enemies that have entered their territory. Unlike many mutants, they patrol their territory from time to time. The leader is the whole herd, the strongest and most aggressive individual. Among the leaders, the cannibalism is rare: they run into extreme rabies and attack their fellow tribesmen, and then devour them; when they die, the morale of the pack falls. Sometimes they fall into frenzy without reason. You are unlikely to meet them singly. \n
			Omnivorous. Do not hunt, eat dead victims or corpses. Like many Mutants-animals, they simply survive. \n\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_boar_text2">
		<text>%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Smaller in size animals (like rats or tushkanos) Boar may well eat, although they are not specially hunted. With flesh periodically grazing together, but just as often and conflict. Blind dogs are driven away if they come too close, in turn, dogs often attack young boars. Wild boars when faced with a Bloodsucker or a pseudo-dog, they attack at once, but they will be able to overcome only the number. Try to stay away from Pseudogiant and Chimera, but sometimes relying on numerical superiority attack them. Like flesh, they have almost no psi protection, so they easily obey the controller. Neutral to the Poltergeist and Zombies. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Boars, especially those who are the leaders of the herd, are extremely aggressive; If the stalker goes to their territory, then we should wait for the attack. These are devoid of any trick: relying on their size, powerful fangs and hoofs, Boar attacks from a takeoff, flying directly at the enemy, trying to knock him down and then tear his fangs and hoofs. Rarely when found alone, most often a group of three individuals. As in the case of blind dogs, it does not move very fast, and in close combat has extremely low maneuverability, which makes it no more dangerous than a tuskan (in case you have at least a bleed). You can avoid contact altogether, as Boar is very easy to notice, and he himself is blind. However, when you are attacked by a large swarm the situation changes dramatically. It is recommended to put them closer, and immediately after the shot sharply jump off to the side: next the running Boar will fly by, exposing the vulnerable (especially for the fraction) side. Repeating this simple combination of actions, you can have in your arsenal even a double-barreled gun to easily deal with a large (from 4 mutants) pack. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Huge amount of damage.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Vitality. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low Speed attacks.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Hulking. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Young Boar. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" A massive, mutated animal, reaching 1,5 meters at the shoulder. The Zone boar's aggressiveness and ability to survive surpass by far those of its relatives outside the contaminated area. Radiation and anomalies left their mark on the physical appearance of the animal as well: its fur is entirely gone in some places, and long and bristly in others. The hooves have evolved into sturdy, sharp claws, the pupils have became colorless, and the boar's bald head is marred by pigmentation disorders and deep wrinkles. Zone boars are quite resistant to radiation and can stay in heavily contaminated areas for longer periods of time. They usually charge at their victims, trying to knock them over and then rip them to shreds. ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" These (flesh) are the most harmless of mutants. Try to stay away from stalkers, but if you attack them, they will defend themselves. It is more dangerous if among the flesh Boar falls. An animal for three hundred pounds is not a toy for you! Try not to be on the runway during the hunt. On the other hand, the inertia of him, too, oh-go: he himself understands, this carcass can not turn around instantly. It turns out, you dodge him - and shot! "%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.\n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_burer">
		<text>Burer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_burer_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Victims of the experiment.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] He uses telekinesis, tears a weapon from the stalker's hands, throws objects, puts a shield, burns a reserve of strength, pushes away at a distance. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Thick dwarf growth of about a meter, much wrinkled skin.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Increased; The most vulnerable part of the body is the head.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Dungeons, dark spaces (hangars, warehouses). 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] They live in families, have the beginnings of religion.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Burers are the result of genetic experiments conducted by special services on criminals to develop human telekinetic abilities. These are fat low freaks with hypertrophic features in the remains of clothes - a worn out form and black raincoats. They can move heavy objects by the mere force of thought, and also create invisible power barriers. Once bureurs were ordinary people, most likely prisoners or stupid volunteers who were not fortunate enough to get into the program to strengthen the supernatural, in particular telekinetic, human capabilities. As a result of the side effect, they turned into real monsters - they lost their human image and went mad. The burghers are alien to human morality and compassion, they kill people for entertainment and food, using a variety of tricks from their supernatural arsenal - there are cases when these freaks lured stalkers into an ambush, posing as normal people. Spacious clothing, most likely being the remnants of a special form, which bureurs cherish much more than other Zone Mutants, helps them get away with a person (at least from afar). Most of these creatures still live close to the abandoned laboratories that spawned them.. \n  
			\n\n
			Their main weapon is their supernatural abilities, allowing to lift objects into the air and throw them at enemies. Also, at a distance, they can lift large objects (to a passenger car) into the air and create a telekinetic explosion that eases in an animated and inanimate objects with equal ease. No less interesting is the ability of the burer to create a gravitational field that protects the mutant, for example, from stalker bullets or grenades. \n  
			\n\n
			Virtually can not keep under control the published sounds: if you do not hear the muttering of the bureurs - then they are simply not there. They can make a sound that resembles a human voice or a child's crying as a bait. The burers also walk very loudly, often giving out their location. Some stalkers heard that they were saying some words "in a very low voice, similar to the voice of Darth Vader." Create around yourself a gravitational field that protects them from bullets. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Like the controller and Izlom, the burer is the result of the "Universal Soldier" program, conducted by the CSRIP. One of its branches is telekinesis. Subjects underwent implantation of extrasensory enhancers, which gave them the ability. They also know how to cause auditory hallucinations in children - child crying. Later, experiments began on the cultivation of humanoid creatures, in one of which the bureras were to be obtained, - on the embryos of people, extrasensory influence was experienced. \n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_burer_text2">
		<text>
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Burer - are community Mutants. They seize territory, arrange nests in them and live there. These mutants have a kind of religion - they build special altars and drag them to various kinds of objects, whether it's ordinary garbage or really valuable things. They live mainly in poorly lit places, rarely come to light. In their nests do not favor strangers, they are immediately attacked. They are afraid of bright light, so they hide in dark places. They feed on corpses. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n In addition to his relatives among the allies, he has izloms and controllers. Perhaps because they are all victims of the experiments of the "Universal Soldier" program, they only refer to different branches of creation. Its main enemies are the Bloodsucker. Flocks of blind dogs and pseudo dogs also do not give him a warm welcome. He tries to stay away from mutants, which the burer is "too tough", for example Pseudogiant or chimera. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude towards people.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Any person attacks without hesitation, while trying to keep from them further, throwing them with all sorts of objects. With close enough contact telekinesis, pulling out of his arms a weapon that can also be thrown, or in an unknown way to act telekinesis directly on the stalker, knocking him out of his strength. After such a telekinetic attack, a person passes over to a sitting position and drops his weapon. When the contact closes, he uses his hands. \n
			The relations with the "Monolith" are completely unknown: the members of the group feed the mutants with the brought bodies of zombified stalkers, and the bureurs in return protected X18. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High Vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] They are able to create around themselves a powerful gravitational field.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Powerful attacks.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Like to attack unexpectedly.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Is able to deplete the main character with gravitational fields. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] If he is in a close room, then, even throwing a grenade away from himself, falls into the zone of explosion.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] The energy field, which protects from bullets, is kept for a short time. While using the field, a monster can not conduct attacks
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Almost powerless at great distances from the enemy.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Vulnerable when moving. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Unknown. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" The buretors for the attack use gravity. If you are close - he will throw you, show off from afar - throw something heavy in you. The tactic with him is this: beat from an average distance - and, most importantly, do not stand still for a second. Only the forces at the same time, take care, with an eye to spending: the burer can also pull the arms out of his hands with his gravity. He is able to do this business well, especially if the hunter is weaker".%c[0,215,215,215] Trapper.\n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_cat">
		<text>Cat</text>
	</string>
<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_cat_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Mutated lynx or cat. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] 1-2 individuals do not represent danger. attacks in groups, attack with bites. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Looks like a big cat.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Low. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] The habitat is similar to the blind dogs.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Good sense of smell.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n This fast and intelligent creation of the Zone is capable of mimicing human speech and lulling stalkers with their meow. It has highly developed animal intelligence, excellent vision, hearing and mobility. The body is developed, muscular - very strong paws and bulldog's jaw, slightly protruding forward. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n In most cases, live alone, less often - in small groups of 2-3 individuals. They live in quiet, secluded places (for example, old houses or forest thickets). \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Aggressive to rats, tushkanos, blind dogs, and pseudo-dogs. There are rumored to be very friendly with fractures, and often attack with then as a team.
            The diet most likely consists of small mutants: tushkanos and rats. Young wild boar are also occasionally mauled. As expected these cats are very hostile to blind dogs and pseudo-dogs.\n
			These highly intelligence mutants, usually attack from ambush or from behind. So, if caught off guard, prefer to retreat - They can be a difficult opponent to finish off; using an affinity for anomalies and incredible sprinting abilities to escape from a unfavorable situation. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n If strongly injured, it prefers to retreat to the nearest shelter. In some cases, shooting a cat can discourage him from attacking you. Even a well-fed cat will attack. If you meet a group of cats, avoid a fight which you most likely will not survive. \n 
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Attacks in small groups.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Speed. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low vitality. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n	 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Cat Baiyun.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" A mutant cat with greenish hair and a lot of bald spots on its sides, like a pseudo dog. On the neck, the thyroid gland is swollen due to radiation. Aggressive. Has rapid reaction and is very fast. Cat Baiyun Distributed throughout the Zone. In the Zoo and in the Voronin's basement, among other radiation-affected fauna of the Zone there are stuffed cats. You can recognize by a characteristic meow. Comparable in strength with blind dogs, but much faster." %c[0,215,215,215]\n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_chimera">
		<text>Chimera</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_chimera_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Zoomorph.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Result of experiments.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Night predator; attacks from the back, making incredible jumps of 20-30 meters.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Four-legged creature with two heads, one of which is underdeveloped.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]High.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] A lair can be organized anywhere.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Extremely clever, strong and cunning creature; is considered one of the most dangerous predators of the Zone. Rumor has it that he can talk and read thoughts.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Chimera has the appearance of a four-legged creature with two heads, one of which is underdeveloped. The chimera has a duplicate system of internal organs (including the brain, but one, like the head, is underdeveloped), which makes it easier to endure injuries - if it damages one heart, the other will continue to function. There is no central circulatory system. The whole body is permeated with capillaries, with wounds this gives the chimera huge chances to survive, despite the loss of blood. The mutant is capable of quick regeneration of both small scratches and damaged limbs. As a weapon uses huge claws on the front paws. According to unofficial data, the chimera was created as a universal Animal-defender in one of the Zona laboratories, possibly in the X18 laboratory (the project "Universal Animal Army Protection"). Chimeras are monstrously strong, deft and cunning. This kind of mutant is one of the most dangerous in the Zone. \n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n It is the result of genetic experiments under the program "Universal Animal Protector" - embryos of unknown animals underwent extrasensory influence on DNA. At the same time, the chimera was defined as a dead-end branch of evolution, which continued to be "grown" and studied. Has a large muscular body with powerful paws and two heads. Paws have sharp enough claws - the main weapon of the mutant; The hind legs are especially powerful, which is confirmed by protracted jumps at the level of her head. Immune to certain anomalies and radiation, has a high intelligence in comparison with other mutants. In chimeras, a duplicated system of internal organs and an additional brain, that is, most likely, the 2nd head of a mutant is something like a reserve brain - this makes the process of killing it very problematic, as well as accelerated regeneration. \n  
			\n\n
			It is not known when chimeras hit the wild, but the first stalkers already reported these mutants. Their habits and movements are reminiscent of a panther. During the bout, he hides behind shelters and is not put under fire. Runs around the enemy in circles and jumps from place to place. The attack basically makes jumps, it hits near if it does not land on the target, but next. After the attack, if he can not immediately get the enemy near attack, then whenever possible jumps off for cover, if there is no shelter, then simply aside. \n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The Chimera always appears unexpectedly, loves to attack from the back. If detected, it may retreat, but not for long. Due to some properties of the legs, Animal can move almost silently, and it is often possible to determine that the chimera is nearby, only by motion sensors. 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_chimera_text2">
		<text>Powerful hind legs give the monster the ability to jump a considerable distance, which, coupled with the huge chimera claws, makes her attack very dangerous for the victim. The greatest danger chimera poses at night, going hunting. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The chimera hunts mostly at night, but, being very hungry, it can attack in the daytime. Chimeras are extremely aggressive and, meeting representatives of someone else's species, often attack. Often, they always come out victorious. The only mutant that is too tough for a chimera is Pseudogiant, but the two chimeras, acting together, can kill him. Always fighting with Burers and Snorks. The least dangerous enemies for a chimera are Boars and flesh, because at one its form they escape without analyzing the road. Neutral to blind dogs Bloodsucker and pseudo dogs. tushkanos and Poltergeist are not of interest to her. Controllers try to avoid meeting with chimeras because they are not able to subordinate them with their psi attacks. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Seeing a person, she usually sneaks from behind and attacks. If the chimera has noticed a stalker, she will attack him until she kills, which does not give her chances to escape from her. In the event that you have time to dodge the attacking chimera, try to shoot it from behind. Guess your movement under her jumps, dodge and jump away - it's important not to lose sight of her. Keep the monster away for short distances and do not let him use claws. A good result is also provided by the following method - climb up the hill (for example, on the roof of the garage) and shoot it from above. At light and medium levels, the difficulty does not pose a great danger, but at the difficulty levels, "Veteran" and "Master" poses a mortal threat to the life of the player. \n
			\n\n
			There is one trick in the battle with the chimera: the pillar. If you stand behind a pillar or any similar object (a thin tree, a rack of power lines, a grid fence) through which the Chimera can not jump, she will helplessly hack into the obstacle and will not be able to reach you, constantly jumping off and again attacking the pillar, if you, of course , will keep up with him for hiding. Having adopted this tactic and having a good reaction, you can destroy a mutant without a single touch.\n
			\n\n
			The most effective tactic is an underbarrel grenade launcher. The most important thing is to shoot the chimera under your feet until she has time to jump. If you kill it in a jump, you can watch the already dead body of the mutant attacking the main character. Usually dies from one grenade, if that hit right to the target. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High Vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Great Strength and Speed Attack. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Funeral.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Almost silent attack. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Vulnerability in the field of an underdeveloped head.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] If you dodge the jump, for a while, substitutes the back for shooting.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Slowness after a jump.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Has only one type of attack. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] The electric chimera is a semi-legendary creature about which, almost, nothing is known.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Very dangerous predators. Night. They go in the dark behind your back - and jump. If you know that next to the chimera, turn your head to three hundred and sixty and keep your friends' ".%c[0,215,215,215] Trapper.
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_controller">
		<text>Controller</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_controller_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Human.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Attack type%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Abidance to own will. Psy attack.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Humanoid with hypertrophied head.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]High.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Dungeons, tunnels and abandoned laboratories.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]He need to see a target to use psy attack.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n The controller is one of the most dangerous mutants found in the Zone. The result of genetic experiments conducted by scientists on the development program in a person of telepathic abilities. He has high telepathic abilities - the victims' brain lesions are almost always irreversible. Trying to move so as to constantly keep the enemy in sight. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Strictly speaking, controllers appeared as a result of experiments conducted in the Zone by Common-consciousness scientists in the X16 laboratory. After the first Emission, the X16 laboratory was damaged, and the experimental ones were left to themselves. Outwardly, the controller looks like a man of thick build with a disproportionately large head, on his head pathetic hair, deep set, bulging eyes, pulsating ulcers on either side of the head, torso wrapped in rags or bandages, dressed in old rags or pants / jeans. Controller's peculiarity is the impact on the mind of his victim, subjecting it to his will - when he meets a stalker or another weaker mutant, at the expense of the abilities of a developed and mutated brain, tries to take the victim under control. The psycho-blow of the controller inflicts considerable mental damage, the control over his actions is lost, accompanied by an incredible headache and there is a feeling that the limbs are filled with lead, it takes more than one hour to depart from the meeting with him. The controller moves slowly, in SC when approaching the monster, a close stalker receives damage without visible actions on the part of the controller, whereas in CP and CS he can strike the stalker with his hands.. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Controller, despite his strong mental abilities, is quite a coward. With sharp attacking actions of the enemy, 	controller disappears from sight trying to catch the enemy by surprise. It lives in dungeons, laboratories and ruins of old buildings, only very strong hunger can force them to lean out of their shelters, but sometimes it also occurs in open terrain. Controllers are in the habit of keeping an entourage with them, consisting mainly of zombies, dogs and snorkers, which serve as both guard and food for them. If he takes control of a stalker, he most often forces to shoot at his own groupmates. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Does not touch burers and Izloms. Probably because they are victims of the experiments of the scientific program "Universal Soldier", they only refer to different branches of creation. Mutants such as rats, Boars and flesh serve as food for him. He tries to avoid meetings with Bloodsuckers, Chimeras and Pseudogiantes, as they are not subject to his psi-abilities. —ontroller uses Zombies as a means to fulfill his own goals: he uses both combat power and protection \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_controller_text2">
		<text>\n The controller attacks with directed psi-strokes, which causes severe damage to the brain of the victim. Also after prolonged exposure, the enemy becomes zombified. He is able to disorient the victim and not let her concentrate. The presence of the controller is shown by a blue screen, which is similar to illusions, there is also a ringing in the ears and a slight swinging, which hints at psychotropic pressure. Since it is almost impossible to get into the head of the controller, being under his influence, it is worthwhile to shoot where it is easier to get to - the stomach. It is also possible to successfully attack a monster with a grenade launcher, but it's best to remove the controller from a distance, until he sees you, in tight spaces it's best to hide around the corner and throw grenade at the mutant. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High Vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Effective psi attacks.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] After a psi attack, the protagonist can not use the weapon for a while.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Psi-attack is disorienting in space. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Can dislodge weapons from the hands.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] One of the most clever mutants in the Zone.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Psi-radiation, causes serious damage if you get close. \n%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] If you lose visual contact with the target, he will not be able to use psi abilities.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Pretty slow.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] The inability to conduct a psi attack at short distances.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] For a creature with developed psi abilities, has a surprisingly limited range of vision, may not notice the player in the daylight in the light of the sun with ten steps, unless he is directly in front of the mutant. Perhaps due to this fact Contollers are underground creatures. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Dies from one or two successfully thrown grenades.%c[default] \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Tunnel controller is a rare subspecies, capable of attacking from a shorter distance.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Underground controller is a species that is even more rare.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" A rare mutant that you can meet closer to the center of the Zone. Outwardly resembles a humanoid with a disproportionately enlarged head. Has a developed perception, as well as the ability to control the behavior of less developed living beings.
			Hardened individuals are able to take even people under control. This is a dangerous opponent, whose meetings are feared even by the most experienced stalkers ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Contoller fights against you with brains. Not in the sense that he thinks, but in the sense that he is a telepath. You, When you hunt for him, often use cover, he can attack only if he sees you. And again: He does not know how to run. So, if you absolutely will, try to treat him with a grenade".%c[0,215,215,215] Trapper.%c[default] \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]"€ Contollers are, of course, the most intelligent creatures of the Zone, their intellect is closest to the human, and they look almost like people, but do not forget that the Contoller brain is almost always affected by radiation and spontaneous mutations. They are not people, no. If they were people, if they had at least half of the human mind, cruelty, deceit and lust for power, they would have already crushed all life in the Zone for themselves. In addition to those creatures that they do not obey: Bloodsucker, dogs and marsh monsters ...¿".%c[0,215,215,215] Hemul, "The Zone of Defeat ¿.
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_crow">
		<text>Crow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_crow_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n\n
			\n%c[guide_blue]Crow%c[default] are the only species of birds that survived in the Zone.\n
			\n In order not to perish in the labyrinth of gravitational anomalies, military pilots use sophisticated detectors. But the secret of how Crow moves safely in the sky of the Zone is still a mystery.\n
			\n About what makes Crow in the Zone so special, and why they remained almost completely genetically intact, compared to the rest of the local wildlife, there is virtually no reliable information.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]General information%c[default]\n
			\nX Health: Weak\nX Speed: High\nX Features: Non-agressive to people
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_flesh">
		<text>Flesh</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_flesh_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Mutated pig.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] He tries to knock his victim off his feet. Blows with claws-claws.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Muttered beyond recognition, a pig with modified legs and different eyes.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Low, most vulnerable in the eye.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Everywhere. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Very rarely attacks first.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Flesh - mutated to the unrecognizability of the pig, one of the most harmless mutants in the Zone. \n  
			\n\n
			The forelimbs turned into insect-like legs - sharpened toothy "saws", which Flesh uses to dig out roots, tearing down carrion, attack and defense. The bones are thickened, therefore, because of the large weight of the skeleton, flesh often needs to rest. Flesh has a high degree of regeneration, which allows them to recover quickly after injuries. Despite the omnivore, the inner structure of the flesh is still approximated to the herbivorous, and not predatory, animal. The stomach is well stretched and digests food for a long time because of an irregular diet. The eyes of the flesh also evolve - one gradually decreases (but does not disappear at all), the second has the ability to quickly rotate in different directions, and the third eye Flesh can "smell," said the famous scientist Sakharov. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Pigs also underwent mutations as well as all other organisms in the Zone. The new ecological situation is characterized by increased activity of new environmental factors, including numerous mutagenic factors. By acting in a complex, physical, chemical, biological, and anomalous mutagenic factors lead to new Type mutations that affect all levels of organization of the genetic material of organisms - DNA. In different parts of the zone, the activity of some factors varies, as a result we can observe a wide variety of manifestations of the mutational process. One of the brightest examples is "Flesh" - a mutated domestic pig. It can be said with certainty that the genetic information of this organism was subject to significant influence of mutagens. The genes controlling the basic life processes and ways of metabolism were touched, from which, the phenType of the animal was greatly changed. The very existence of this mutant is a great miracle, since most mutations lead to a fatal outcome. \n			
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Flesh graze in small groups, do not behave aggressively, but if they are many, they are ready to defend themselves. They like to ambush, hiding in the bushes, but they hunt only when they are hungry. Due to biological proximity, they often wander with Boar. Often fighting with dogs for the territory, but they can also get along with them in relative proximity. Like all the creation of the zone, they can bypass the anomalies, but in a panic they may well fall into a trap. Quite sneaky, alone does not pose a danger, however, getting lost in a pack can pose a serious danger to the stalker. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n They often graze along with the Boar, conflict with the dogs, with the stronger mutants do not fight (and do not occur). \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_flesh_text2">
		<text>
			\n Flesh will protect their lair from several stalkers, but when a large group appears, they will most likely run away. If you attack the flesh - they will start to run around and bewilder. They will unexpectedly beat from different sides, spontaneously counterattack. The best advice is to kill a few, then the flesh will disappear in a panic. It is also desirable to press your back against the fence or boulder, so that the Mutants do not surround you. If there is a Boar in the pack - kill them first: Avoid their attacks and hit in the back. Against such flocks fit shotguns and submachine guns, against a couple of individuals can use a pistol. If you decide to hunt, you can start offensive with grenades. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]External cover.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Sealed and characterized by the presence of several additional layers of modified epidermis. On the transverse microsections, an additional layer of cells is well distinguished. Strongly thickened shining layer and keratinized, indicates an increased reproductive potential of epithelial cells. Also on microphotographs, undifferentiated epithelial cells are clearly visible. This probably explains the regeneration capabilities of the skin of these mutants. I especially want to note that the structure of keratin - the main building protein - has changed significantly - its mechanical parameters have increased. In the superficial layers, blotches of bone tissue are distinctly distinguishable. Their function is rather protective. \n  
			\n\n
			Fabrics on the limbs, too, have changed: gradually a relatively soft tissue of hoofs is replaced by bone tissue. The splitting of the hoof is now represented by one long bone growth that the mutant can use to attack. \n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Keep in packs, often with Boars.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] They can suddenly attack from different sides.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Quickly hide from sight, especially in the marshes. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low damage.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Few groups of flesh prefer to flee.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Poorly developed sense organs. You can sneak up on a pack close and attack. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Forest, steppe and swamp flesh. There is also a pseudo-Flesh. Forest flesh is almost no different from their steppe counterparts, which can not be said about the marsh: it can be immediately distinguished by a ton of color and blisters on the muzzle. \n			 
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Like most other living creatures in the Zone, the domestic pic also underwent serious biological changes since the day of the catastrophe. It seems the genes responsible for metabolism were especially affected in this case. Mutant pigs, known simply as Flesh among the stalkers, are one of the most vivid examples of the Zone's disastrous perversion of nature. Mutant pigs developed a protective layer of scales and exoskeletal plates. Their regeneration potential increased several times, as did the complexity of their nervous system. Just like a normal pig, a Flesh is an omnivore and may attack a stalker if hungry.  ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" These are the innocuous of the mutants. Try to stay away from stalkers, but if you attack them, they will defend themselves. It is more dangerous if among the flesh Boar falls. An animal for three hundred pounds is not a toy for you! Try not to be on the runway during the hunt. On the other hand, the inertia of him, too, oh-go: such a carcass as a boar can not instantly turn around. It turns out, dodge it - and shot!"%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_fracture">
		<text>Fracture</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_fracture_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Man, the victim of experiments.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Rubbed into the confidence of stalkers, follows them, scares off mutants, who are not afraid helps to destroy. Hungry for food, asks for food. If you do not give, then attack from the back. Can give a lot of valuable information.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Outwardly reminiscent of a tramp. Under the cloak hides his hypertrophied claw.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Medium.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Not far from stalker bases.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Attack with a hypertrophied arm, at a decent distance.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]General Information.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n A tall, thin, hunched mutant with pronounced elongated limbs. The head and skin color resemble a zombie, but Izlom is not. He walks in a half-squat, dragging his hands on the ground. Runs additionally pushing hands like the primates. When the wound begins to run right side, dragging his left hand.
			Has a human head, clearly visible skull outlines. There is a weak scalp on the sides and on the back of the head. Southeastern hollows, large nose. \n 
			The head is connected with an elongated thick neck-hump - closer to the head the neck resembles the human, and at the shoulder girdle it joins the hump of Izloma. Among this muscular formation there is an enlarged Adam's apple. \n 
			The very body of Izlom is thin, the skeleton is visible. The arms are much longer than human ones - this can be seen on the sleeves of the robes. The left is longer by about a quarter, this is noticeable in the brush. The mutant's brushes themselves are greatly enlarged (unlike the fingers), and the left has sharp claws.\n 
			Walks in the old form of CLR workers: a dirty robe (perhaps, once was white) green-brown with the CLR emblem, torn at the elbows due to the length of the mutant's hands and slightly in the hump area, and dirty jeans, slightly torn from below and on lap. There is no shoe, because of what on the feet there are large calluses. There is a weak club foot. \n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n It is the result of experiments of the CSRIP. The experiments were carried out in the field of studies of pyrokinetic and extrasensory. For the last victim, implants were implanted with special amplifiers. \n 
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_fracture_text2">
		<text>
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Can exhibit aggression, but can also help in the exchange, for example, of food. It attacks a stalker only from the back, but he is usually not very aggressive. He hides his hand under his clothes, so that he will not be attacked immediately. Very cunning. Its main trick is to scream because of the bushes "Help! I'm wounded! "(Often can remember replicas, short phrases, dialogs, use either as a trick or as useful information). Stalker-beginners are guided by a trick and go to help a friend, after which they receive a crushing blow with a hypertrophied limb. He lives close to stalkers, sometimes gets along with them. For food can tell useful information about the Zone. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n It feeds on various small animals: rats, flesh, dogs, carcasses and all human food. Neutral to the burer and supervisors. Often dwells with zombies.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude towards people.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n They are often hostile to people. But sometimes they can get along with, if they feed him. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Greater Attack Power.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Often accompanied by zombies. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Small Speed of movement.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Medium, closer to low, Vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Has only one type of attack. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Unknown.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" His hand can be sold for a lot of money. And if the conversation goes well, you can get some useful information from it ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_karlik">
		<text>Dwarf</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_karlik_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Most likely - the victims of the experiment.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] During the attack, they beat their strong hands, inflict telekinetic attacks. During the escape tries to hide behind shelters. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Dwarf, about a meter tall.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Increased; The most vulnerable part of the body is the head.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Presumably in underground laboratories, cellars and natural caves.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] They live in families, have the beginnings of religion.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Until now, it is not clear who is a subspecies - a dwarf or a burer? Be that as it may, dwarfs are much more common. They were also formed as a result of experiments under the "universal soldier" program. Because of the dwelling in the dungeons, their skin is pale yellowish-white with a hint of green, blind from light. Well (but not like the bureurs), telekinesis and foresight are developed and fight hands well. Their head is also hypertrophied. Degree of reasonableness is very high. \n  
			\n\n
			The ugly dwarf, dwells in the dungeons, does not like to appear in the light. Dwarfs have very powerful hands, with which they can tear their victims, developed intellect and quick reaction. The character of dwarfs is extremely vile, nervous anger forces them to commit wild and unexpected acts. Their character, along with intelligence, makes them one of the most dangerous enemies in the Zone. They have a strong foreboding and telekinetic abilities.
			There is a collective mind. Immunities to radiation, succumb to psi-radiation. At a fright they run up with a squeal, like a child's.
			During the run, they quickly move their small feet. Approaching 5-10 meters to a place with shelters stops and tries to feel the enemy at a distance. In his absence, continues to move.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Exact origin of dwarfs is unknown. Most likely, they were created in the laboratory and are the results of some experiments. Probably, children were used as experimental subjects. \n
			Perhaps related to the program "Universal Soldier". \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_karlik_text2">
		<text>\n Inhabit dwarfs, like the burers, in the dungeons and do not tolerate light. There they arrange workshop traps for stalkers with the help of garbage (they cover the passages, cause the collapse of the tunnels). They themselves see in the dark wonderful. For some unknown reason, they hate blind dogs. Perhaps (not proven), have their own religious cult -? worship stolen goods from the stalkers. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Burers are their leaders, who must obey unquestioningly. Blind dogs are sworn enemies that need to be killed, even at the cost of their lives. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude towards people.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n For them, people are just food. Extremely aggressive, they attack even single-handedly. Arrange traps for stalkers, scientists and military. Overlap the exits with the help of various large debris, debris and beams.  \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Leader of dwarfs.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n All dwarves worship the leader named Burer - the evil "dwarf master." He is deep underground and is the sole ruler of all dwarfs. Occurs in an underground laboratory in the Dark Valley, never rising to the upper levels. "Master" Burer has the most powerful telekinetic gift in the Zone, can lift very large objects (stone blocks, metal beams) into the air. The dwarves never descend to Burer, always receiving only telepathic orders, they "tremble with fear" at the thought of such blasphemy. Among the dwarfs themselves go terrible stories about the incredible cruelty of their leader. \n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Telekinesis.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Telepathy. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Telekinetic shield.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Attack on distance.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Very large Vitality. \n			
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] When hit by bullets - falls into hysterics.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Telepathic abilities of dwarfs are much weaker than the abilities of the controller.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Can not use, many abilities, without visual contact. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173 Brown dwarfs.. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Small dwarfs - can live on the surface. \n			 
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]"... stalker moves along the dark corridors, wades through the jungles of the rubble of various industrial debris - beams, rusty structures, concrete blocks, etc. In the hands of AK-74, the belt has a life-form detector. The detector delivers its quiet signal - a large live mass at a distance of 10 meters. The stalker turns off the sound of the detector and freezes in a dark corner, three meters from it a passage through which, presumably, a dwarf will go. The detector signals about the approach of live weight - eight meters, seven, six, five ... five ... five ... The dwarf sensed something! The stalker keeps the passage on sight, it seems to him that the darkness is a little thickened. The dwarf stands five meters further along the aisle and, it seems, too, waits. Here the stalker almost opens fire, a brick slowly and silently flies into the passage, it rotates a little. The brick hangs in two meters in front of the stalker. Silence is not violated. The brick, swinging slightly, unfolds in the air. He rises a bit and rushes to the stalker. Having received a noticeable blow with a brick, the stalker does not stand and rushes into the passage to attack the dwarf, but he is greeted by an avalanche of flying bricks... ".%".%c[0,215,215,215]Folks.
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogiant">
		<text>Pseudogiant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogiant_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Unknown.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Presumably, the result of experiments on people.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Fast moves to the victim, stunning by powerful shock waves with help of its own strong paws.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] A huge drop-shaped body with a pair of hypertrophied limbs.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Very High.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Everywhere.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Slow, strong blows, radioactive.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n A huge drop-shaped monster up to two meters tall. For movement and attack uses the so-called "hand-held", always attacks the forehead. Quite tenacious. It attacks either coming up close, or "slapping" the hypertrophied limb about the ground, creating a local shock wave. Presumably, it is an asexual being. Has a cumbersome formless body and an underdeveloped leg under the tail. Despite this he runs well, he is cheerful in counterattacks. The Pseudogiant has a large, slightly smaller body and a head that is disproportionately small in relation to the body. His uneven head is "decorated" with numerous dents and craters - traces of some mutational processes. It seems that sees Pseudogiant with only one eye. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Quite stupid, but extremely strong and enduring. His origin is unknown, but, presumably, he is a man (in favor of this, the foot near the tail and the outline of a muzzle that resembles a human face from a distance say that some of the documents describe that the sources of Pseudogiant are broilers. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The mutant hunts solely alone. Pseudogiant do not have a special tactic of hunting, they attack without any thought into the forehead of any prey. Pseudogiant huntes at any time of the day, often found in underground laboratories, but can also be selected outside. At the sight of a man with a roar they rush at him. Mostly he eats only killed prey, but sometimes he does not disdain to carrion. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Hostile to almost everyone. It is known that Pseudogiant does not hunt tushkanos (they are too small to be his prey and he kills them solely in self-defense), and hates chimera and bloodsuckers, since they are his strongest enemies from mutants, due to the fact that they possess very high mobility and Vitality. He also attacks the pseudo-dog and blind dogs, furiously fights with Boar and flesh. Burers, Snorkes and controllers try to avoid meeting him, but they are not talking about open hostility, because they are, in most cases, neutral to each other. The only mutant that is not of particular interest to Pseudogiant is the Poltergeist (most likely it is because he can not catch up and kill him). \n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogiant_text2">
		<text>%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude towards people.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Always attacks people and without delay. Armed man for him is the worst enemy. He never gives up, even when he is under a hail of bullets. Probably, such anger Pseudogiant to people is associated with experiments in which this mutant was grown.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] A huge supply of health. The most tenacious living creature in the entire Zone. Is able to withstand two direct hits from RPG-7y and two explosions on mines.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Huge attack power. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Will create shock waves, hitting under which you are deafened - you walk more slowly and can not run.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] The body of the monster radiates a background radiation. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Absence of pronounced sensitive areas.\n%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Underdeveloped intellect.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] High visibility.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low maneuverability due to large dimensions.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Quickly discovers his position with loud steps. If Pseudogiant walks nearby, you can notice a shaking of the ground, so there is almost no chance of catching the victim by surprise.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] The belly is the Weak place.%c[default] \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] There is no particular difference between Pseudogians, except that they can be divided into ordinary (reddish skin and greenish wool) and hardened (yellowish skin and gray hair).\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" The pseudogiant resembles a massive, drop-shaped abdomen with a pair of disproportionately large limbs. The limbs are arms and legs at the same time. The creature uses them to move around and grab its victims. An adult pseudogiant can weight up to two tons and stand 2 meters tall. Their clumsy appearance might be deceiving, since they can move very rapidly if needed. Their muscles are exceptionally powerful and their bones are as hard as steel. The creature's brain is protected by a sturdy (up to 10 centimeters thick) skull, while many complex functions are controlled by the spinal medulla. Another astonishingfeature of the beast is its ability to create local shock waves, which damage all living things in the vicinity.  ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" With this beast the most difficult thing is to kill him: he is as tough as a tank. The only thing that I can advise effective - try the shot point-blank. The main thing, remember: the giant flings everything that is not covered in two meters of concrete, no matter how much it weighs. That is, attack it from above - it's better, - just make sure that your support is strong ".%c[0,215,215,215] Trapper.%c[default] \n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_poltergeist">
		<text>Poltergeist </text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_poltergeist_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Possibly a humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Victims of the experiment.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Attacks a person using telekinesis. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Flying, sparks surrounded by sparks.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Medium, closer to low. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Dungeons, rarely - open spaces. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Reacts to movement.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n These are truly supernatural beings, found only in the depths of the Zone. They live, as a rule, inside dilapidated buildings. In their non-material form, they are half invisible, since they represent a certain clot of supposedly electricity. Reminiscent of a human body without legs. Few of the stalkers ever saw this mutant, so all the information about him is drawn from vague and rather contradictory stories, the truthfulness of which is questionable. Poltergeist is blind and deaf. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The origin of the Poltergeists stalkers is reliably unknown. But there is a legend that these are the spirits of stalkers caught under the ejection. In fact, Poltergeist - the victim of experiments on the transformation of matter into the field structure. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Constantly flies his territory, does not do anything else. The enemy feels at a great distance and attacks immediately. At the detection the victim hears a certain similarity of a low beeping of small loudness. At close range, the psi-abilities of the Poltergeist begin to appear, and the visual perception of the enemy's world changes color to blue-violet (regardless of subspecies).\n
			At death, it breaks up into bloody scrapes that literally evaporate in the air. You can also hear a deaf echo, similar to howling and groaning at the same time. When a telepathic Poltergeist is applied to damage, it emits an electrical sound. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Since Poltergeists almost always live in dark and underground rooms, occasionally leaving there, they very rarely meet other representatives of the fauna of the Zone. If they were in an open area, they would be at enmity with blind dogs, Boars, pseudo dogs and flesh. \n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_poltergeist_text2">
		<text>
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude towards people.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Hostile to people. They attack from afar: depending on the subspecies, they are thrown by various heavy objects, or create local pillars of flame. When approaching a person tries to fly away and hide in some kind of shelter, but still continues the attack. \n
			It is best to enforce it in close combat - its low survivability combined with its not-so-high movement speed makes it an easy prey. Shotguns are especially effective, high-precision rifles are of little use in this case due to the peculiarities of the mutant's body structure. Occurs in the experimental labs of the Zone, so you must prepare for every battle beforehand, knowing exactly what to expect and under what conditions you'll have to work. \n
			Must aim a little higher than the center of the "glow" when shooting otherwise bullets will go in the milk. \n
			If you throw out any garbage (for example a dozen loaves) or throw bolts to the ground before the fight, the Poltergeist (like the burer) will throw them away without harming your health. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Telekinesis.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Intangible form.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Attack at a distance. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Vulnerable to explosions. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] A small amount of health. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Fire Poltergeist  - are more rare species. In non-material form has a red-orange color. He leaves near the enemy energy clots, from which burst the pillars of the flame. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]"Supernatural in the eyes of some, invisible creatures haunting the deeper reaches of the Zone, usually haunting old, abandoned buildings. Nothing is known about their origin, although rumors in circulation claim they are spirits of stalkers hit by a massive wave of radiation. Their mysterious appearances and disappearances seem to correspond to the poltergeist legend, hence the name. Known encounters with poltergeists are quite diverse in fact: from mischievous laughter and blood-chilling howling, to deadly fireballs appearing out of nowhere. Unfortunately, all information about the poltergeist phenomenon originates from unclear and contradictory stories of questionable validity ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" These are of two types: some gravitating sweep objects into you, others try to fry. Who is inexperienced - starts to reel around, but this is just not necessary. A poltergeist has one feature, even two: blind and deaf. He does not see, he does not hear, but he perfectly feels everything that moves in his field. An experienced hunter hunts a poltergeist like this: stopped for a while and then stopped again. ".%c[0,215,215,215] Trapper.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudodog">
		<text>Pseudodog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudodog_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_green]General Information:%c[default]\n\n
			\n%c[guide_blue]Pseudodog%c[default] frequently come across dog-like mutants.\n
			\n Despite the name, pseudodogs lead their ancestry not from dogs, but from wolves who lived in the forests of the Zone at the time of the second catastrophe.\n
			\n Actually, there are not so many pseudops and left from the wolf - their head is more rounded, with huge, very strong jaws with numerous huge teeth.\n
			\n Pseudo dogs are often seen with blind dogs, although they are much faster, stronger and more aggressive than their blind relatives. Pseudo dogs are also territorial predators and, without hesitation, attack uninvited guests.\n
			\n Powerful muscles and a modified skeleton allow him to move with incredible Speed and make huge rapid jumps, which makes them much more agile than most other members of the canine family.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]General information%c[default]\n
			\nX Health: Medium\nX Speed: High\nX Features: Rapid
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogeist">
		<text>Black Poltergeist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogeist_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Black Poltergeists %c[default] are a rare subspecies of Poltergeist.\n
			\nFor sure about these creatures nothing is known, since they appeared relatively recently.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\n By appearance resemble a cluster of coal-black clouds, killing any loser, who was unlucky to wander into their possessions.\n
			\nBlack Poltergeists are not tied to any particular habitat. As a rule, they appear where no one suspects them.\n
			\n At death, they are torn into numerous formations similar to the initial cloud, which are then scattered.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]General information%c[default]\n
			\nX Health: Medium\nX Speed: Medium\nX Features: Psi-impact
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pyrogeist">
		<text>Fire Poltergeist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pyrogeist_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Fire Poltergeist %c[default] are a rare subspecies of the Poltergeist, capable of pyrokinesis.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
			\nThey look like a haze, surrounded by a fiery glow. Therefore, they are easily distinguished from the usual Poltergeist. At death they burst into a mash of blood and fire.\n
			\n The only way to attack - resembling an anomaly "frying", directed the pillars of fire, with which they try to burn their enemies, since they do not possess any telekinetic abilities.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]General information%c[default]\n
			\nX Health: Medium\nX Speed: Medium\nX Features: Fire and Psi influence
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psydog">
		<text>Psy-dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psydog_text">
		<text>
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Mutated Wolf.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Rapidly runs to the victim, attacks in a jump.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Squat dog with fanged mouth.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Medium, the vulnerable part is the head.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Everywhere. The habitat includes most of the locations - from the Cordon to the city of Pripyat inclusive. In the depths of the Zone there are the most difficult individuals capable of causing mental relatives. Often in the Landfill, Research Institute "Agroprom" and in the Dark Valley.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Attack in the pack.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Powerful musculature and a modified skeleton allow this monster to move with incredible Speed and make huge swift jumps. The pseudo dog is very resistant to radiation and shock anomalies. There is evidence that a large strong individual without serious damage will survive and acquaintance with "Kisel". He jumps far and, perhaps, knows how to "teleport" for short distances. \n
			The psi-possibilities of pseudo-dogs, with the exception of some subspecies, are small. Mature individuals are capable of inflicting psi-strokes on the victim, if it is a question of stalkers, then to direct the directed weapon away from theirself. \n
			The first meeting with the pseudo-dog makes an immense impression on the beginner - sometimes fatal. Many stalkers consider the pseudo-dog to be the real "spirits of death" of the Zone. However, with experience, the causeless fear of this objectively not the most dangerous creature passes. \n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n When looking at the appearance of a pseudo dog, it seems very doubtful that it has originated from a wolf. The form of the muzzle of the animal has been changed so much that discussions are still going on about whether the pseudo-dog is a mutation of the known species of animals or has taken place as a separate species. \n
			Strictly speaking, there is not much left of the wolf in the pseudo-dog. Most of all, the head was changed: round, with huge, but not very prominent jaws, armed with numerous huge teeth, growing throughout the life of the animal. At a sight the more or less similar breed of a dog - the bulldog is recollected. Also in the guise of it there is something anthropomorphic, but very distant, so one can not assert with absolute certainty the mutation of this monster of the Zone from the animals known to us. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n These creatures lead a territorial way of life and violently attack anyone who invades their possessions. They are often found singly, but they can also be found in pairs and small flocks, in a half-dozen individuals (in the most extreme cases, you can see a flock of ten individuals). Often you can see how the pseudo-dog is led by a flock of blind dogs. But it is unlikely that this "cooperation" extends beyond one joint hunt. Pseudo dogs can be tamed, but you need to start with a very small puppy. There are at least two stalkers known to have succeeded: the Doctor has a dog Druzhok, and Noah has a female dog, Lessie, who later brought off her offspring who helped a group of stalkers who hid themselves in the barge from mutants when they attacked it during a particularly powerful emission.\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psydog_text2">
		<text>%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Alone, the pseudodog attacks any mutant that is smaller than its size (for example, tushkanos or rats). From larger mutants escapes at the first sight. But being a pack, they will attack anyone who invades their territory or disturbs during the feast. They have ubiquitous enemies - Boar and flesh. In the battles with them, as a rule, they win. Stronger opponents for them - Snorki, Burer and Bloodsucker, whom they are able to overcome only a large number. The most dangerous enemy for a pseudodog is Pseudogiant, who, because of powerful attacks and a huge amount of health, can kill a whole flock alone. Pseudo dogs are neutral to chimeras, controllers and Poltergeist am. Among the allies - only fellows and blind dogs, with whom pseudo dogs often arrange joint hunting.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Battle tactics.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n A pseudo dog does not differ either intellect or population (rarely when you can see more than three monsters in one flock). It moves though fast, but without completely maneuvering, which makes it an easy target, even for the inexperienced shooter. In addition, she always attacks the enemy at an angle of 90 degrees, and if you take into account that her massive head occupies about half of the chest, then even an unnecessary line is likely to hit the mutant in the face, which in the presence of an appropriate caliber can kill it on place. In the event of a collision with the pack, only the number of targets changes, but the tactic remains the same - letting it get closer and putting lead in the throat. In general, this species is not far away from blind dogs and in some ways even inferior to it. \n  
			\n\n			
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Speed.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Hunting in the pack. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Funeral. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] If you dodge the jump, for a while substitutes the back for shooting.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Slowness after a jump.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Comparatively low Health. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Psi-dog.\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Mature pseudodog.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Despite the name, pseudo dogs did not come from dogs, but from wolves. Wild animals that lived in the forests of the Zone at the time of the disaster, became the ancestors of one of the most dangerous species of mutants. Pseudo dogs are not so similar to mutated dogs as wild wolves do not look like mongrels. These creatures lead a territorial way of life and violently attack anyone who invades their possessions. Lightning-fast reaction, incredible mobility and sharp teeth make the pseudo-dog a very serious opponent, against which it is difficult to resist even a large mutant or a well-armed stalker".%c[0,215,215,215] Encyclopedia.\n  
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Not as dangerous alone, as in a dense pack. They Attack only if they are hungry, but they are almost always hungry. If you are hunting a pack, try to beat from the hill, otherwise you will simply be overwhelmed by pressure, especially if there are a few full-grown in the pack. Pseudodogs of a few surviving blind dogs, but smarter - and therefore more dangerous. If a whole flock suddenly appears in place of one, remember: those that attack you are phantoms. A real pseudo dog will stay away, only occasionally running up to bite. So try to figure it out quickly. As soon as the present one dies, all phantoms will disappear at once".%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_rat">
		<text>Rat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_rat_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Rat. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] 1-2 individuals do not represent danger. Flocks attack, attack with bites.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Looks like an ordinary rat.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Low. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Presumably in underground laboratories, cellars and natural caves .... 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Hunted exclusively by the swarm.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Rats are the constant companion of man. And in the places where people left, they are even more free to live. Apparently, factors such as radiation and Habitat played a role here. It is unlikely that these rats, by habits and physiology, have gone far beyond the usual. Do not give in to radiation and easily adapt to other unfavorable factors. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Many animals had to mutate in order to win the right to life from the Zone. But gray rats are already brilliant masters of survival. Rats are not from the underground laboratory complexes, they are the true owners of the Zone, and not its children. Perhaps they are carriers of anthrax.\n
			\n\n
			It is difficult to imagine a more adapted organism. Radiation and anomalies practically did not affect rat physiology, but forced them to learn to recognize new dangers. This known resistance of rats to the effects of radiation is explained by the effectiveness of their DNA repair systems. Rapid reproduction rates and a large number of descendants allow them to quickly adapt to new environmental conditions.\n
			\n\n
			Apparently, thanks to the still poorly studied psychoethological features, the rat pack acts as a whole organism. In fact, single individuals do not represent anything interesting from the point of view of science. Only in the pack of rats are their most interesting properties, such as collective intelligence. Moreover, the more individuals in the pack, the more coordinated its actions. This interaction is similar to that in fish groups. But on land scientists met with a similar phenomenon for the first time. To coordinate the actions of the rat, apparently, use a special kind of psycho-wave communication, it is not excluded and the option with ultra- / infrasound. The latter has several proofs in his favor: for example, rat insanity. A single individual issuing an infrasound of a certain frequency is not taken into account as dangerous. But the pack, using coherent waves and the amplification effect (interference), is already a real threat to the life of the stalker. Also, the effect of rat insanity can be caused by toxins or microorganisms contained in saliva and on the teeth of rats.\n
			\n\n
			The scent and hearing of rats became much better; rather than as it was before, it was due to a deterioration in vision. It is due to hearing that the rat pack can act reasonably, make constant contact with other members of the flock through ultrasound. Infrasound is used only as a means of attack. The heads of each pack are rat wolves - they are very large, in relation to other rats, individuals, probably representing a subspecies or other species. The genetic similarity of rat wolves to ordinary rats is quite high, allowing a certain degree of kinship between them. Due to the size and special body, they can "broadcast" ultrasonic signals for the whole flock. 
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_rat_text2">
		<text>
			As a resonator for ultrasound production, they apparently use a special organ, which is a fat body surrounded by a connective tissue in such a sound lens. It is located in the cavity of the skull. An interesting feature is that small rats have an asymmetrical arrangement of teeth on the lower jaw: the right dentition is slightly shifted forward relative to the left one. The resonator for capturing ultrasounds in rats is precisely the lower jaw: from the sound-collecting organ (the auricle, Medium ear), a signal is transmitted through the fiber system to the lower jaw to enhance and differentiate. Each branch of the jaw is innervated by its own nerve, which has branches to each tooth. Since one row of teeth is further away, impulses from it come later. As a result, there is interference of sound waves, their analysis allows the rat to determine their character, direction and frequency. \n
			\n\n
			Vision of the rats, as they thought before, was no worse - in fact, the ratio between the rods and cones in the direction of the sticks slightly shifted (the sticks are responsible for the night vision), that is, the rats became better seen in the dark, but worse by light. In the dark their eyes glow red. To catch electromagnetic fields in rats there is a special organ: vibrissae, that is, their mustache, they play the role of such antennas. \n
			\n\n
			All scientists who studied the biology of the Zone agree that the rats perfectly adapted to the new conditions. It is difficult to imagine a more adapted organism, because a large number of offspring and fast current natural selection allow rats to adapt in the most severe conditions. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Rats meet in packs, in rare cases you can meet them alone. Rats feel dangerous places and carefully bypass them, warning the squeals of their brethren. They are very smart creatures and try to attack the victim from different angles. The victim, surrounded on all sides, has very little chance of surviving. They live in abandoned places and in dungeons. Perhaps they communicate by ultrasound, but this has not yet been proven. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Finally, this is unknown. Perhaps they are neutral to the tushkanos. One of the most dangerous enemies is the subspecies of the blind dog dog-rats. As in the outside world, most likely, cats are afraid. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n In most cases, They attack instantly, but they will also allow the leader to "chase" the victim in order to knock him out. In the case of a large number of victims from the rats, they escape. They can stay in place if they are full or for some reason can not leave their place. As described above, they attack stalkers, jumping on their backs and trying to bite the neck between 3 and 4 vertebrae. \n
			For the extermination of rats, stalkers use shotguns and grenades against them. Ideal option - flamethrower. \n 
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Attack in the pack.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Speed. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low vitality. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Rat wolves are large and aggressive rat individuals. When they are hungry they devour their relatives. Usually there are one rat wolf in a pack of ten rats. Rat wolves are the main backbone of a large school. They are immune to various poisons and strong radiation. More dangerous than ordinary rats. Rat wolves control their flock.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" Rat - After the disaster many animals died or left the Zone. The remaining rats have bred and become one of the most numerous animals in the zone ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_snork">
		<text>Snork</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_snork_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information: 
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Human.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Attack type%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Leapingly approaches and on a certain distance jumps to knock down a ravin. In close range combat hit out with hands and legs. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Humanoid, moves on all four. Face always covered by a gas-mask.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Medium, vulnerable while jumping (since shooting better in the mutant's chest to throw it back).
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Ruined buildings, dungeons, open space, caves.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] The ability to make fantastic jumps of 10-15 meters in length.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Snork, like Pseudogiant , - one of the mysteries of the Zone. The anatomical similarity of Snork and human's organism is 90-95 percents. As a result of irradiation and life on nature, the hairline disappeared, the body is strewn with bruises and wounds. The gas mask is shifted so the so the mouth with absent lips and dark reddish gums are clearly seen. There is an opinion that Snorks wear gas-masks with a purpose, but what is the purpose still unclear. They move using four limbs, often bend and crawl, constantly sniff the ground searching the ravin. Because of the destruction of cartilaginous material, the creature goes slightly hunched, as the spine can not endure permanent loads on the interlayers. The internal structure of the limbs has changed: a large number of tendons have appeared, allowing Snorks to make incredible jumps, to attack they approach to target like cats, trying to come from the back. They make sounds resembling an animal roar, sometimes they make sounds that resemble hooting, there are times when Snorks say something similar to curse. They live in packs, and organize a lair. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Versions of their origin are similar: many believe that Snork is the next step in degradation of zombies. The similarity with zombies ranges from 17% to 26%. Snorks are a partly mutated zombies, this explains why there are a lot of them near to the psi-fields. Apparently, when the zombie finally lose its weapon and remnants of memory, a new model of behavior was developed, close to the animal. The upright movement pattern is replaced by crawling, which reduces visibility and increases the movement speed. There are three possible versions. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestryle and behaviour.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n In general, Snorks live and hunt in a packs, the number of snorks in a Pack in nearly unlimited. However, they can hunt alone. They have a lair usually underground (caves, underground laboratories). The largest lair was seen on Yantar on the  swamp behind the laboratory. Usually they crawl on the grawnd, sniffing in search of a ravine, and if it is found, they come up rushing and then they do a big jump with a kick. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n For Snorks many creatures are a potential prey. Livin in open terrain, they have ubiquitous enemies which are Boar and Flesh. Wkirmishing with them usually winand then fiercely pursue the ones who left the battle. Snorks always attack Blind doga and disperse their packs. To pseudodogs the attitude is same, but for Snork to beat them is difficult because of their high mobility. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to humans and advice for a stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_snork_text2">
		<text>
			\n They will attack immediately any human. Shotguns are very effective against them. Do not think about long range combat Snork can jump very far and hits really hurt. The best option is a semi-close distance, so the mostre could not get enough space for and effective attack, and it is easy to predict his movements, and the aiming is easier. Keep in mind that Snork crawls when he moves, that allows the most part of pellets (if you will shoot at 90 degree angle) to hit directly in the head. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]C-Consciousness involvement.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The existence of snorks is shrouded in mystery like everything in the Zone, it is not clear where the new snorks come from. Also, perhaps this is one of the unsuccessful experiments of scientists on the project "Universal Soldier". Scientists may have wanted an obedient laboratory guard, immune to damage, capable of performing incredible leaps and firing on the fly, thereby dodging enemy attacks. Scientists have received: everything is the same, but naughty, aggressive, with animal instincts of a monster. In the X16 laboratory, there are corpses of dead single stalkers who died in a very strange way and began to mutate. If you look closely, their skin is suspiciously similar to the skin of a snork and some corpses were too similar to them. Especially in the laboratory about 7 snorks. Since all laboratories in the Zone belonged to O-Consciousness, it can be assumed that they were involved in the creation of snorks and this can be considered as a version, since O-consciousness has done too much “useful” for the Zone. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High range of a Jump. (from 15 to 20 meters).
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Strong attack.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High speed of attack. \n%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Weaknesses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Low vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] It is easily noticeable even at night - it starts to growl when approaching.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Slow when he is leaping.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] On the middle range does not jump, since he affraids to overjump.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] While jumping, inactive.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Most vulnerable during a jump.%c[default] \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Sub-species.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Snorks-man eaters are a rare species of especially dangerous creatures..
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Snorks-scavengers are a species even more rare.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]"These creatures, apparently, were once humans, although it is difficult to imagine what conditions can bring a person to such a state. Snorks are crazy creatures that lead a completely animal lifestyle, essentially differing little from predatory monsters of the Zone. They move to four limbs, bouncing above the ground and constantly sniffing it to catch the smell of prey.Care carefully and prudently, trapping stalkers like predatory animals. Lightning reflexes and hypertrophic muscles allow snorks to perform long exact jumps and tearing the victim to shreds in a few seconds. Some individuals retained details of the army uniform or individual details of equipment, which suggests the missing military or stalkers. "%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]"Remains of people... no rest for them. Single Snork is no big danger for a skillful hunter. You wait till he jumps and you shoot a charge in him. It is worse, if there is a couple of them: in this case you shoot them as fast as possible and dodge from them. Snorks know that, and that is why they does not attack one by one ".%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.%c[default] \n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_stronglav">
		<text>Stronglav</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_stronglav_text">
		<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]General Information:%c[default] \n \n
			\n Stronglav - the legendary three-meter bloody Bloodsucker. He lived at the Rostock plant before the Duty group arrived. They say that he is so smart that he plays with his victims. Stronglav is very old and lives here for a long time. And with age, Mutants become more insidious and quick-witted.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_tushkano">
		<text>Tushkano</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_tushkano_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215]Animal.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Mutated rat
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Flock attack victim. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Ugly rodent, a bit like a rat.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Very Low. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Everywhere. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Constantly make loud noises.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Stalkers call these animals tushkanos. In fact, these animals are not related to all known tushkanos, although they are very similar to them. It is not yet possible to specify exactly the species from which the tushkanos of the Zone occurred, since they underwent very profound changes during the mutation process; one can only assert that their ancestors were schooled animals, most likely some kind of rodent. Reaching up to 40 centimeters at the withers, they are much larger, faster, more mobile, more aggressive and more gluttonous than the usual desert animal and in general have nothing to do with it genetically. They live mainly in dungeons and ruined buildings, feeding on everything that gets caught - from plants to inattentive stalkers. Sometimes even large animals become victims of carcasses and Mutants: attacking a large flock, they will easily tear apart any creature that has not managed to escape.. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The fact that the tushkan is bred in the laboratory is confirmed by the fact that in X-18 in some chambers there are corpses of these rodents. Among stalkers, there are two opinions about the ancestor of these mutants: the first is a rat, the second is a mouse. \n
			In favor of the rat says the fact that the carcasses are aggressive and omnivorous. The second theory is supported by the fact that the tushkan has "mouse" ears, the number of fingers closer to the mice, and also the fact that the tail in the tusk is not as long as the rat's. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Reaching 40 cm at the withers, they are much more mobile, more aggressive and more gluttonous than the desolate beast. They live mainly in dungeons and ruined buildings, feeding on everything that gets caught - from plants to inattentive stalkers. They usually live in flocks, sometimes even in very impressive flocks of up to 50 individuals. As a rule, for 5-10 individuals. Easily amenable to the controller - the brain has small dimensions. However, their strength lies in flocks - being in the pack, their amount of intelligence and strength increases dramatically. Thus, it can be said that tushkanos-individuals do not exist. Hunt a flock, attack the victim with a crushing herd, chasing her, leaving no chance of escape. Those who do not flee, get strong bleeding wounds, or even lose their lives. A wounded pseudo-dog has no chance of salvation, if a flock of these rodents has spotted it. They also want to refresh themselves with a ready-made breakfast or a sleeping stalker. The harbingers of tunnels and dungeons have tenacious sharp teeth, capable of digging their way into the industrial environment in which they usually live. They perfectly oriented in various tunnels, dungeons, bunkers in full or partial darkness. They live in the same place, respectively. A gaggle of carcasses can swallow the body in a couple of minutes, if until that moment they were starving for at least one day.\n
			\n\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_tushkano_text2">
		<text>%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Sometimes even large animals become victims of carcasses and Mutants: attacking a large flock, they will easily tear apart any creature that has not managed to escape. They have a special aggression towards chimeras and urban Snorks. Often hunt together with blind dogs and pseudopags. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Sometimes they run away from people. In this case, you can quite confidently say that you are lucky. It is very difficult to guide shooting in the tuskans, and this makes them a curse of stalkers. Against them you can use grenades, but it is advisable to do this before the Mutants shorten the distance. Automatic weapons are not ideal, because of its high degree of accuracy, therefore, the best option in the fight against the carcasses is a shotgun. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Bites cause bleeding.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92]Move rapidly.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Hunting in the pack. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Very low vitality. \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Collector tushkanos - a subspecies living in sewer and collector pipes. There are five to seven individuals in a pack. Mostly males, although there is no apparent difference between male and female. They feed on stalkers and half-decayed corpses-zombies, who can walk. An important difference is that the amount of gray matter is very large, but vision is poor. Dimensions are less than average.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Deserts - are a subspecies of tushkans living far from people. They feed on meat of flesh, Boar, but do not disdain and carrion. In the pack there are about 10-15 individuals. They are rare. They can be recognized by the comparatively large size of the legs and the small size of the head. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" The horror of a hunter! One of the most stupid mistakes that can be made in life is to underestimate the animals because of their small size. The tushkanos are insanely fast and brisk and always move in large flocks. How they will start to stretch you in a small piece in different directions, you will immediately see the light! The main thing is to not be too late. Here, you know, the most unpleasant thing is? It's very difficult to get on the tushkanos. That's why I advise all stalkers on this occasion to always carry a shotgun with a stock of cartridges.."%c[0,215,215,215] Gonta.\n
		</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_vodianoy">
		<text>Waterman</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_vodianoy_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Unknown.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Presumably, the result of experiments on humans.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Fast movements, long jumps in the direction of the victim.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Carcass with thick hair, strange processes in the head, huge mouth.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]Medium.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Marshlands.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Prefers quick and unexpected attacks by jumping.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Even on a large land, swampy terrain often gets a bad name and a lot of rumors about any mysticism happening there. It is not surprising that the swamps in the Zone are even more notorious. Water is considered to be the most dangerous inhabitant of such places, this monster causes chilling fear of the soul even for seasoned stalkers, although nothing is known for sure about him.  \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n The exact origin is unknown. Perhaps it was once a man, as evidenced by a physique similar to an ordinary humanoid. A huge number of evidence of terrible experiments on people in the Zone, allows you to conclude that Water is not a victim of the effects of radiation. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and Behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n A secretive way of life, extreme aggression and habitat in swampy areas, in which stalkers prefer not to wander, contribute to the almost complete absence of information about these mutants. Some say that Watery in his habits reminds Snorkov, while others believe that the Water is only the fruit of the imagination of green newcomers, rustling every rustle in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_zombie">
		<text>Zombie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_zombie_text">
		<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]General Information:
			\n\n\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type%c[0,143, 188, 143]         - %c[0,215,215,215] Humanoid.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Origin%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] A person who has been exposed to psi-emitters or telepathic beings. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Type of attack %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Noticing the victim, moves to her and strikes with his hands. Quite slow. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Appearance %c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215] Walking half-dead in scraps of clothes.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Vitality%c[0,143, 188, 143]   - %c[0,215,215,215]High, vulnerable part - head. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Habitat%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] Abandoned settlements and laboratories. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,154, 205, 50] Features%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215] If after the fall you do not finish them, after 5-10 seconds it rises and again attacks.%c[default] \n 
			\n\n
			\n Zombies are people who have been attacked by a controller or exposed to a psi antenna. Physically - these are people, but completely lost their personality and ability to think. The only thing left is instincts and life habits. The destruction of a person depends on the strength and duration of the impact. It is not known whether they regenerate. There are reports that radiation and psi radiation are tolerated easily, so they can attack stalkers in those conditions in which stalkers can not normally fight. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Origin.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n There is no unequivocally proven version of the zombie-civilian origin, but there are several basic: \n 
			Degradation of zombified \n  
			Perhaps a zombie is a long-time zombie stalker who, after a long walk in the Zone, lost all his equipment and finally lost his identity. \n 
			Self-settelers \n 
			After the first explosion at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, some people refused to evacuate and remained on the contaminated land. This version says that zombies are people who lived in the exclusion zone, which fell under the second release. Among them are not only settlers, but also prisoners, on which experiments and laboratory personnel were put. Two facts speak in favor of this version. The first - in the RA emissions actually turn stalkers into zombies. While the first release was much stronger than all subsequent ones, the person who fell under it degraded even more. The second fact is that on some zombies you can see the scientific form, for example: on an ordinary civil zombie. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Lifestyle and behavior.%c[default]\n
			\n Plant life, are neutral until they seek food, but are always hungry. When people try to find food, they attack people and animals. The bodies of some of them are so decomposed that they can not be distinguished from an old corpse, and because of the zombie habit of lying motionless for hours, careless stalkers can accidentally step directly on still living and dangerous zombies. Zombies of the military and stalkers are dangerous while "fresh" and have retained weapons. Then they degrade and finally go down - they lose all things, tear their clothes ... Usual condition - aimless walking around the Zone, they sit, doze, moan, mutter fragments of phrases. They can ask for something or say (ask them to save them, withdraw them from the Zone), if they find a prey, the zombie starts to move slowly in its direction, ignoring any dangers on the way. The inhibition of all physical processes in their body leads to the fact that it is difficult to kill them (they fall like dead, after a while they get up and try to attack, they go after the abuser). 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_zombie_text2">
		<text>Often, they can have objects of everyday life, weapons, etc., but they do not know how to use them. They like to repeat the habits of people (apparently, they have conditioned reflexes). Zombies eat everything indiscriminately. You can also meet a civil-zombie.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Relationships with other mutants.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Mutants do not attack Zombies. This can be explained by the fact that zombie meat is too dirty for eating. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Attitude to people and advice to the stalker.%c[default]\n
			\n\n
			\n Absence of pain and slow metabolism make them very problematic opponents. The controller can "activate" zombies, forcing them to attack their enemies. Zombies are not very dangerous; especially when they are already old (ie they are in their condition for a long time). Quickly killed with a shot in the head. But still, if you shot at him and he fell, do not rush to approach him: he will rise and continue to attack. For a medium-equipped stalker in large quantities are dangerous because of the great vitality. The most suitable weapon for shooting a zombie is a shotgun loaded with grape shot. No matter whether it's a double-barreled gun or a pump-action shotgun, it's important to try to plant as many pellets in the zombie's head as possible. It is best to climb any surface above human growth (concrete tiles, cars, buildings). But only on ladders or with the help of jumps, , do not use anything what has steps, as zombies can get on them.\n
			\n\n
			%c[0,215,215,215]Traits.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] High Vitality.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Powerful punches.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,205, 92, 92] Almost noiseless movement.\n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Weakneses.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Head - a vulnerable place.
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] Very slow. 
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,107, 142, 35] At long distance from the enemy They are powerless.  \n
			\n\n
			\n%c[0,215,215,215]Subspecies.%c[default]\n
			\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]X%c[0,255, 222, 173] Civilian Zombie. \n
			\n\n
			%c[0,173, 216, 230]" The Brain Scorcher strips its victim of mind and reason, leaving only an empty, mindless shell. The brainless bodies then turn into zombies, following only the most basic instincts, wandering aimlessly around the Zone without weapons or clothing. Zombies are little more than sluggish walking corpses, caring only about food and sleep. They eat and drink just about anything they can get their claws on but the animation of them eating is not included, hence they are virtually soaked in radiation and toxic waste. Usually they roam the Zone without any apparent purpose, or just lie corpse-like in abandoned buildings. However, as soon as they sense the presence of a human being, they attack immediately. Experienced stalkers have learned to avoid them if they can. ".%c[0,215,215,215] Wiki.\n
		</text> 
	</string>


	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_historic">
		<text>Historic Mutants</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_historic_rat_wolf">
		<text>Rat wolf</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_historic_rat_wolf_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n \n
			\n%c[guide_blue] Rat wolf %c[default] he was a rare subspecies from mutated kind of rats.\n
			\nMuch more dangerous than the usual rats currently living in the Zone, the rat wolf was a merciless machine for killing.\n
			\nThese creatures often headed packs of ordinary rats and stood out sharply in their sizes.\n
			\n In addition to being about two to three times larger than an ordinary rat, there were only a few minor differences in their appearance - like large and completely black eyeballs.\n
			\n Natural selection ultimately played a role - because of their size, they were very prominent in the common pack and were easy prey for the cats of the Zone and other mutants.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]General information%c[default]
			\nX Health: Medium\nX Speed: Medium\nX Features: none
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_historic_tark">
		<text>Tark</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_historic_tark_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n \n
			\n%c[guide_blue]Tark%c[default]  - died-out mutated horse.\n
			\n This being only slightly reminds the ancestors because of radiation of the Zone.\n
			\n Tark has no tail, hind legs are atrophied, lobbies are strengthened\n
			\n This "pseudo-horse" has big dimensions: about 3 meters in withers. The neck after mutations became most of all similar to the big muscle connected to powerful muscles of a back. Flesh of a mutant isn't capable to regeneration. The animal is extremely aggressive and unpredictable. Often meets in herds to five individuals. It is rather a remnant of antecedents, than herd instinct.\n
			\n Tark eat all. Their madness blocks sensation of fear. They Are hostile to all beings of the Zone. Unlike other mutants in the Zone they were incredibly wild animals, their madness often suppressed their perception of fear and probably promoted possible falling of their generation.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]General information%c[default]
			\nX Health: Medium\nX Speed: High\nX Features: Agressive
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>