<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

    <string id="encyclopedia_characters">
		<text>Characters</text>
	</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Strelok">
			<text>Strelok</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Strelok_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nStrelok — One of the most experienced and capable stalker-Loner in the Zone. He has created own group with Fang, Ghost, Doctor and probably Guide. As the Marked One, he was the most famous stalker-pathfinder. Several times Marked made his own way in the depth of the Zone that eventually caused widespread cataclysms.\n
				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                    First campaign to the north.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Stalkers composes huge legends about Strelok and his Group, such as: At the beginning of August 2011, Strelok with his team penetrates to the center of Zone to the Chernobyl NPP.  After entering they found suspicious-looking closed door that was securely closed. Fang has told that he can make the decoder for this door, but he needs tools and time. In attempt to leave the CNPP the group was attacked by patrol of fanatics, and during heavy fighting the wounded Strelok has fainted . Fang and the Ghost find his body on an entrance to the half-ruined reactor and bypassing patrol, leave the CNPP together with their wounded companion through a shoulder. After that they carry the half-dead Strelok to the Doctor and  he will try to heal Strelok's serious wounds. After treatment, Strelok leaves the house of the Doctor and goes to the north where gets under emission. Eventually, destiny being well-disposed to the Strelok, by crawling he reaches the Doctor, and the Doctor saves his life once more.  Being recovered, Strelok considers a repeated campaign to the north but before it, preliminary visits group’s base where it learns that the Fang with the Ghost have decided to go to the CNPP without him and were ambushed in Army warehouses, and moreover the Fang has died, in the Ghost record it is said that in 100 meters from them, there was the mercenary with a scar on a face. Strelok makes a promise to revenge "the person with a scar".	
\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                    
Second campaign to the North. %c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Strelok gathered to the north again. In order to get to Chernobyl, and to pass an awful «brain Scorcher» he's heading to the Red forest. Making the way through Yantar, Strelok has elicited at scientists a prototype of protection against psi-radiation under the pretext of his testing and made the way through psi-installation on Yantar in the Red wood. Escaping from «Clear sky» group and the mysterious mercenary with a scar, Strelok undermines the only tunnel leading to the catacombs which lead to Pripyat.  Then he has reached the CNPP where he was overtaken by group of "Clear sky". The mercenary by means of an electromagnetic rifle has put a prototype of psi-protection of the Shooter out of action. The zone has categorically reacted to actions of people — having released the pulsing heavy-duty emission after which nothing was known of stalkers.
				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                   The Marked One, or the third campaign to the north %c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n  The truck of death has had an accident on a northern part of the Cordon. Anonymous stalker, while he was looking at any valuables, find the body of the survived stalker among dead corpses in the truck of death, and then brings him to Sidorovich. For a tattoo on his hand, Strelok gets the nickname Marked. He doesn't remember either the name, or the past. In his PDA there is only one record — "Kill the Strelok" then the third campaign of the Strelok to the center of the Zone and his subsequent final disappearance has begun... Though some stalkers say that  Strelok helped several years later the survived military in the East Pripyat.
				</text>
		</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Degtyarov">
			<text>Degtyarov</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Degtyarov_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n Degtyarev is the experienced stalker who long time was considered as a missing, but several years later has appeared also unexpectedly as well as has disappeared. Stalkers say that he has started own investigation and actively looked for the fallen helicopters and military. He has found a method to make the way to east Pripyat and went there with group of stalkers among whom there were a Zulu, Vano, the military and even the Monolithuanian. Degtyaryov perfectly knew Zone because before accident of 1986 he lived in Pripyat and he also liked to tell stalkers about his adolescence in the city that became the ghost town. Today it is unknown where is Degtyaryov, someone says that he has left the Zone together with military, and some consider that he has died in the hometown and at night it is possible to see his ghost which is peacefully walking on streets of Pripyat... \n
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Wram">
			<text>Scar</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Wram_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nOne of the most mysterious stalkers of the Zone. Some Stalkers says that he pursued the Strelok during his second campaign to the Chernobyl NPP. «Clear sky» members told that he was founded barely alive on swamps, and have been carried to the base, then he has joined their ranks. The last information about Scar, tells that he disappeared on a territory of Chernobyl NPP with other members of Clear Sky group during the heavy-duty emission. \n
				</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Klik">
			<text>Fang</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Klik_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nFang — he is a loner also a member of Strelok’s group. Fang is closest friend of Strelok and Ghost, nevertheless he is also a good technician. He had a little rough and rigid character. Fang was quite strange, self-contained person, moreover he had problems with mispronouncing 'r' and 'l'. Fang was engaged in assembly of the strange device which according to him had to help to get to the "center". The unknown mercenary and two stalkers make an ambush in Army warehouses near the "bloodsucker’s village" In which Fang and Ghost find themselves fallen into an ambush. In firefight Ghost and Fang kill two stalkers, but the unknown mercenary who was in hundred meters away manages to kill Fang. Ghost buries the friend on the suburb of the "bloodsucker’s village" \n
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Prizrak">
			<text>Ghost</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Prizrak_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nGhost —is a loner also a member of a well known Strelok’s group. In the group Ghost was the best strategist, also he is not bad technician, but nevertheless the Fang surpassed him in it. Ghost, Strelok and Fang managed to get on the CNPP thereby they deserved to be called Zone Legends. Ghost and Fang have decided to make the device for penetration to "center", and at the following raid, to use it. In attempt to leave the center of the Zone, stalkers were attacked by a patrol of Monolith group. Strelok was wounded, Fang has suggested Ghost to throw Strelok, but the Ghost didn't listen to him.  After that, Fang and Ghost managed to carry the Shooter on swamps to the Doctor. Ghost and Fang have begun to assemble mysterious devices. They have made two copies of that strange device from details which they could find. But in Army warehouses there was unforeseen — Fang has been killed by mercenaries. Ghost buries the friend on the suburb of the "bloodsucker’s village". And after Strelok has alone jerked on the CNPP and has disappeared, the Ghost was employed to scientists on Yantar, today it is unknown where he is...\n
				</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_fanatic">
			<text>Fanatic</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_fanatic_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nAn intense man full of purpose, his aggressive behavior has earned him well deserved authority over rookies. He has got the nickname for the devotion to the secret code of honor of stalkers and uncompromising fight against bandits. After Wolf leaves the Cordon for the heart of the Zone, Fanatic takes over leadership of the Rookie Village. \n
				\n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
				\nFollowing Wolf's temporary departure for the Army Warehouses, Fanatic took charge of the rookie village, looking after new arrivals on his own until his friend's return.\n
				\nDespite no longer being solely in charge he is still regarded as an authority, though he much prefers to be out fighting bandits and mutants than standing idly by.\n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Kartograf">
			<text>Cartographer</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Kartograf_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n He was just a simple man, named Cartographer.  Real names of legends, often recede into the background or just vanishes. He has been devoted to the favourite business which he has inherited from the father in due time, and that — from the grandfather. By the hand of fate he appeared to be in the zone. As well as all people, firstly he was afraid almost of everything, and, become accustumed, has continued to be engaged in what he was engaged at all time before — to make maps of local landscapes and better than any photography of any satellite, especially with maps of forests with secret paths, caves in which it is possible to overstay emission. His maps was very helpful. Last time he was seen, when he has gone to explore Pripyat, unfortunately, exactly at that time there were a lot of anomalies, perhaps, that is the reason of his disappearance. Someone says that he has died, others — that he has got under influence of Owners of the Zone and became one of them, rest — that he has collected several powerful artifacts and now he may not use just hidden tracks, but quickly pass territory where skilled stalkers waste a lot of time and forces, now the Cartographer can disappear from one place and appear in another. Of course, all of this more likely the myth or legend, appeared because of his excellent maps since then nobody saw him, and if someone saw then cannot tell anything concrete about him.. \n
				</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Voronin">
			<text>General Voronin</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Voronin_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nGeneral Voronin is the leader of the Duty faction. It is unknown under what conditions he became the head of the Duty, but some consider that he is a successor of the general Krylov who has disappeared under mysterious circumstances during war of groups. Stories tells us that Voronin has killed the legendary bloodsucker Stronglav, but whether it so actually? Zone legends cannot vanish so easily... \n
				</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Provodnik">
			<text>Guide</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Provodnik_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n Guide is credited of being the first Stalker ever, because he known the Zone as well as one’s own five fingers. Can carry out to any point of the Exclusion Zone, however he is not always agrees. He has helped the Strelok, having brought him to Doctor; perhaps, he was familiar with him and earlier. He is quite legendary in the Zone, And he won't go with just anybody, either. From what we can hear, he charges quite a bit. But if you find him and have enough cash, you can rest assured he’ll take you where you need to go. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                     " He is quite legendary in the Zone, And he won't go with just anybody, either. From what we can hear, he charges quite a bit. But if you find him and have enough cash, you can rest assured he’ll take you where you need to go. Guide is a Zone veteran, he knows her in all kinds of ways." %c[default]\n
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Noi">
			<text>Noah</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Noi_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n Noah hates mutants so much, he often clear caves on a tableland, which placed near arch anomaly «Circus». Most stalkers avoid contact with Noah, claiming he is insane and fires on people on sight, that happens because he confuses, and think that is mutants. Noah is a hermit who appears to suffer from memory lapse. Noah has a tamed pseudodog - he calls her Lessie.  He has tamed her as a puppy, and she began to serve him truly — she protects from "hordes of mutants" while he sleeps. He also claims a prophecy about a "wave" which will be in the form of a large emission and a subsequent horde of mutants who will kill everyone who isn't prepared for it, and the only save zone is «Ark». \n				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                     "Noah’s Mindconstruction ! There is an old Zaton’s feature – stalker with name Noah. Well experienced man, goal oriented and totally out of the mind. His white whale is to save all stalkers from a fast apocalypse, here he also tries to build an ark from the old barge… As for me, so it is a solo performance named as «Madhouse». If you want go there, make sure that you are not annoying Noah, he is out of his mind, but in general - quite harmless." %c[default]\n
				</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Borov">
			<text>Borov</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Borov_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nIn 2011 he worked as a barmen on bandit’s in Depo. He wants to be in head of group, but that position was occupied by Yoga. Borov hated him so much, there were enough reasons: Yoga was cruel, selfish, cunning and also greedy. He didn't appreciate his own people, and that’s why among bandits began to arise the discontent. Borov was one of such haters also. However dreams become true — Borov after all became the leader of group. What became with the previous kingpin — it is unknown.  Perhaps, Borov is also his murderer. After the Freedom group has left the Dark valley, the Borov together with the gang has founded new base in the territory of Old factory. The depot has been devastated, the Bar "Super Grub" — is destroyed, and bandits were beaten out by stalkers under Seriy’s command. Perhaps, Borov has also concluded a neutrality with "Freedom" as those have simply "presented" them a new shelter. With his arrival to the power internal "policy" at bandits became softer — now they didn't keep order as it was at Yoga, and have slid to the level of Renegades. \n
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Lesnik">
			<text>Forester</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Lesnik_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n Old Forester living in the Zone, he refused to be evacuated from her after accident on the CNPP. Lives in the building of the abandoned mine near the Red wood. According to him, he has supernatural ability to feel anomalies and pass them. He have helped the Scar and "Clear sky" to reach Limansk. With Scar’s help has released group of mercenaries from spatial anomaly. \n
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Semetsky">
			<text>Semeckiy</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Semetsky_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nImmortal stalker Yuriy Semeckiy, He have reached the WishGranter (according to one of versions — with not less legendary stalker by nickname Journalist) and  have wished immortality. As usual WishGranter deemed his wish in particular way– from this moment, Semeckiy has to die every day. Stalkers consider daily message about his death as a good sign. But some of them consider that constant notices of Semetsky's death are just the simple virus which has come into stalker’s PDA network. \n
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Tachenko">
			<text>Tachenko</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_Tachenko_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n Tachenko was one of the Military officers sent into the Zone, where after all terrible events and creatures, he decided to struggle against her by his own forces. During one of operations he has decided to turn off communication with the headquarters, by that giving the choice to soldiers of the group: to leave or remain with him and to battle against the Zone. The remained soldiers together with the commander have based one of the largest stalker’s group named as — "Debt". General Tachenko with the group of five people has been trapped in the spatial anomaly. Stalkers couldn't find a way out of her, long time being in a stalemate. At some point Major Chepurna has disappeared, Tachenko and the others hoped that he could find a way out, however he has died. After a little while the colonel Kosmach has gone crazy — he has shot the lieutenant Zakharchuk and the lieutenant Bunchuk then has blown out his own brains. Left alone, General Tachenko has made his agonal record on a PDA and both shot himself. \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_ivan_trodnik">
			<text>Ivan Trodnik </text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_ivan_trodnik_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Ivan Trodnik%c[default] – former guide, nowadays medic of "Clear sky".\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\nEarlier he was heading conductors of the group in raids on novel Swamps,  today Ivan spends days by patching wounded stalkers.\n
				\n After the accident which has comprehended the faction, He was forced to do such kind of work because he was the most experienced doctor from «Clear Sky» group.\n
				\n Now indulges in memories of former times, of the only joy of the life – researches, and accuses the mercenary Scar of all his troubles .\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Clear Sky»\n• Rank: «Veteran»\n• Reputaton: «Very good»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_xenotech">
			<text>Klin</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_xenotech_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Klin%c[default] - skillful mechanic, repairs generally equipment and weapon of the beginning stalkers.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]
				\n In the past he worked on the neutral’s base at the old farm located approximately halfway between the destroyed bridge on the Cordon and the Dump. Now he is sitting in the village of beginners on the Cordon, and helps beginners with repair of their equipment. \n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Loner»\n• Rank: «Professional»\n• Reputation: «Good»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_ashot">
			<text>Ashot</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_ashot_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Ashot%c[default] - Ashot is a cheerful and optimistic  Freedom faction's trader you can find him on «Yanov» station.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n According to his words, you can always buy newly made bullets, but they cost a little bit more than those that you can buy from other traders. \n
				\n Ashot with his friend Yar often act out with nothing suspecting stalkers. \n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Freedom»\n• Rank: «Expert »\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_axel">
			<text>Aydar</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_axel_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Aydar%c[default] – medic on «Skadovsk» (Zaton).\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data:%c[default]\n
				\nAydar – He is little bit closed person, it is rumored that he has come to the Zone to hide from the law.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Experienced»\n• Reputation: «Indifferent »
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_cardan">
			<text>Cardan</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_cardan_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Cardan%c[default] Experienced technician and also he loves alcoholic drinks.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n He has come Has come to the Zone together with two friends — the Joker and the Barge which have left him after the quarrel during one of boozes.\n
				\nCardan has based on the ship his own workshop on repair of weapon and equipment.\n
				\nCardan was a member of Project 62, a research project run in southwest Zaton, more specifically under the Iron Forest anomaly field. The project seemingly collapsed in 2004 due to Insufficient financing.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Expert »\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_barkeep">
			<text>Barkeep</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_barkeep_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Barkeep%c[default] - the owner of bar "100 X-ray" in Rostock.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\nDue to a location of Rostock in the center of the most brisk parts of the Zone, he is very important dealer. He is literally a lifebuoy for the stalkers who are coming back from sorties or just preparing in a campaign.\n
				\n Besides management of bar - leases numbers, supplies stalkers with equipment and work, pays awards.\n
				\nHe is respected by many stalkers as he was one of the initiators of opening a way to the center of the Zone\n
				\n It is not so much a position, how many a nickname. Besides obvious function of management of bar, giving of drinks and food, the Bartender hands over rooms, buys up loot, supplies stalkers with equipment, cartridges, weapon, medicines and work. Besides this, stalkers address him for obtaining the necessary information and search of workmates. Not the Saint and not the rascal, themselves knows his price that’s why he is held in respect among stalkers. It is rumored that hides in Zone from the shadowy past. After has got to anomaly, he began to limp and he have decided to replace occupation. He has arranged bar near Duty’s group base which imperceptibly became the main place of collecting veterans of the Zone. Barkeep has many communications both in the Zone, and in the outside world.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Legend»\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_beard">
			<text>Beard</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_beard_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Beard%c[default] - buyer of artifacts and the bartender on "Skadovsk".\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\nPossibly, the leader of local free stalkers on Zaton. He is one of the main figures near the center of the Zone.\n
				\n He is a Bartender of the"marsh ice breaker". He is quite good-natured for what stalkers often call him "Batka". Some say that he is one of the first stalkers of the Zone, and rumors are supported with big awareness of the Beard on everything on light. Beard has come to the Zone together with Grouse. He gets the main profit on sale of artifacts. For a very long time he kept balance between Stalkers and Bandits on Skadovsk for what a huge number of stalkers remained grateful to him.\n
				\nOffers various work to stalkers though, generally is interested in artifacts. He is always ready to help.\n
				\n His bar is one of the most brisk places in Zone and in popularity was almost made even to bar "100 X-ray".\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Expert »\n• Reputation: «Very good»
			</text>
		</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_cold">
			<text>Cold</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_cold_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Cold%c[default] has restored and has headed Clear sky group after it has nearly died.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n In the past he was a bartender on the basis of "Clear sky". Sociable person, likes to tell various stories. He has helped to reconstruct base and now heads Clear sky group.
				\n Though it is formal that he is a bartender, Cold one of the few in Zone who has risen on up, accepting reins of government Clear sky group when most of his key members either have died, or have run away.		
 				\n He is known among the companions as the cheerful and good-natured person and also the fan of trite jokes. Has come to the Zone because hasn't found the place in the outside world.			
	\n There are only a few doubts that he has made the correct decision, having restored the group to the former glory and now taking the important place of the power in the Zone. \n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Clear Sky»\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_doctor">
			<text>Doctor</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_doctor_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Doctor%c[default] is one of the few survived members of the group of the Strelok.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n According to a popular legend, the Doctor was one of the first stalkers who have reached the WishGranter, and wished to treat any living being in the Zone.\n
				\n His desire has been granted, and he has received a gift of healing, but has lost ability to see differences between people and mutants.\n
				\n Doctor refuses that information by saying that any of those who has reached the WishGranter, never came back live.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners» \n• Rank: «Legend»\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_gonta">
			<text>Gonta</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_gonta_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Gonta%c[default] –Is professional hunter.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n Gonta's group into which entered Garmata the Crab and Danila, has arrived to Zaton by the instructions of Trapper to destroy a chimera.\n
				\n But Danila hasn't returned from a trip to a den of bloodsuckers.\n
				\n Then the group has employed the stalker Soroka. Soroka has promised Gonta to help with hunting. But hunting wasn't successful: Soroka, having betrayed hunters, he has run away, Crab was wounded.\n
				\n By means of the mysterious stalker they have killed a chimera, have disclosed Danila's fate and have done justice to the traitor Soroke.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Veteran»\n• Reputation: «Good»
			</text>
		</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_hawaiian">
			<text>Hawaiian</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_hawaiian_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Hawaiian%c[default] - is a dealer and the bartender at the Yanov station.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n Hawaiian — is cheerful and positive person showing loyalty to "Freedom".\n
				\n Having caught sight of the stalker, usually shouts: "Alokh! ( hi!" in Hawaiian) what, probably, the reason why he received such a nickname.\n
				\n It is interesting that he at the same time is both a bartender, and the dealer.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Expert »\n• Reputation: «Very good»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_librarian">
			<text>Librarian</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_librarian_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\nLibrarian, despite his name, actually is a bartender of group of "Clear sky".
				\n After emission which cut off swamps from other part of the Zone the librarian has appeared in a trap without an exit.
				\n Having faced death by the bandits or something even worse, he has decided to go to southern areas and has joined "Clear sky" where he has replaced Cold by himself as the bartender after Cold became the leader of the group. \n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Clear Sky»\n• Rank: «Veteran»\n• Reputation: «Very good»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_lieutenant_kirilov">
			<text> Lieutenant Kirilov </text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_lieutenant_kirilov_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue] Lieutenant Kirilov %c[default] one of the most talented technicians of military forces.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n Originally he was just a radioman, Kirilov always had a dexterity easily to disassemble things and to collect them back.\n
				\n After a failure of the operation "Fairway" he and his group have found a shelter in an old laundry where he used his skills in disassembling and repairing of all equipment and weapons.\n
				\n After this, His colonel Kovalskiy recommended him to take role of the major technician on their base on the Agroprom. \n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\n•Group: «Military»\n• Rank: «Veteran»\n• Reputation: «Good»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_limpid">
			<text>Limpid</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_limpid_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Limpid %c[default] is the Bandits experienced  technician.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n Earlier he worked on a factory as a mechanical engineer, it is fair to tell that he understand technologies very well.\n
				\n However after he was discharged from the factory because of the drunk fight, he has fallen in alcoholism and soon has lost both the wife, and his house.\n
				\n When in his life there is nothing left, he has decided to go to the Zone to begin all over again, soon after the meeting with bandits in the Dump, he started to work as their technician.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\n•Group: «Bandits»\n• Rank: «Professional»\n• Reputation: «Good»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_loki">
			<text>Loki</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_loki_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Loki%c[default] - Loki is the leader of the Freedom detachment stationed in Yanov\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n He together with his group he break through " Brain Scorcher" to the center of the Zone.\n
				\n Unlike other leaders of group, has less jealous approach to ideology, once having even agreed to a ceasefire with "Debt".\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Freedom»\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Excellent»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_major_kuznetsov">
			<text> Major Kuznetsov </text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_major_kuznetsov_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue] Major Kuznetsov %c[default] is a corrupt and cruel millitary Officer.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n From the moment of arrival in the Zone several years ago Kuznetsov has risen from the period when he was a modest keeper of check-point to the skilled commander which frightens all his subordinates \n
				\n Despite the small official power in command and control, he has bribed and has receded highest authority, where only a few people are ready to resist to him.\n
				\n As a result he became the actual leader of armed forces in bigger parts of the Zone.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\n• Group: «Military»\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Neutral»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_nimble">
			<text>Nimble</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_nimble_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Nimble%c[default] - appears as a enterprising businessman and rare equipment dealer..\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]
				\n He has started his stalker career in quality of the member of "Clear sky", and then as the courier for Sidorovich, he has got the important contacts which have allowed him to construct own business.\n
				\n Nimble unlike other dealers, specializes in sale of rare equipment which is very difficult to find, he also doesn't foreknow what kind of goods will fall into his hands next time.\n
				\n Originally he traded on "Skadovsk", but after revival of Monolit group has got over on the Cordon, in the neighborhood of Sidorovich's bunker.\n
				\n He is a stalker with very interesting story. His name speaks for itself - he has managed to stay also the green beginner whom Marked pulled out from captivity, and the member of Clear Sky group, and person for whom it is possible to order extremely exotic bagatelles. Some say that he takes orders to this day. Earlier he actively cooperated with the dealer from the Cordon, yes, with Sidorovich, and stood well with him. What relations at them at the moment it is hard to say, Nimble became one of most popular "dealers".\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Legend»\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
				</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_novikov">
			<text>Novikov</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_novikov_text">
			<text>\n%c[0, 143, 188, 143]Information:%c[default] \n \n
				\n%c[guide_blue]Novikov%c[default] - talented technician. Also he is known as Grey – one of the oldest members of «Clear Sky» group.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information%c[default]\n
				\n He is a member of group from the very first days. Novikov is characterized by the companions as true Master of his duty. Cold claims that he is able to do weapon and ammunition of air.\n
				\n After crash of group for a short time he worked under the contract in mobile scientific laboratory on Jupiter, later, after receiving news of revival of "Clear sky", has gone back to Swamps.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Clear Sky»\n• Rank: «Veteran»\n• Reputation: «Excellent»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_olivius">
			<text>Olivius</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_olivius_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Olivius%c[default] – guarding loot and other stolen goods  for bandits.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n After Borov’s ( the former leader of bandits ) death Olivius used some kind a chaos of reformation to quickly increase his influence in the Dark valley.\n
				\nThough some stalkers consider that bandits have a leader now, there is only a small share of information, contracts or tradings with participation of bandit’s faction in which Olivius hasn't laid his hands.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Bandits»\n• Rank: «Veteran»\n• Reputation: «Excellent»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_owl">
			<text>Owl</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_owl_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Owl%c[default] – is trader on «Skadovsk».\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\nUnfriendly and rough person. From all inhabitants of the vessel he is distinguished with nasty character and quarrelsome temper.\n
				\n Has the widest range of weapons and ammunition and also very much highly appreciates information.\n
				\n He has good relations with Sultan and tense relations with the Beard. Perhaps, earlier he was a bandit (what tells his raincoat about).\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Expert »\n• Reputation: «Bad»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_professor_kruglov">
			<text>Professor Kruglov</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_professor_kruglov_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue] Professor Kruglov %c[default]  is a doctor of biological sciences.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n Before arriving into the Zone, Kruglov has studied pathogenic mutations at animals and their effects therefore it was only the matter of time until his research has given him here.\n
				\n Within the last several years he worked with the colleague professor Sakharov, and claims that he has made several large discoveries - though the few stalkers really know what he speaks about, and usually just feign understanding.\n
				\n Recently he has begun to conduct own research laboratory in a hangar near the main bunker in Amber where he offers various technical work as that who visited him.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Scientists»\n• Rank: «Experienced»\n• Reputation:«Neutral»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_professor_sakharov">
			<text>Professor Sakharov</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_professor_sakharov_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue] Professor Sakharov %c[default] He is one of the most skilled researchers of the Zone.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\nAs the chief researcher of mobile scientific laboratory of Amber, professor Sakharov has shared with the majority of scientific achievements which have arisen from the Zone.\n
				\n In spite of the fact that he is considered polite and Professional, his only true care consists in the discoveries which are seldom appearing for reflections for the researchers, sending them to certain death.\n
				\n Because of the nature of his work at him almost boundless stock of contracts for production of artifacts and parts of mutants that makes him very popular employer among reckless stalkers.\n
				\n He is veteran of researches of the Zone. He participated in the first expeditions of 2007. In general, professor Sakharov is mercantile and actually he is interested only discoveries for the sake of which he won't regret to send people to a certain death. When performing his tasks many people have died. However the majority of his researches after all have brought benefit, for example a hoop for Psi-kupol helmets which several times pulled out stalkers from paws of controllers.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Scientists»\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Excellent»
				</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_sergeant_spooner">
			<text>Sergeant Spooner</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_sergeant_spooner_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue] Sergeant Spooner %c[default] is Experienced soldier and cunning dealer.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n Throughout the most part of his life, Information always played an important factor in acceptance of his decisions, always carefully selects with whom and what he can trade.\n
				\n Naturally, he has found the place after the accession to army where his skills are of great value, and now uses the situation as the front for the personal business of trade and information.\n
				\n About him very few information, and least of all is known of why he has such peculiar nickname.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\n• Group: Military\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Excellent»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_sidorovich">
			<text>Sidorovich</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_sidorovich_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Sidorovich %c[default] he trades in his old bunker near the village of beginners.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n Has reputation of quite honest businessman who gives to newcomers the chance to survive. Extensive communications allow him to import on the territory of the Zone even luxury goods.\n
				\n However many consider him greedy and hard-fisted. Those who try to compete with him in his own territory or just had misfortune to anger him, often become targets of hitmen.\n
				\n Good he either Bad, he continues to play an important role in Zone economy and in life of his group as is an excellent source of work for those who want to grow rich quickly.\n
				\n Well-fed, low (to be exact small) bald man. Major customers are the stalkers beginners who have recently come to the Zone. Has a set of communications, He founded an agreement with a military post. He Is at the same time both an authority, and an object of humour of stalkers: on the one hand, quite honest business and the fact that he gives to many beginners chance to survive in the Zone, and on the other hand — he is greedy, selfish, and is mercantile. His nickname is chosen not casually: the surname Sidorov is rather widespread and can be used by the dealer for a nickname, confusing, a middle name it or a surname.\n
				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                     Years 2008—2010.%c[default]\n
				\n For the first time he has got over in the Zone in 2008 when there was only a need in buying up and dealers, than the authority of people around as the pioneer has deserved. After a while he has expanded the range of goods, having begun to trade in weapon with local stalkers. He took the written-off weapon from military, in particular from the major Kuznetsov with whom he had strong links.
				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                     Year 2011.%c[default]\n
				\n In 2011 he has begun to year active cooperation with stalkers because of what the number of sales and the general commodity turnover has grown, the quantity of the bought artifacts has increased that has also positively affected trade. Same year Sidorovich has helped stalkers with fight against military, in particular Valeryana, in his problem with Haletsky — having provided them the mercenary Shram who has helped with destruction of forces of the opponent on the Elevator and ATP. In exchange Sidorovich has received extraordinary important for further trade loot, brought to him from the center of the Zone.
				\n\n
				%c[0, 215, 215, 215]                                                     Year 2012.%c[default]\n
				\n In 2012 there has come crisis, the quantity of goods and the price of them have fallen, dealers bought up everything. Once in the bunker to Sidorovich straight from the Truck of death the seriously injured stalker who has appeared subsequently as Strelok. He was nicknamed — "Marked" (because of a strange tattoo). Marked has performed several tasks for the dealer, having fulfilled a debt for the rescue. The same year he has taken control of the classified information from a post of military, having received very necessary information for the customer.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Loners» (Trader)\n• Rank: «Legend»\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_blackbird">
			<text>Blackbird</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_blackbird_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Blackbird %c[default]is trader from «Clear Sky» faction and also Nimble’s friend.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n As well as many stalkers before him, Blackbird has come to the Zone in search of wealth and has adjusted quite good supply channels of goods and information.\n
				\n Soon he has met Nimble and both have understood benefit of combination of the efforts at once.\n
				\n Using old contacts Nimble, Blackbird became the dealer of "Clear sky" that has allowed them to provide illicit routes through Swamps and to become quickly the prospering businessmen.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Clear Sky»\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Excellent»
			</text>
		</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_sultan">
			<text>Sultan </text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_sultan_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Sultan %c[default] is the former leader of bandits in Zaton.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n Considering his his title of "kingpin", many in the Zone consider Sultan the person who very much appreciates himself.\n
				\n His life was full of troubles; after the death of the close friend because of abuse of psychoactive substances the Sultan has killed responsible dealers and later has been imprisoned\n
				\n After his release he has again appeared in prison because of his "business" soon enough, eventually has gone to a zone where he has joined bandits, has climbed a career ladder among thieves and has begun to operate the gang.\n
				\n Finally all his attempts to be approved as the leader in group, his enterprises and transactions in Zaton have been broken and demolished by singles from the Beard’s group.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Bandits»\n• Rank: «Master»\n• Reputation: «Terrible»
			</text>
		</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_wolf">
			<text>Wolf</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_wolf_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Wolf %c[default] – informal head of the beginners village.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]\n
				\n He regards his task as a protection of the village and stalkers beginners who live there from  external threats, the Wolf constantly watches situation on the Cordon.\n
				\n Communicating with Sidorovich, he often employs groups for elimination of bandits, mutants and other threats for the security of the village.\n
				\nIn the past the leader of the camp of beginners on the Cordon. The old stalker who has retired and having put on the place the stalker by the name of the Fanatic.\n
				\n\n%c[0, 215, 215, 215]" I worked at the mine, so it was closed as unprofitable. Money — zero, prospects none. And here rumors have gone that in the Zone it is possible to grow rich fantastically. I had some experience behind shoulders, that’s why I have decided to risk. I can't tell that has grown rich, however a money was really got. Yes it is history the most usual, many have so appeared here... To me here "flesh" on a leg has bitten off a finger, hair from radiation have begun to pour, "Frying" right has put a leg... lousy thing — "Frying". And that time face to face has faced the bloodsucker — though don't remember... Generally, it is possible to speak as much as you can,  but only when you will be influenced by this business  somehow — you will understand something " %c[default]\n
				\n He Considered himself as the defender of the village and stalkers who live there, from threats from the outside. The wolf uses network of intelligence agents and spies to monitor the unfriendly movements which happen in the Cordon.
				\n Divides information which he finds with Sidorovich, they often send road groups and luckies to clean encroaching strength of bandits, mutants and other threats. Both are interested in safety of the village.
				\n Also he worked for group of dissenters of "Debt". After loss of military documents on "Agricultural industry" the Wolf began to act, he has left the village of beginners towards Army warehouses, and his position was held by the Fanatic. Having brought dynamite to "Debt", I remained in Army warehouses.  \n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]\n
				\nGroup: «Loners»\n• Rank: «Legend»\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_yar">
			<text>Yar</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_characters_yar_text">
			<text>
				%c[guide_blue]Yar%c[default] – stalker with a lot of different talents.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
				\n He is the most skilled technician of Freedom group.\n
				\n he Has visited Pripyat on the basis of loners and has even undertaken duties of the technician and the doctor there.\n
				\n Upon return on "Yanov" he was engaged in information tradind.\n
				\n%c[guide_green]Data%c[default]
				\nGroup: «Freedom»\n• Rank: «Expert »\n• Reputation: «Impressive»
			</text>
		</string>
</string_table>
