<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies">
		<text>Anomalies</text>
	</string>

		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies">
			<text>Archianomalias</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_jelezoles">
			<text>Iron Wood</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_jelezoles_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Iron Forest - Archianomaly, is a large accumulation of anomalies "electra". In the south-west of Zaton there is an old electrical substation. In this place, electricity "came out" of wires and transformers, forming a large field of anomalies "electra". The name of the dangerous substation was apparently due to the numerous metal supports of the power transmission lines in the territory. In some places of this archeanomaly there is an increased radiation background. \n
			</text>
		</string>	

		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_sosnodub">
			<text>Pineoak</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_sosnodub_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Pineoak - an unusual archeanomalya, a cluster of sodas under a tree "dome". A fairly new type of symbiotic anomaly, formed as a result of the "fusing" of some species of trees, usually oak and pine. It is well distinguished from afar by the unusual shape of the "dome" from tree trunks, which in themselves are harmless, in contrast to the accumulating hazardous chemicals under it, often concentrating in the anomaly "Soda". Getting under a dome of anomaly, any organic "burns out", as if covered with organic acid. There is a version that an anomaly, like a predator, dissolving organic matter, feeds itself. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «This is the same thing that has grown between the hills above the sodas. Everyone here calls her so: some wise man has determined that the bark on that tree is partly pine, and partly - oak. If you want to find an artifact there, you need a good protection from chemistry ... Well, take more ammunition, there are often dogs on the hills.».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_betonvanna">
			<text>Concrete bath</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_betonvanna_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n It is a cluster of anomalies "soda", located in a "concrete bath", apparently, served as the basis for the foundation of some extension to the plant "Jupiter", and not built. At the elevation in the center of the anomaly periodically appear artifacts of chemical nature, which can be picked up without even getting into the poisonous waters of a concrete bath. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «If you looking for artifacts, it is better to use acidic ones. And the best place to look for them is the Concrete Bath. There are few competitors there: the place is disliked because of the fact that near the shop of "Jupiter".%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_simbiont">
			<text>Symbiote</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_simbiont_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n This archyanomaly represents the further evolution of " Grasping hands" The main damaging factor is a strong psy-impact against the background of high temperatures and the highest gravitational pressure. The scale of the anomalous zone is striking: the average radius of influence varies from 20 to 30 meters. The anomaly is clearly visible at any time of the day in the wavy air curvature, rising high into the sky. It is in a single copy in the Red Forest. Near the anomaly is a scattering of stones, which stalkers call "Devil's Parking". \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_loza">
			<text>Withe</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_loza_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n "Withe" - a bizarre archeanomalia, reminiscent of a vine, sagged between houses in Pripyat. This archeanomalia is dangerous for the anomalies "Soda" on the ground and in the pit (where, presumably, the roots of the vine are located), and on branches - flying from above "Chemical comet". A significant relief for the stalker who decided to conquer Withe is that the Acid Comet is in constant motion and moves along the branches of Withe. As a result, you can trace the frequency with which the "Comet" passes this or that segment of the path. At night, "Withe" makes an indelible impression on all observers. A large plant, most like an overgrown vine or a vine. Under the plant on the ground in abundant numbers are located "Soda". On the trunk from the wall to the wall flies "Chemical Comet". \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «Little is known about these places, basically, what Garik told. He says there is a place where from the acid anomaly the hefty grapes grew, the size of a ten-story house. Maybe he does it, but if not, then I would check this grape for artifacts».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_rubec">
			<text>Scar</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_rubec_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n This anomaly is on Zaton. In the very anomaly you can get some good artifacts, which are often found at the base of the Rubts. Go through artifacts possible, but difficult. In addition to the directed psi effect, static "electros" are located at a certain height. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «The place where the earth was cut with a knife ... There were artifacts, but with something that climbs there, something strange happens. This thing on the brain gives with such force that there is not something to get out - on inhale-exhale brains are not enough».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_plavni">
			<text>Flipper</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_plavni_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n A small bog, located behind the cement plant. In the swamp there are a lot of "sodas" emitting corrosive chemical vapors, so without good chemical protection, one should not go there. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «The small bay behind the cement factory. At this point the bay turned into an eerie smelly swamp, there is plenty of soda in the water. Although, what kind of water is already almost continuous acid. Artifacts were found there, but they say that this place is very like monsters».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_zagrruki">
			<text>Grasping hands</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_zagrruki_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n A creepy formation that arose under the action of a high gravitational field. As a result of this influence, the silicate rocks contained in the soil are stretched along the flow of gravitational waves and fused, forming curved brown hooks. Inside, the grasping hands abound with "fries", but may contain other anomalies. For example, in the center of zagrebushchih hands in the red forest there is a depression with a "carousel", and the "hands" themselves are covered by a psi-field. \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_kogot">
			<text>Claw</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_kogot_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n The claw is a cluster of gravitational anomalies, under the influence of which the earth arched into a bizarre formation, something resembling a claw. Under the "dome" of the anomaly is quite a lot of "Tramplins" and "Funnels", there is "Carousel", as well as a fairly high level of radiation. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «This anomaly is full of gravitational artifacts. This place is not difficult to notice, there the anomalies heavily damaged the earth, part of the hill just demolished. And in the caves that opened in the hill, immediately the sniffs settled, but they rarely come out. And, even if they do, then no further anomalies».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_vulkan">
			<text>Vulcan</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_vulkan_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n The volcano is an archeanomaly located in the courtyard of abandoned apartment houses near the deli (Pripyat). Outwardly, the anomaly is a bit like the "Circus". A significant difference is that instead of excavation there is a small "dent" in the ground, emitting the "Comets". In addition, instead of poltergeists around the anomaly grazers and pseudo dogs graze, hoping to get a roasted meat. \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_cirk">
			<text>Circus</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_cirk_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n The circus is an archeanomaly, which is a circle about seventy meters in diameter, along which two "comets" swirl. "Circus" - an interesting anomaly, located on the Creek. As a result of unknown processes in the ground, there was a kind of deepening, in the center of which were "frying". At an altitude of about ten meters there is a "carousel". Its name, apparently, was due to the similarity with the arena of the circus. Inside, two moving fire anomalies circulate, which can cause significant damage. But also the hare can be found excellent: in the anomaly "Mamina beads", "Fireball" and even sometimes "Eye" or "Flame" are formed. Seldom comes the "Crystal". It is worth noting that some believe that mobile fire anomalies are somewhat similar to a poltergeist. \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_pepeliwe">
			<text>Ashes</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_pepeliwe_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n The ashes are archeanomalia, located to the north-west of the "Yanov" station. The accumulation of fries in the old cemetery. The place is quite dangerous, but there are valuable artifacts. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «The ashes are an old cemetery near the Cops. It's very dangerous there, a lot of "Heat", sometimes zombies come. Usually this place is bypassed by the tenth road, but sometimes artifacts are found there».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_bitum">
			<text>Bitumen</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_bitum_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Bitumen is an archianomaly located not far from the Jupiter plant. It is a collection of "fries" and "carousels." Not far from the plant, Jupiter formed a break in the earth, possibly under the influence of gravity anomalies. Because of the "fry" formed in the break, the road to the sides of the anomaly "swam". \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «Not far from the plant" Jupiter "road failed. This place was nicknamed "Bitumen", because there the road surface floated. In the breach is full of anomalies - frying mixed with gravity ... And since the anomalies of the two species, it means that the artifacts must be different. Even the Goldfish».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_anomrowa">
			<text>Abnormal grove</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_anomrowa_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Abnormal grove - a small grove, entirely covered with acid mist and "soda". A small grove in the vicinity of the "Jupiter" under the influence of chemical anomalies turned into anomalous. Trees and other plants underwent strong mutations. In the grove were noticed soda and acid fog. \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_kotel">
			<text>Cauldron</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_kotel_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n A cauldron is a collection of fries formed in a lowland filled with water. A kind of anomaly "Rift", formed in a marshy area. In cracks up to several meters in depth and in deeper layers of moist soil, the accumulated water warms up to high temperatures, periodically bursting out under high pressure to the outside with jets of steam, which is why it received such a name. This anomaly can be seen from afar, however, like all the others. It looks as if someone has blasted a hill from within and filled it with a swampy mace. \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,173, 216, 230]                                                     «On cool days around the anomaly, heat is retained, which attracts not only mutants, but also stalkers. Courageous and stalwart stalkers seeing the artifact manage to take healing hot "baths"».%c[default]\n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_razlom">
			<text>Split</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_razlom_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n The fault is a fiery anomaly, most reminiscent of a fault in a frozen volcanic lava. The heat emanating from the fault in the earth quickly turns into a flaming torch as soon as an alien body enters the anomaly. It is rare. At what impacts appears - is unknown. \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_mirazstreet">
			<text>Mirage Street</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_mirazstreet_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n Soon after the stabilization of the Zone (presumably 2007-2008), a squad of singles was sent there to study this area, which remained on the map as a "white spot," but they did not return. Later, the situation decided to evaluate the stalker, nicknamed Shurup. He disappeared, but before that came from him a message with a single word: "Mirage!". Later, a detachment of debt was sent to the sector. As they approached, they noticed a pseudo giant walking along an ideal straight line, who later did not understand why he committed suicide in a cruel way. A few seconds later, three of the four stalkers "Duty" also went straight and committed suicide, hitting the Impact of the rare anomaly "Mirage". One - with overclocking broke his head against the wall, the second - cut both veins with glass, the third - climbed on the pole and hanged himself on the wires. The commander of the detachment was lucky: he did not see the "mirage" and switched on the CCP video recording mode shortly before the tragedy unfolded. At the base, he returned gray, muttering something about the demons. In his hands was a PDA, still working in video recording mode. \n
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_anomkorr">
			<text>Abnormal corridor</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_arhianomalies_anomkorr_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information: \n
				\n\n
				%c[0,215,215,215]                                                      Description.%c[default]\n
				\n\n
				\n It is an unremarkable corridor, which in fact is one of the most horrifying things in the Zone. Being in a sleeping mode is harmless, does not react to smooth touches, but as soon as a person makes sharp movements, the chance of triggering is great. A bullet or a grenade that exploded in the corridor activates the anomaly 100%. After activation, the corridor collapses to a very small gap, just crushing everything that is inside at that moment. After the convulsion, there is a process of calm, after which the walls continue to tremble a little, and a corrosive substance leaks out of them - mucus, which looks like a gastric juice. Time passes and mucus returns to its place, leaving only inorganic substances. \n
			</text>
		</string>	

		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_elektra">
			<text>Electro</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_elektra_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,70, 130, 180]Electro%c[default] - An anomalous formation, roughly 10 meters in diameter, accumulating large quantities of static electricity. When triggered, the anomaly bursts into a storm of arcing electricity nearly always lethal to all living beings. Easily recognizable by the blue gas it emits, along with the endless arcing of small bolts of electricity in the vicinity, the Electro holds no distinction for what crosses its event horizon, be it a human, a mutants or an inanimate object, and discharges as soon as anything gets too close.
				\nThe Electro is always in clusters and often located in tightly confined spaces, although clusters out in the open with a spacing of one meter or more between neighboring Electros have also been recorded. They are easily avoided when outdoors, and at their most dangerous in confined areas.\n
			</text>
		</string>	
			
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_prostpuz">
			<text>Spatial bubble</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_prostpuz_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Spatial Displacements.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Cordon, Red Forest, Surroundings of Jupiter, Limansk.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,255, 218, 185]Compass.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,106, 90, 205]Spatial bubble%c[default] - a rare anomalous formation, has the property of instantaneously transferring matter from one point of space to another. \n
				Well-marked spherical translucent formation. Without going into the details of Einstein's theory of relativity, this anomaly can be called a "hole in space". Stalkers calls it \n%c[0,106, 90, 205]Spatial bubble%c[default], probably because of the appearance and action. \n
				Any object or part of it, falling into the area of the anomaly (the entry point), instantly "falls out" from the back (exit point), but only where this side turns out, no one knows. Perhaps you will jump forward with your feet straight in %c[0,160, 82, 45]Meat grinder%c[default]. The precise mechanism of the action of this Zone phenomenon has not been studied, which is connected with the rare appearance of this anomaly and its certain unpredictability in relation to experimenters, is also unknown. There are cases of clumping such anomalies into one, in the place of their mass appearance. Having fallen into such a twist of space, people can wander for a long time on the space limited by these anomalies, repeatedly teleporting to its center. Sometimes in such anomalous places can find the unique artifact %c[0,169, 169, 169]Compass%c[default]. Its name speaks for itself - it is able to find a loophole and show "paths" in space. With its help you can find the point of entry or exit from the spatial anomaly. \n	
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,173, 216, 230]"Attention. We are stuck in an anomaly....can't get out......it's like space is warped......which ever way we go...can't move...equipment has gone off the rails....can see the outline of a town on the horizon...our coordinates...51...10..3..1..2....Is anybody out there...?"%c[0,215,215,215] Unknown.%c[default] \n	
			</text>
		</string>	
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psi">
			<text>Psi-field</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psi_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]There is a bad state of health on the rise. Strong negative Impact on the human psyche.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Invisible, but tangible Impact on the brain.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]In many places. More often at the edges of power lines.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n Terrain with high %c[0,255, 218, 185]Psi-Impact%c[default]. Similar "brain" lawns and glades are often formed near the towers of power transmission lines and other metal structures that play the role of antennas in the transmission of psi waves by Caymanov installations. In such places, hallucinations, loss of movement coordination, severe headaches and various mental disorders are not uncommon. With prolonged exposure to Psi-radiation, the human brain either disintegrates completely, or undergoes irreversible changes, transforming its carrier into a zombified one. One of the biggest zones of psi-radiation is the "Burnout of the Brains". When hit by Psi-radiation, voices and whispers are heard, it is difficult to concentrate on shooting. \n
				\n In the Zone, there is a specific effect on the human psyche and the brain as a whole, called psi-radiation. This Impact is extremely negative. Being under intense psi-radiation, a person can get serious brain damage, which leads to insanity at best or to destruction of the person and zombie at worst. A zombie is a human shell that preserves only some of the simplest reflexes, but completely lost memory (except for separate fragments), the ability to think and does not have a sense of self-awareness. \n
				%c[0,255, 218, 185]Psi-radiation%c[default] can be divided into two types according to the appearance pattern. The first is the man-made psi-fields with the help of special installations. It was this psi-field that was generated by radiators on Radar and at the Yantar plant, which prevented the penetration of stalkers to the center of the Zone. It is worth noting that the Psi-radiation on the Radar forced the stalkers to see hallucinations in the form of Phantoms - translucent mutants. The second type is created by the Zone. Small psi-foci are often found near power poles, as well as in archeanomalies (for example, "Scar"). \n
				In addition, the Controllers are able to generate directed Psi-radiation and create dangerous psy-fields around themselves. \n
				Scientists at Yantar has developed a special device that reduces the Impact of psi-radiation.\n	
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,173, 216, 230]"Mitka is said he have completely gone mad after he returned from Amber Lake. Is it possible for the controller to get Impact? - No, he would not have let him go so simply. There's something else..."%c[0,215,215,215] Unknown stalker.%c[default] \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_teleport">
			<text>Teleport</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_teleport_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Teleports an object.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,205, 92, 92]DATA LOST%c[default] 
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,106, 90, 205]Teleport%c[default] is a kind of white elongated spiral, which is in constant motion. If an object falls into it, the teleporter transfers it to a certain point. \n%c[0,106, 90, 205]Teleports%c[default] are in many places where without their help it is impossible to safely move further, for example, on the destroyed sections of bridges over the fountain soil near the Chernobyl NPP. \n
				Most likely, some \n%c[0,106, 90, 205]Teleports%c[default] since they can often appear for a short time directly ERROR It is possible to notice the periodic attempts of the fighters of the group to break through the barrier organized by the stalkers. One would assume that the creation of teleports is possible only near large power sources near the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, but this does not explain ERROR(to the periphery of the Zone. \n	            			
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_tesla">
			<text>Tesla</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_tesla_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Electric discharge.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Electric.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Closed spaces with high anomalous activity.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n %c[0,70, 130, 180]Tesla%c[default] - mobile anomaly of electrical nature. In fact, it is %c[0,70,130,180]Electra%c[default], which can fly quickly on a chaotic trajectory. Occurs mostly in confined spaces with high anomalous activity. Artifacts are not produced, by its nature is a provocateur electro-magnetic pulses, because of which the devices begin to fail to work, or at all turn off, but also there is a theory that the anomalies evolve, and it is the evolution of %c[0,70,130,180]Electra%c[default]. It is possible that these anomalies are responsible for the frequent crashes of military helicopters in the Exclusion Zone. \n
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,173, 216, 230]"I personally watched only "Comet" and "Tesla." The first is a fireball about a meter in diameter. The heat from it is felt and at a greater distance, I can assure. The second is what can be described with the words "ball lightning". Of course, the ball, and, of course, the electrical nature ... Both anomalies are actively moving, but as a rule - along closed trajectories. An attentive stalker can easily pass by them. The main thing - do not be distracted."%c[0,215,215,215] Pilot.%c[default] \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_tramp">
			<text>Springboard</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_tramp_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Deals a strong gravitational blow, when hit in the epicenter, throws the object out of itself with great force.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]"External" gravity.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Everywhere.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,160, 82, 45]Medusa, Stone Flower and Night Star.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n The Springboard anomaly is very common and can be found almost anywhere in the Zone, both outside and in buildings. To the naked eye, the anomaly appears as a rippling heat haze or air fluctuation accompanied by dancing leaves and sometimes crimson-colored stains on the ground. Throwing a bolt into a Springboard causes it to send out its distinctive shockwave, making it easily identifiable. It is also one of the anomalies that are harmless to pass through for a split moment after having been triggered, making bolts very useful tools for navigating a Springboard field. As players approach a Springboard their vision becomes gradually but markedly brighter as they get closer to the anomaly itself.
				\nSpringboards are easily identifiable, and easily avoidable but varying locations and odd spawn points in the games can make them a nuisance in a firefight. Players have often died in the middle of a fight, forgetting or not noticing the anomaly's presence with all the distractions, then walking straight into it. Just like all anomalies, its best to scout the location and find a way around it. \n	
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,173, 216, 230]"It was one of the first types of anomalies ever recorded. A Springboard is an unstable gravitational field limited to a pocket on ground level, about 1-2 meters wide. Reacts to the presence of creatures or objects by sending out a powerful shockwave that damages anything within radius. The damage caused by this changes throughout the anomaly's lifetime, ranging from minor bruises through serious wounds to instant death."%c[0,215,215,215] Encyclopedia.%c[default] \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_lift">
			<text>Ëèôò</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_lift_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Deals a strong gravitational blow, when hit in the epicenter, throws the object out of itself with great force.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]"External" gravity.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Everywhere.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,160, 82, 45]Pelicle.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\One of the first recorded anomalies. Causes impact damage by a variable gravitational field. Stays in one place for an average of a week, varying its impact strength during its "life". The result of an encounter with %c[0,160,82,45]Trumpin%c[default] can vary from minor bruises and contusions to instant death. During daylight hours, it is fairly easy to spot by distortions in the air above it, swirling foliage, and distinctive red-brown spots on the ground. Detected by any kind of detector, as well as by objects planted in it (bolts). \n
				\n Lift%c[default] is a gravitational anomaly, within which the Earth's gravity weakens. Gradually drifting in it for a few seconds, you can get out of it. Completely invisible. Also draws in corpses. Invisible to the human eye. Often you can only get into the anomaly from the acceleration, otherwise it will be "pushed" back out of the anomaly. At low acceleration on the way out of the anomaly it can "pull" back in. \n
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,173, 216, 230]"This anomaly was one of the first to be discovered back in 2008 on the field of the stadium in Pripyat. Since then, it has become increasingly common in various places in the Zone. An experienced eye can easily detect the anomaly by the fluctuations in the air, distorting objects, leaves swirling around, and traces of unfortunates caught in the epicenter. The elevator does not react to small objects, it does not discharge like other gravitational anomalies."%c[0,215,215,215] Encyclopedia.%c[default] \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_komet">
			<text>Comet</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_komet_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Make a strong gravitational impact, when it hits the epicenter, it throws the object out of itself with great force.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]«External» gravity.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Everywhere.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,160, 82, 45]Medusa, Stone Flower and Night Star.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n The Comet anomaly functions much like a Burner anomaly in that it deals fire damage on close contact, but with a key difference in that the Comet is mobile, hovering around within a certain area at a rapid pace.
				\n The Comet anomaly, unlike the Burner, is extremely powerful: it can kill even a well-armoured stalker if he gets hit directly.\n	           		
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_karusel">
			<text>Whirligig</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_karusel_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Tear apart all the living things that get inside.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Gravity.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Everywhere.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,160, 82, 45]Blood of stone, Slice of meat, Goldfish, Stone flower and Soul.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\nA common and dangerous anomaly, which snatches its victims up in the air and spins them at a breakneck speed. The exact nature of the Whirligig remains unknown. The anomaly can be recognized by a light whirlwind of dust above and by body fragments scattered in the vicinity. Victims caught on its outer rim, far enough from the maximum effect zone at the center, can escape the Whirligig with relatively minor injuries. As the stalker Cayman said: " These artifacts are formed from those %c[0,160, 82, 45]Carousel%c[default]. Toss, twist, rip on %c[default] Slice the meat %c[default], sucks  %c[default] Blood of stone %c[default] and shake out your %c[default]Soul%c[default]".\n	
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_fuzz">
			<text>Burning Fuzz</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_fuzz_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]With the rapid approach of any body emits a cloud of particles, which in case of contact with open or weakly protected skin seriously injure the last.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Acid.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Everywhere.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n This anomaly is usually found outdoors. It resembles moss or vines, hanging down like curtains from its growing spot. Reacts to rapidly approaching living beings by discharging a cloud of projectiles severely injuring uncovered or lightly protected skin upon contact. Does not react to slowly moving targets. Burnt Fuzz is generally considered the least dangerous anomaly in the Zone since it can be easily spotted and avoided. Even so, players rarely seem to take damage when coming into contact with the anomaly. Touching a Burnt Fuzz curtain seems to elicit a reaction from the anomaly, but only players with little or no armor have reported being hurt by it.
				\n The first example in the Zone of anomalous or mutated plant life, its organic origins may be they key to understanding why it isnt affected by things like other anomalies, or doesnt normally respond to situations like other anomalies do. \n           
		   </text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gravi">
			<text>Vortex</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gravi_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]At the moment of activation with a terrible force draws in itself everything that is within a radius of 10-15 meters.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Gravity.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Gravitational field.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,160, 82, 45]Screw, Gravy and Goldfish.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n An anomaly of presumably gravitational nature. When triggered, the tremendous power of the Vortex drags everything within the radius 10-15 meters towards the center. Victims drawn into the core have little to no chance of survival: their bodies are quickly constricted into a tight lump, only to be blown up in a powerful discharge of energy a moment later.  In some cases, they may levitate in air with agony, and soon their entire systems are shredded into mere skeletal and flesh parts.
				\n The anomaly remains stationary throughout its lifetime (a week on average). Easily recognizable in daylight by the air fluctuation above, dancing leaves, fragments of dismembered corpses lying around and a distinctive dark stain in the center. Highly dangerous at night since it can be revealed only by means of a detector or by throwing metal objects into it.
				\n The difference between a Whirligig and a Vortex is pretty simple: size and strength. The Vortex has a much larger range, much harder to escape from than a Whirligig, and it deals a lot more damage. Escaping the Vortex anomaly, once dragged in, can range in difficulty from easy to downright impossible, depending on the strength of the anomaly and the difficulty level. The type of armor worn is also very important, as the odds are that you will take at least one hit. One possible method of escaping, once drawn in, is to wait until the anomaly discharges, taking the hit. After discharging, the anomaly has no pulling power for approximately one second, allowing you to sprint out and escape it. This method will only be possible with armor with high anomaly protection. Wearing an exoskeleton and getting caught in a Vortex almost always ends in the player's death, since it prevents sprinting; meaning that the player cannot escape the anomaly once drawn in. \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_zhar">
			<text>Burner</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_zhar_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]When activated, creates a powerful column of high-temperature flame.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Fire.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]In the tunnels, basements and just in-depth places.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]No.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n The Burner can be a bit difficult to see, even in daylight, as it's only revealed by a faint heat haze. If the anomaly is triggered by either a living being or an object such as a metal bolt, it shoots out a tall pillar of flame in the air, burning everything in its vicinity. Though somewhat rare, the Burner anomaly is often found in clusters. Some clusters also emit extreme high ambient temperature, which hurts anything in their vicinity. Burners can emit temperatures as low as 100 degrees Celsius, up to several thousand, hot enough to crack concrete and melt metal, which explains why some Burners appear in areas that have massive cracks and severe damaged soil, while other sites are untouched.
				\n Burners are very dangerous at high difficulties, and can be extremely dangerous even with top-tier armor. The Burners don't have a set spawn point like other anomalies do, or even a set trigger point. Simply being in the same vicinity can trigger a conflagration. A tactic for avoiding damage is to first throw a bolt into the anomaly, triggering it, then quickly running through the jet of flame. This tactic, if used repeatedly and without delay, can mean the difference between traversing a cluster unharmed and getting scorched at least once. \n
			</text>
		</string>
					
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_radiation">
			<text>Point of radiation</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_radiation_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]When in the hearth - it irradiates the body.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]RAD.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Everywhere.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,240, 255, 240]No.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n The zone of high level - more than 50 microR/h - radiation. It is necessary to avoid a long stay in such places. \n 
				\n %c[0,47, 79, 79]Radiation%c[default] - radioactive spots left over from the 1986 catastrophe.\n
				\n Radiation contaminated sites can also be called an anomaly. Only on the cod of the Geiger counter can we roughly determine the boundaries of a dangerous place. Typically, the phonet is an abandoned technique. X-ray can be picked up on the edges of the game areas. The further the player moves north, the more often he will see the infected spots. At the Chernobyl nuclear power station it is not even worthwhile to put on without a suit with good radiation protection. \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gazirovka">
			<text>Fruit Punch</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gazirovka_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]When touched, he throws a cloud of poisonous gases.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Poisonous gas.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Next to the "acid mist".
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,107, 142, 35]Soul, Bubble, Firefly, Kolobok.%c[default] \n
				\n\n
				\n The Fruit Punch is a puddle of lambent green liquid that is easily visible in almost any environment due to its bright glow and distinctive hissing and bubbling noises. On contact with creatures or objects such as bolts, a Fruit Punch lights up brightly and emits a sharp hissing sound. It is extremely corrosive, damaging creatures and objects on contact. Any matter left in a Fruit Punch will eventually dissolve, hinting at the anomaly's corrosive nature and spelling doom for any protective suit. For players, contact with a Fruit Punch will cause damage with each 'flash'. This anomaly is commonly found underground.
				\n Concerning its characteristics, it is generally accepted that it derives from the remnants of a highly radioactive spill of some reactive substance that gained its anomalous abilities from the Zone. Its corrosive properties are exhibited by its intense and rapid damage to all living tissue and inorganic matter, metal and plastic alike. \n
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,173, 216, 230]"An anomaly of unknown nature. On contact inflicts injuries similar to the effects of a strong acid. Forms three types of artifacts: Slime, Slug and Mica."%c[0,215,215,215]%c[default] \n
			</text>
		</string>
		
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_kisel">
			<text>Kissel</text>
		</string>
		<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_kisel_text">
			<text>\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]Information:
				\n\n
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Effect%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]When touching, causes acid burns.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Damaging factor%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Acid.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Place of Appearance%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,215,215,215]Primarily in the dungeons.
				\n%c[0,143, 188, 143]•%c[0,154, 205, 50] Born artifacts%c[0,143, 188, 143] - %c[0,107, 142, 35]Slime, Slug, Mica, Bubble.%c[default] \n
				\n\n    
				\n Liquid education is not clear until the end of nature. It looks like a glowing bright green slime, well visible in the dark. When in contact with the body, it causes injuries similar to those of strong acids. In a suit with a closed cycle of breathing, the damage will be minimal. In this anomaly non-stop strange chemical processes occur. Their result is acid, corrosive to the skin, and poisonous gases that equally corrode the lungs. Fortunately,% c [0,107, 142, 35] Kissel% c [default] is easy to see in the open area. Worse, when you suddenly find it in a dark tunnel. \n
			</text>
		</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_emission">
		<text>Blowout</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_emission_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Blowouts%c[default], also known as %c[guide_blue]Emissions%c[default], are sudden emissions of a huge amount of radiation.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
			\nStrong winds, thunderclouds and scarlet red sky appear with the onset of the ejection, accompanied by numerous eruptions of thunder and a deep roar underfoot.\n
			\nThese events begin with a sharp surge of radioactive, abnormal and psionic activity - and end up destroying most of life when radiation waves cover the Zone.\n
			\nDespite the fact that it is extremely lethal, it is still quite easy to survive as a result of the release, hiding in buildings or underground tunnels, until it ends.\n
			\nIn much the same way as a psi-storm, the huge amount of energy released by the outburst seems to "recharge" many anomalies, allowing stalkers to find new artifacts in them.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_phantom">
		<text>Phantom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_phantom_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Phantoms%c[default] are illusory beings that exist in the mind, and not physically.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
			\nWhile it is difficult to classify it as an anomaly or a mutant, the phantom is an involuntary mental projection of the mutant that is currently in the Zone. \n
			\nThese projections are always accompanied by audible "howling" noise and appear luminous and transparent, gradually floating towards the victim through the walls and through the air. \n
			\nIt is not known why they only take the form of mutants, including those that the stalker has never encountered, and why they never see those that are now extinct, such as Tark. \n
			\nThe leading theory of this phenomenon suggests that the living mutants of the Zone are to some extent strongly connected with the noosphere, and that due to this, psi fields inadvertently imprint their appearance and hostile nature in the minds of its victims. \n
			\nSome stalkers equip their helmets with a fine mesh of copper wire and also their lodging for the night and even tents in order to protect themselves from the harmful effects of the ejection. Some stalkers constantly carry small sapper shovels with them, and if they feel that an ejection is coming soon and there is not a single shelter around, they immediately begin to dig a hole and dig in it. In 50% of cases, this method of shelter from ejection can save lives in the zone. \n
			\nIt is rumored that an experimental drug was delivered to the Zone that allows the body to go into suspended animation for a short time and then wake up, but this drug did not pass proper testing.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psistorm">
		<text>Psi-storm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psistorm_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue]Psi-storms%c[default] consist of several psi-vortices that release a deadly amount of psionic energy.\n
			\n%c[guide_green]Information:%c[default]
			\nThese unusual weather anomalies are a very recent phenomenon in the Zone, and there are many assumptions about what causes them to appear.\n
			\nStarting with a purple-pink haze and large formations of thunderclouds, very little time is required to create a psi storm and begin the destruction of the Zone.\n
			\nIf the stalker's equipment gives the owner greater protection from psionic damage or uses drugs to provide a similar effect, one can survive the loss of individual psi-vortices during a storm without shelter.\n
			\nThis is ensured by the fact that they immediately begin to meditate after that, since even the most trained stalkers will still find themselves in a very delicate situation after such an impact.\n
			\nLike emissions, a huge amount of energy dissipated by a psi storm, it seems, "recharges" many anomalies, allowing stalkers to find in them new artifacts.\n
			\nSome stalkers equip their helmets with a fine wire mesh net and also their lodging to protect themselves from the harmful effects of the release.
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>